♪ You woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your momma always said
you'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said,
you're one in a million ♪
♪ You got to burn to shine ♪
♪ But you were
born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
in your eyes ♪
♪ When you
woke up this morning ♪
♪ All that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never
told you about ♪
♪ Right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're
lookin' good, baby ♪
♪ I believe you're
feelin' fine ♪
♪ Shame about it,
born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
in your eyes ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got a blue moon in your eyes ♪
♪ You woke up this morning ♪
♪ The world turned upside down ♪
♪ Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got that
shotgun shine ♪
♪ Shame about it,
born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
in your eyes ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
New York's only classic rock
station, Q-104.3.
Look at this.
The house sang out to us
of both Miami and Taormina
where we had our honeymoon.
Nicole said, let's buy it.
Can just about smell the salt.
You mean the painting
or the view?
Both.
That's called
the "trumpay la oil."
Fool the eye.
It was done by an artist right
over here in West Hempstead.
I'll be damned.
Follow me, Jerry.
This little bitch is for you.
It's a Whirlpool Duet.
Top of the line. Same as mine.
Nicole is head over heels
with it.
This is above and beyond,
Carmine.
Well, thank my father, too,
may he rest in peace.
This is for Freeport.
It's a token.
You know it's
my understanding, Carmine,
that Johnny's still sore
about that.
That's why I appreciate
your support.
I'm moved up here now.
You and me are gonna
do great things together.
Amen.
Daddy! Daddy!
The boat is sinking!
Carmine! My God!
I just sailed her up
from Miami three weeks ago.
She was fine.
You should call
the coast guard, Carmine.
Whoa!
Oh! Ow!
Oh, shit.
It's okay, take it easy.
After all these years
of marriage,
you know what you find
yourself thinking
in your private moments...
Please, God, let me die first.
I don't wanna miss him.
Well, he's gonna be all right.
You're lucky.
In some way,
you've been spared that.
Well, you and Tony
calling it quits now.
Maybe we should
cancel the party.
Maybe he'll be fine
by his birthday.
You know he's turning 75, Ma,
that's a milestone.
Ooh.
He's got some bruising.
Very lucky man.
Those hedges broke his fall.
But a few days of rest
and he should be fine.
The neurologist is
giving him a final look,
and then you can take him home.
Thank you so much, Doctor.
- You're welcome.
- Thank God.
Ooh.
His roofing days are over,
I'll tell you that right now.
I guess, huh?
So, uh, what do you
think about the party?
Jeez, Ma, I--
well, I think
we should go for it.
Well, what do you think
about inviting Tony?
Well, that's the thing.
I don't know if I should or not.
Everybody would understand
if you didn't.
- You're separated.
- I know, I know.
But just the idea of
having a family party
in the backyard without Tony
there manning the grill,
playing host,
it wouldn't be the same.
Shh. It's gonna be okay, baby.
Why don't they take
care of this man?
I think it's
a very wise decision.
What decision?
I haven't made one.
I thought I heard
you say that you had.
That he wasn't coming.
Maserati.
Kinda draws attention, no?
Ah, true. Friends of ours, most
of 'em, probably wouldn't own it.
It was always a dream of mine
to own a fine
Italian sports car.
A salut' then.
And in the guinea gray it,
uh, looks fantastic.
Tops out a 176 miles per hour.
Standing quarter, 13 and change.
- How many horses?
- 390.
What'd that set
you back about, uh...
99 and change.
You're spendin' like
you're already on the throne.
- Had a good year.
- Oh, God bless.
While we're doin'
car talk here, Phil...
Madonna mi',
he won't let that thing go.
He owed me money
and he was duckin' me.
Look, I'm not
sayin' you're wrong.
Phil treats nickels
like manhole covers.
Believe me, I know.
But the captains loyal to me
need to know
I stand behind them right now.
Fuckin' Little Carmine.
This asshole's givin' away
washing machines.
You believe that?
He don't have collision
insurance, fuckin' Phil?
His son-in-law's a broker.
They let it lapse
lookin' for a better rate.
Fuckin' idiot.
Tony, I ruled in your favor.
The racetrack.
The money Philly owed you.
Well, if I'm payin' for it,
we do it at Pussy's
or we don't do it at all.
His wife's runnin'
the body shop now.
So I can at least
control expenses.
Thanks.
Come on.
Get in, take ya for a ride.
Fuckin' thing's so powerful,
I had to take a lesson
from the dealer last night.
Pretty low.
How does Ginny like the car?
She loves it.
But she hasn't
driven with me yet.
With her knee, she has a
little trouble gettin' into the seat.
Oh.
Whoa.
Tony. Hi.
Hey, Ang'. How are ya?
Good.
Listen, a friend of mine
banged up his car pretty good
so I was thinkin', you know,
maybe help us both out
and, uh, throw
a little business your way.
You didn't need to come down.
You just could've phoned me.
The thing is, I gotta
pay for the repairs.
Long story.
I distracted him
while he was drivin'.
Anyway, the point
bein' that, uh,
anything you can do
to keep costs in line,
would be a big help to me.
Well, you look like
you're doin' pretty good
since we had
that phone call, uh,
you know, you asked me could
you take over Puss's body shop.
Thank you for that, Tony.
You didn't have to say yes,
with all the other kinda
business you do through here.
Uh, anyway, his name is Phil,
and, uh, Carmela sends her love.
Please say hello...
Finally.
I left a message
I was gonna come by.
Well, I got in late.
Girl called in sick.
You should get a new one.
Have a seat.
May I get you anything?
How's your father?
Much better.
Oh, thanks.
He'll be fine for
the party, thank God.
Well, that's good.
What party?
75th birthday?
You know, the surprise party
we talked about last summer?
Oh, yeah, that's comin' up?
- Yeah, next Saturday.
- Oh.
But actually that's
why I wanted to come by.
'Cause I think maybe
it would be best--
be easier, anyway,
for both of us, if uh...
If I went at it alone.
And not have you there.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, you know my father
would love to have you there,
you know he's crazy
about your sausages
and all the rest of it, but...
I thought, uh, you know,
why put us and--
and people in an
uncomfortable situation.
Well, I decided right away
when we broke up
I wasn't comin'.
Really?
I'm so glad you understand.
It was hard for me
to come to this decision,
let alone tell you.
Well, I'd like
to contribute, anyway.
No, Mom and I are
taking care of it.
For Hugh's 75th? I insist.
You know, I would rather see
you go back to your therapist.
I'd like to see you
go to a therapist.
And I'm not the only one.
- Oh, really?
- Mm.
Well, you can tell them all
that I can't afford it.
Well, it's not really
your business anymore,
whether I go or what!
Brought you some
Danish and coffee.
Fuckin' medication.
I can't think.
Can't stay awake.
It don't have that side effect.
But it'll help your outlook
if you take it consistently
like you're supposed to.
What's on?
It said in the guide
it's an Italian movie.
But even with the captions,
I can't tell what's what.
They had Jesus hangin'
off a helicopter.
But you could tell
it was a dummy.
You know who I saw
at the bakery?
How the fuck could I know?
Rosalie Aprile.
Said they're havin'
a surprise party
for Carmela's father next week.
He's gonna be 75.
You get an invite?
No, but we go way back
to when Moses wore short pants.
I better call Hugh.
Tell him not to expect me.
It's a surprise party, Jun'.
What, are we children?
Anyway, at our age
it's enough surprise
we're still alive every morning.
What city and state, please?
In West Orange.
DeAngelis, Hugo.
The call can automatically
be completed by pressing one,
for an additional charge
of .35¢.
The fuck.
It's over anyhow.
Hello?
Hugo, como esta?
Who is this?
Corrado. Soprano.
Oh, ho ho ho.
Corrado. How are ya?
How am I.
I'm a prisoner in my own home,
Hugh, is how I am.
What do we live for?
Yeah.
Anyhow, I wanted
to wish you a buona fortuna,
and also send you my regrets.
I'd love to be at your jubilee.
Junior.
Jubilee?
But the federal government says I can't
leave the house,
and my family keeps me sedated.
Bobby told me
it was a surprise party
but I told him, I go,
at our age it's enough surprise
every day when we get up
in the mornin',
right?
Oh, I suppose so.
So happy birthday, my friend,
and many more.
Arrivederci.
♪ Maybe you won't
recognize me now ♪
recognize me now... ♪
To think, when I got
outta the joint,
I thought an airbag
was Paulie Walnuts.
How we do this week?
Good.
The Acura dealer,
what's his name,
he took 20 units.
Carlo gave me the okay to make
some personnel changes
at the warehouse.
Your call.
I don't know.
The airbag thing.
It earns good.
It's not hard work,
Christ knows, but...
But what?
Think I could be of a lot
more service to you in other areas.
And gettin' straightened out
wouldn't hurt neither.
Just eat what's on
your plate right now.
I mean, Christ,
what's it been, a month?
I'm a team player, cousin.
I'm Charlie Hustle.
If that's what you want,
I'll do it.
Look.
If you need some money...
Get the fuck outta here.
All right.
Let's go get a drink.
What should I get Hugh
DeAngelis for his birthday?
I was thinkin' cigars
but then I figured
you were probably
gonna bring some.
Well, actually
I decided not to go.
In light of the situation,
I went, I saw Carm,
I told her I thought
it'd be best if I sit it out.
Hi, Phil. Joe.
Where's your
brother-in-law, doll?
I wouldn't know.
Hey, Phillip,
how the hell are ya?
How's the neck?
Where's the car?
We all passed a lotta water
since the old days, huh?
I was away when all that shit
went down with your brother.
What the fuck happened?
We don't like to talk about it.
Your car's in here, Phil.
It's all set.
What the fuck is this?
It was a front-end
collision, Phil.
This new paint
isn't as brilliant.
It's factory paint,
same as original.
It is different, it's duller.
Something's off with the seat.
What is it, Phil?
Feels off kilter.
Try it, Joey.
You're right; it's off its axis.
It reclines strange too.
Try it.
Nobody said anything
about the seats.
This is unacceptable.
Come on, Joey.
Give me a call when you
get the job done, all right?
A couple of days, Phil.
Phil, we did
what was asked of us.
Call me when it's done right.
So Dad,
how does dinner
at Vesuvio's sound
for your birthday next week?
Just us.
We'll come here first
for the presents,
and then we'll go over there.
Sure, sure.
That sounds fine.
Did somebody tell you something?
I know all about it.
You can save
the cloak and dagger.
AJ!
Huh, what?
Junior Soprano
told me all about it.
That miserable fucking man.
Ugh!
You don't know the half.
Relax.
I'm fine with knowin'.
At my age, it's surprise enough
to be able to get
outta bed every morning.
So who's comin' to this shindig?
God damn him!
All of us, your brother,
Lester, Dr. Fegoli...
Russ Fegoli? He's in town?
He retired from
the foreign service.
But they were livin' out
in Marin Country or wherever.
Well, they settled on Jersey.
Octavia, the oldest, lives here.
Wait, who's Dr. Fago?
Fegoli. Feg.
She of the five-page
Christmas card.
"...And on Flag Day,
Papa Russ shook hands
with Andrew Cuomo..."
What an honor. BFD.
The Fegoli kids
finished college.
That's what sticks in your craw.
What sticks in my craw is that
when he got that medal
you two weren't even
invited to the ceremony.
It was out in California.
They knew that your father
doesn't like to be out of his element.
Now, here's someone we can
all be proud of, Anthony.
Dr. Fegoli served
in the state department.
In Rome, he was career assistant
to the ambassador
to the Vatican.
He got a medal
from the Pope himself.
Wow.
But when we were kids
together in the Navy,
he had such a bad
case of the crabs
we used to call him
the governor of Maryland.
Hey, Hugh,
stop acting like a child.
Oh, lighten up.
He's old enough to hear.
She's right, knock it off.
Who else is comin'?
Freddy Di Novi...
Tony'll love him.
Who else?
Dad, Tony isn't
coming to the party.
Why won't he come?
Well, I felt that, uh,
since we're separated,
we should get used to the idea
of living separate lives.
Oh, that's a crock a shit.
Hugh, don't talk
to her like that.
This is very difficult for her.
I've known the man
for 20-something years!
It's his house!
How's it gonna look?
I talked to Tony about it;
he's in agreement with me.
Because you put
the screws to him.
Fine, I'll cancel the party.
Go right the hell ahead
because I'm not comin'
if the man of the house
isn't there.
Yeah?
Tony, it's Angie.
We did all the repairs
you said on Phil's car.
He came today and now he found
a dent in the rear.
His seat, there's
a problem with that.
His seat?
I didn't wanna get
into these extras
without checking with you.
Ang', honey, you wanna run
a body shop, run a body shop.
You said could you claim
your piece of the garage.
So you wanna be
a woman in business,
then do what you think
the situation calls for.
I just wanna put
my kids through college.
That's a good thing, Ang'.
You know some women left alone
like that would've given up.
Tony, before I outlay
for these costs,
yeah, I need to know--
Ang', I'm not there,
what do I know?
It's your call.
Ton'? What's up?
Pussy's body shop is
one of your stops, right?
Well they're fixin'
the fuckin' Shah of Iran's car.
Uh, can you be there
when he picks it up?
Make sure he's happy,
but don't let
the shit spiral out of control.
Right. I'll take care of it.
Thanks.
On my way to Welsh Farms,
get a triple blueberry sundae.
Good for you.
Enjoy.
Hot summer night.
Go for it. You deserve it.
All right, yeah.
I'll talk to ya later.
- Opus.
- Fine choice.
Angelo, here,
spoke very highly of you
and how you handled yourself
with him in Pennsylvania.
That's why I wanted to meet you.
We were like Frick and Frack
in the can.
Angelo's my buddy.
He knew all the Jackie
Gleason stuff by heart.
He acted all the parts hisself.
Do a little bit for Rusty.
The mambo thing.
Mambo?
Oh! Carlos was teaching
you the mambo?
That's a different story!
Get out! Get out!
So how's your reentry been?
You doin' okay?
Yeah.
Tony's been good with me.
I always liked your cousin.
He's a real gentleman.
Angelo's lookin'
out for you, too.
I told Rusty that you
might need a little earn.
Well, yeah, I could use
a little cash injection.
Maybe a push up the pyramid.
You know, time served.
We need somethin' done.
Nice little payday for you,
and an opportunity for you to
hone that rep you left behind.
And this involves...
Somebody needs to go.
Anyone I know?
New York guy, not Jersey.
Who's he with?
Friend of a friend.
Not a friend of ours.
Friend of Johnny's.
You guys gotta settle that shit.
It's not the boat.
It's Lorraine Calluzzo.
Rainey Calluzzo.
Little Carmine
went to school with her.
They go back that far.
Kill a woman. Come on.
I can't sign on right now.
I wanna give my cousin
the benefit of the doubt.
He don't want us involved in
this problem over here anyway.
Why don't you think about it
for a bit?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
But thanks, guys.
We had a big talk
over here the other day
and the consensus seems
to want your presence
at my father's party.
Well, that's nice but
it's kinda short notice now.
Look, it's for
my father, not me.
I made plans
to go fishin' with Sil.
Well, he really wants you there.
If you could find a
way to make it,
I know he would be very happy.
He's very fond of you.
The New York salsicc',
hickory wood, whatever.
You're not usin' Artie?
Yeah, I got him doin'
appetizers and salads,
but, uh, he's really there
as a guest.
I am cooking.
Tomorrow's gonna be a madhouse,
just, living hell.
I don't know, I'll...
I'll see what I can do.
Thank you, Tony,
I appreciate it.
Uh, Jerry say to refrigerate.
Okay. I think there is
room in the garage.
- Hey, Carm.
- Tony.
I know you're shorthanded, uh,
I thought you might need
some help around here today.
It's my weekend with the boys.
They'll stay out of the way.
Aunt Carmela's nice enough
to let you guys enjoy her pool,
and you wanna
destroy her property.
It's a beach chair.
It can get wet.
Don't get smart!
You wanna go home?
What can I do?
Ah, the dips.
I forgot the dips.
I gotta duck out later.
I could pick some up
for you at Grand Union.
Grand Union closed
its doors 10 years ago.
You know what, frig the dip.
They're gonna have
to survive with salsa.
Can I make you a cocktail?
I make a mean Rusty Nail.
Now? No.
Thanks again for lettin'
the kids take a swim.
Aw, sure.
Anytime, you know that.
Cheers.
They love bein' here.
This is truly a beautiful home.
What, are you here,
five years now?
I asked you to get up at 11:00.
We got a lot to do today.
Well, you were supposed to send
this to Mr. Wegler for summer school.
Put it down!
Greetings, birthday people.
You are here, which is great.
You can help with the set-up.
- Hi, Mrs. Soprano.
- Hi.
Uh, uh, Finn this
is our Uncle Tony.
Tony this is
Meadow's friend, Finn.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm making grandpa's favorite
maple-walnut icebox cake.
We have cake. Jerry just--
Why don't you take a swim?
I know you're hot.
Do you have a towel?
I'll bring you a coffee, too.
- I'll be outside.
- Cake pan?
Meadow, I have
a lot to do today.
Hello?
I'm making dessert, to help?
Seems like a nice guy.
Yep.
- Any luck with Kelly?
- No.
I been scourin'
the internet for any trace.
Here is your cake pan.
And you're gonna
clean up your baking mess.
I can imagine how much
you must miss her.
Your only daughter.
What was she like 11
when she lived with you guys?
We had her 12th birthday party
right before she moved out.
How'd she do
in school back then?
Straight A's.
Oh, my God, what is
the matter with them?
Don't lift that by yourself,
Hugh.
Wait for some help.
What are you doing here?
You always do this!
The party is not for hours!
- He needs help.
- What am I doin' here?
I'm returning your port-a-vac.
You said you needed it.
Happy birthday, Grandpa.
Later for that,
get your uncle out here.
He left; he said he told you
he had to bolt for a minute.
He asked us to watch the twins.
Here, help me with this.
Oh, my goodness, what a bother.
Excuse us for living.
How ya doin'? I'm Tony.
Oh, yeah, the other
Tony's cousin, right?
It reclines perfectly, try it.
Fuck that.
I don't feel like
I'm sittin' at 12:00.
You're sittin' at 12:00.
May I?
I don't give a fuck.
You can sit in there
till fuckin' St. Gennaro.
It'll still need
to be dealt with.
This car went through
a major collision.
Seems okay.
How could it be okay
if it's askew?
What's the matter, Joey?
You got a fuckin' eye problem?
Look like Stevie Wonder,
your eyes rollin' around.
Aw, what'd I say?
I didn't say nothin', Phil.
Replacin' the seat
will cost a fortune.
Give me a break, Phil.
The seat is fine.
You just have a problem
with the grain
on the leather from the factory.
You think I'm stupid?
Ho, ho!
Don't take it out on me.
Come on, Joey.
Hey, Phil.
Now, how about this.
They replace the tracks
under the seat,
maybe throw in
a CD player in the dash.
We already did that.
We replaced the tracks.
He's got a CD player.
Jesus God, Duke,
they're hosin' us for
a $2,000 factory seat.
Come on, Joey.
Tony, nice to meet ya.
Come on, you comin'?
Joe, try to keep
him cooled down.
Here ya go, Freddy.
Get it, Jason, come on!
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Ma, what?
Dr. Fegoli, Russ.
- What?
- He's allergic to tomatoes.
All right, so we
will deal with it.
Jesus.
Don't you have any hors
d'oeuvres without tomatoes?
The prosciutto-wrapped chevre.
Rosalie just took 'em out.
An Italian allergic
to pommodori.
Dio mio.
You have my sympathies.
Well, it wasn't
always like this.
Started when they gave me
radiation for my prostate.
Don't ask me why.
So did you know Monsignor Kelly?
He was in charge of the tours
at all the catacombs?
I made you a plate, Russ.
Thank you, Mary.
You know, Carmela's
mother-in-law, Livia,
detested northern cooking.
Really, why?
She skeeved the butter.
The father was like that, too.
The whole Soprano
bunch over there.
So many neopolitans and
sigilian' feel that way.
Well, you really have
to go to Italy to know,
and so many of them don't.
I ate like a champ all
the way up and down the boot.
The whole two weeks.
But those recipes that you
used to send me from Tuscany.
Lena...
My God, they were a revelation.
Bollito misto, osso bucco...
Mmm.
The lovely Carmela Soprano.
Would you like
to say a few words?
Oh, he's back, thank God.
Will you get
the guests arriving?
See?
And where the hell is Tony?
Have a glass of wine, Carm.
Calm you down a little.
He is bringing the charcoal
and the sausage.
He's always gotta wait
till the last minute.
I heard that!
- Agh, finally.
- Hi, Tony.
Got no faith in me.
I wonder why?
Pins and needles,
needles and pins.
Palumbo's.
The birthday boy's favorite.
- Where is he?
- He's out back.
Oh, good.
Honey, try to pace yourself...
♪ 'Fritto misto bacala,
a couple of meatballs too ♪
Hey, there he is!
Hey, happy birthday to Hugh,
got sazeecha for you!
Russ, wait'll ya
taste this stuff.
There's nothin' else like it.
Tony, I want you to meet
a couple of our oldest friends,
Dr. Russ and Lena Fegoli.
Nice to meet you, sir.
My son-in-law, well,
whatever, Tony Soprano.
Hey.
A doctor in the house, huh?
That's good, 'cause somebody
usually
goes down at these things.
He's just joking.
Unfortunately my doctorate
is in international affairs.
Oh.
From Princeton.
G.I. Bill.
So you're a doctor like,
uh, Kissinger's a doctor.
- Yes.
- Oh.
Russ had an audience
with four popes.
Oh.
What section did you all sit in?
Aw, idiot.
T.B., make sure you
shoot the food tables
before they're pillaged.
Well, I'd, uh...
Love to stay and chat,
but I got a fire to start.
Nice to meet ya, Doc.
Nice to meet you.
Everybody!
Could you gather 'round please?
Everybody, everybody!
Come on over.
I would like to make a toast
to the man of the hour.
A very special man.
A man who I love
more than words
could possibly say.
My father.
- Here-here.
You are the best father
and grandfather in the world.
- Salut'.
Salut'.
Speech! Speech!
You are the greatest,
my little Melly.
Oh.
- Thank you for everything.
- Mm-hmm.
Tony, thank you for
having us at your home.
Mar', my lovely bride.
Still the prettiest girl
in the world.
Thank you for puttin' up
with me all these years.
Aww.
Thank all you freeloaders
for coming!
So why don't you
open up your gifts, Dad?
Not now, Carmela,
It's very, uh, mercenary.
Well, good, people
spent money on them.
I'll break the ice.
Here.
Open this one.
It's from him.
Aw, you're too much.
A Stratocaster?
Aww.
A Beretta.
Ooh, aww...
Shotgun, oh wow.
This is...
I don't know what to say.
It's a Giubileo 12-gauge.
28-inch barrel.
Nice to have money.
Get me another
Rolling Rock, Jay.
What time did you
start drinkin' today?
Probably right after you got up.
Oh, cuz!
Tony, can you bring
the camera over here
and get a shot of this?
Sure, I got nothin'
better to do.
Expect a freezer full
of venison this year.
You got it, kid.
Beautiful piece.
The over-under action,
the engraving,
they're artisans.
And you know, I've been to
the Beretta studio in Brescia.
No kiddin'.
I'd love to see that.
You know that company
goes back to the 1500s.
Madonn'.
Sure, the best pieces,
they never export, you see.
I want one and all here to know
what a wild man
Hugo was in his day.
Remember what he did at the
bund meeting in Paterson, Russ?
Threw that cherry bomb
on those Krauts?
Yeah, tell that one.
You made my father's year
with that gun.
He deserves it.
You look beat, Tony;
why don't you take a break?
Nah, I'm all right.
Could use a beer, though.
Well, you got it.
Thanks.
Salut'.
How's that look? Done?
You're the grillmeister.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I still think we have the
greatest legal system in the world.
But it's becoming more
and more discriminatory.
I mean, if you're
a minority, or worse,
an immigrant from
an Arab country,
civil rights don't apply at all.
No place is the breach
of civil rights
more evident than
the penal system.
Rehabilitation? Please.
Yeah.
The nature of the system
instills a convict mentality
to the point where prison
becomes the only venue
where the convict can function.
My little bleedin' heart.
She is wise beyond her years.
She better be.
All the money I'm spendin' over
at liberal university
in sunny Harlem.
Come here.
How you doin'?
- Good.
- Yeah?
Remember when you
were a little girl
what I used to call you?
What do you mean
you don't remember?
You were too young to remember?
- Don't!
- No!
How come you don't remember?
Remember what I used
to call you, huh?
- Ooh.
- Hey, ow!
You know Hugh built this house?
Your friend's maxin' out the
situation down there at Puss's.
Sure.
Factory seat. Two k.
I tried.
Well, I'd hate to see Ang'
get stuck with that.
Then again, her friend
over there is takin' me
to the cleaners
with this divorce shit.
I gotta belt-tighten.
Can we get some able-bodied
seamen over here?
Tony B.?
What, am I a fuckin' slave?
Ho!
I didn't have a drop.
God damn it.
Lester'll drive;
he's in the bathroom.
Watch your head.
Hey! Virginia Mayo.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry for everything,
what can I say?
Get my boy home safe.
You're sorry for what?
- Aw...
- No-no I wanna hear.
Oh, please, Carmela.
The off-color jokes,
the sausage twirling...
Tony.
These are cultured Italians.
Russ is a success, a diplomat.
This was a shock for them.
And he's such a diplomat
he insults his host?
You heard what he said to Tony.
He is a pompous man.
He always was.
Let's talk about this
another time.
That's why you
didn't want Tony here.
Had nothin' to do with
the marital situation.
All along, it was so that
your cultured Italian friends,
who were born and raised
on Arthur Avenue I might add,
wouldn't meet your
gavone son-in-law.
He made us all
look like gavones.
Whatever we are
I am proud of it,
unlike you obviously.
I have always been
proud of my heritage.
Oh, bullshit.
I remember you telling
aunt rose you were glad
DeAngelis didn't end in a vowel.
I never said that!
And when Meadow came out,
"Oh my God, she's so dark".
You're drunk. I'm going home.
You know, there are
Italians all around
with their closet self-loathing.
I just never wanted to believe
my mother was one of 'em.
And now what the fuck
are you crying about?
You're secret is out.
Marco.
Polo.
Marco?
Marco. Polo.
Fish outta water!
You're it, Ton'!
Takin' a T-O.
Marco. Polo.
Here let me-- let me get this.
No, I'm fine. You have fun.
No, no, really. Let me...
Forget it, I'll get it.
Tony, put me down!
You look like
you could use a dip!
No, don't you, I'm serious!
One.
- Two.
- Tony, don't!
Three!
- You bastards!
- You're it, Carm.
Whoo!
Idiots.
Hey, don't let her get out.
You--no!
Ho!
You're still it!
Marco.
Polo.
All right.
Pleasant dreams, hammers.
Night, Dad.
Good night, Grandma.
Good night.
Your grandma's not a maid.
I'll put 'em in the hamper.
- What's this?
- I don't know.
- Yes, you do.
- Shut up.
Am I talkin' to you, Justin?
I asked you a question, Jason.
Pins.
From the '96 Olympics
in Atlanta it looks like.
That's when you were
stationed in Saudi Arabia,
right, Dad?
Yes, that's right.
But I'm talkin' to your brother.
You took this tonight,
didn't you?
I borrowed it from AJ.
You stole this from your cousin
who opens his house to you?
I found it on the floor
way in back of AJ's closet.
He doesn't care.
With all the stuff he has?
He got to go to the Olympics
and everything.
I love where he lives.
I don't wanna come back here.
My son steals
from his own family.
You're gonna return it
tomorrow and apologize.
Where are your Gameboys?
That's mine.
Jason's is in the drawer.
I'm givin' both of these
to the Salvation Army.
I didn't do nothing!
You're just as bad as he is
'cause you didn't stop him!
We should get going, AJ.
I don't wanna drop you off
at Patrick's too late.
Call me when you
get to Patrick's.
Yeah, I'll try.
He's in a bad cell area.
He'll try?
Just showin' her he's not a kid.
Mm...
I think he's showin' her
more than that.
Well, that's inevitable.
It's scary is what that is.
He'll be fine.
He's in love.
Oh, please.
You know what
it's like at that age.
Hmm?
Can't wait to see each other.
Can't keep your
hands off each other.
Tony, what are you doing?
What am I doin'?
Tony, let's call it a night.
Why?
- You tired?
- Yes.
Come on.
Artie is right over there.
He's comatose.
Tony...
This is nice, no?
Doesn't it feel nice?
I didn't say that.
No, Tony, don't.
Shh...
So which type of,
uh, torture instrument
we going to use?
That will wake up the neighbors
you know.
Yeah.
You have to go where you
have like a two-by-four...
Hello?
Blundetto.
How can I help you?
I'm in.
You asleep?
Here you go, Joey.
It's bigger than last week's.
Hey, Crystal.
The room is empty.
Come on, time is money.
Thanks. Phil'll be very happy.
Yeah. Send him and John
my best, huh?
Good night, Heather.
Good night, Muz.
- You're off?
- Yeah.
I'm goin' downtown.
Me too.
Let's go.
See ya next week, Joe.
♪ So mother
when you've seen me ♪
♪ Don't forget
I'm your boy too ♪
♪ I know my brother
has done you proud ♪
♪ He's one foot in the grave ♪
♪ Mother, don't you
recognize me now ♪
Hey, Joe.
Hey. Tony, right?
What, you come here too?
♪ I'm a burglar
in the first degree ♪
♪ But it don't
seem to worry me ♪
♪ And I'll be down on
Cannon Street ♪
♪ Passport in my hand ♪
♪ Should you not recognize me
I have heavily made-up eyes ♪
♪ Momma, you won't
recognize me now ♪
♪ Brother, you won't
♪ Hello there ♪
♪ Sister, you won't
recognize me now ♪
♪ Mother, you won't
♪ Whoo hoo ♪
♪ I'll be so tired ♪
♪ So tired ♪