♪ You woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
you'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
you're one in a million ♪
♪ You got to burn to shine ♪
♪ But you were born
under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
in your eyes ♪
♪ When you woke up
this morning ♪
♪ All that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never
told you about ♪
♪ Right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're lookin' good baby ♪
♪ I believe
you're feelin' fine ♪
♪ Shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
in your eyes ♪
♪ Singin' now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon in your eyes ♪
♪ See you woke up this morning ♪
♪ The world turned upside down ♪
♪ Lord above,
things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got that
shotgun shine ♪
♪ Shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
in your eyes, yeah ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
Yeah! Whoo!
♪ Down the square ♪
♪ Found the last tank
filled it full right here ♪
♪ Well I want it higher ♪
♪ A thousand feet tall ♪
Dad.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Well, I got an office here.
You come down with Finn?
And some people.
Promise me no, uh,
drinkin' and drivin'.
Who's your designated driver?
I'm not the one with
all the dents in their car.
All right, have fun, huh?
Need some money?
Have a good time, sweetheart.
Be careful!
- You see Meadow?
- Yeah.
I wish I knew she was here.
I wonder what the fuck
she's thinkin'.
I'm sorry, Ton.
Some kid had a seizure upstairs.
It's been a horrible night.
Hey, Ton, Vito and Gene
just called.
They're five minutes away.
We're leaving. Here.
All right, uh, call 'em
and tell 'em to meet us
at Bud's Butter Bun
on Broadway and 18th.
All right.
Did I just see your father?
He's got an office here.
Saturday night?
That's dedication.
The guy sure can
put in the hours.
Let's go someplace else.
Tony's spendin'
so much time at the club.
You think that might have
something to do with you?
Oh, if you think
I'm gonna blow this guy
for your sick purposes,
you are sadly mistaken.
So go on about this
phone call the other night.
It was just some guy
with a Southern accent.
Christopher grabbed the phone
and yelled at him
for callin' the house.
Said he'd see him down there.
Down where?
Did you check
the log on his cell?
Not since I almost
got caught doin' that,
and I am not doin' it again.
Wait'll he goes into the shower.
See if there's a 4-0-4 or 3-3-6,
and memorize any other
numbers you don't recognize.
Oof...
What's the matter?
I gotta go to the bathroom.
- I know, you said.
- No, I, g--
I-I gotta go.
Number two.
I'll take you to your car.
No, I gotta go now.
Oh, my God.
You okay?
We're almost there.
Try to relax.
Don't you got a general
anesthetic or somethin'?
This lidocaine didn't do much.
And we are... done.
Jan, wanna do your thing?
Just keep a little pressure.
All right.
I'm gonna get this
down to the lab.
See what's what.
Okay.
There we go.
You okay?
You think he got it all?
We hope so.
Meantime, there's
a canteen on level L.
I'll let you know
when the results come back.
Does having a bowel movement
relieve the pain?
Yeah.
Would you describe the diarrhea
as loose or liquid?
Liquid.
But this is gettin'
so I'm afraid
to be away from the toilet.
I'm so scared I'm
gonna have an accident.
Is this tender?
No.
Sit up.
How's your personal life?
What do you mean?
Well, sometimes GI disturbances
are stress-related.
Is there anything unusual
that might be giving
you the jim-jams?
I just want somethin'
for my stomach
so I can quit
goin' to the bathroom.
That's what's givin' me stress.
Why don't you get dressed?
We'll talk in my office.
I hear you're spending time
with today's youth.
You lost me.
Meadow said she saw you
at Adriana's club.
I gotta explain
my business to you now?
After so many years?
No, it's your life, Tony.
Got that right.
What'd you do to your head?
Did you fall again?
Banged it on the medicine chest.
Don't worry about it.
It's nothin'.
There's your allowance.
Now, that actually
looks like fruit.
Yeah, it's so hard.
What do you do it for?
Irritable bowel syndrome?
He'll know more
when the tests come back.
I still gotta bring him
a stool sample.
Jesus, please.
You were the one who yelled
at me to go to the doctor.
I gotta know every detail?
I could be really sick,
Christopher.
Yeah, my Aunt Josephine
had colon cancer.
Her whole asshole rotted out.
I may have to go into therapy.
Plus, they might
put me on Prozac.
For diarrhea?
To help me cope
and handle stress,
which is a lot
of what causes it.
What do you gotta
be stressed about?
That bar?
War, Christopher.
The Middle East.
You don't listen
to the president?
We're gonna mop the floor
with the whole fuckin' world.
The whole world's
gonna be under our control,
so what are you worked up about?
Oh, give me the Orioles
over the Tigers for two
and the Jays over
the Rangers, three Gs.
I'll just get my day planner.
No, I'm done.
My stupid car.
5,000 miles,
and the alternator's goin'.
What about you?
Mimi said you went
to the doctor.
I've been havin'
trouble with my stomach.
That's why I'm drinkin'
White Russians.
- Wh-what?
You got ulcers already?
It's called IBS.
What's that?
Irritable bowel syndrome.
My mother had that all her life.
See this?
Yeah, I noticed that,
what happened?
- It's cancer.
- What?
Yeah, squamous.
Oh, my God, that's terrible.
Well, they think
they got it all.
Knock wood. Just... cancer.
The things that run
through your head, you know.
Sure.
I got a top guy, though.
Katz.
Hesh recommended him.
Naturally.
So this... disease you got.
What causes it?
I did a Google on it,
and, like, the doctor, too,
they--they all say a lot
of it's psychological.
So on top of everything,
now I'm a head case.
No, come on.
Stop blamin' yourself.
Christopher don't wanna know.
Not that I blame him.
Ah, I gotta take off.
AJ should be comin' home
from his volleyball thing.
Listen, don't say anything
to anybody, okay?
People hear "cancer,"
they start to bury you already.
And you don't tell anybody
what I told you.
All right,
take care of yourself.
Say hi to Anthony.
Yeah.
You're such a good father.
I wish my dad
had been like that.
'Night, dear.
It's a straight shot
on I-95 to Raleigh.
You give this shit to the fence,
I'll meet you in Winston-Salem,
we'll load up the cigs
and come home.
We're pickin' up
so many cigarettes.
Why don't we, instead of two
vans, rent a deuce and a half?
You know, share the drivin'.
Because the cops.
The van's under the radar.
Erik Estrada over here.
Forgot your folic acid.
What is all this stuff?
A beauty parlor chair?
If they even heard of
electrolysis down there.
Where you goin'?
Jesus Christ, go back to bed.
What the fuck's your problem?
My fuckin' tooth is killin' me.
Well, you should
go back to the dentist.
Why do you have to go anyway?
Can't they just
drop this stuff off?
Tony wants me to talk
to the guys down there.
The jerk you were
yellin' at on the phone?
Is it the cigarette thing
you were talkin' about?
Six different kinds of dope
you get to take
for a stomachache.
I got a fuckin' impaction,
I can't take shit
besides oil of clove
'cause I'm sober.
I know, it's hard. I'm sorry.
Have a nice trip.
I love you. Call me.
She's got diarrhea.
Whoops.
You want?
Ah, twist my arm.
I'm expectin' some guys
from New York, so...
No problem.
I got plenty to do out there.
Ah...
- Who's this on?
- Oh, please.
It's called The Lost Boys.
Sil's been raggin'
on me all week
for me to play 'em here.
Their manager or somebody
owes him money.
So, uh, I thought
this was your day off.
Chrissy's away.
I don't like stayin' home alone.
Although at least
I can pour a glass of wine
without him givin' me
"the expression."
Yeah. Yeah, I know that look.
The, uh--the
"constipated owl" look.
You know, when I first met you,
I was scared of you.
Really?
Yeah, but I'm scared
of everybody.
It's always my first reaction.
Well, you're not scared
of me now, are you?
No.
You wanna shoot?
Huh?
Make it interesting,
sawbuck a game.
Mm?
No, it's--it's the round thing,
in the middle there.
How you feelin'? Everything
all right in here now?
- Your stomach all right?
- D-don't--
I know what you're doin'.
Don't distract me.
Oh.
- Ho!
- Hmm.
I've been hustled.
Oops. Did I get your toes?
No. No, no, no, no, no.
I'm so sorry.
Come on, get up.
Come on.
Ah, shit.
All right.
Wait.
Yeah. Go on.
Tony here?
Yeah, come on in.
Hey.
Let me know if you guys
need anything.
What, are you gonna tell me
about the traffic again?
Here, our friend
sent this for you.
Thank you for takin'
the appointment.
And--and I know
I'm on probation,
and--and I deeply regret...
what I did.
My nephew's fiancée.
I know what you're thinkin'.
So?
Well, nothin' happened...
but it could've, very easily.
I mean she really got to me,
this young lady.
She, uh...
What?
This is a very big step.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I mean, that you've come here
to talk about this impulse
instead of just acting on it
without thinking.
No, I always think.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Having sex with
your mistress's cousin,
like the mistress wasn't enough
to piss off your wife.
Tell me about the niece.
She's drop-dead gorgeous.
I mean, someone like her,
I could...
I could do it right this time.
I could start
a whole new family.
I'm young enough.
Fuck 'em all.
And this is something
you're contemplating?
What?
It'd be a disaster.
Of major proportions.
Carmela, I-I-I'd
get hosed financially.
There'd be no reasonin'
with her after that.
And--and my nephew, it--
it would kill him.
After years of groomin' him
to be my number two.
And it'd be very bad
for the girl.
She doesn't deserve that.
I mean, I'm not stupid.
I know part of it's
this father-figure thing
and, you know,
on account a hers ran off.
It would be like committing
an act of symbolic incest.
Whatever.
Look, what am I gonna do?
I-I got lucky the first time
'cause I was able
to control myself.
But you only get one of those.
Rationalizing.
"I can't control myself."
You can.
I don't know.
It's different for women.
It's all about up here
with them.
She could make a play for you.
You might wanna think about
how you're going to establish
limits and boundaries.
For example, you could tell her
she means a great deal to you,
but you think of her
as a daughter.
Even if I wanna
fuck her brains out.
This is a milestone for you.
You're at a very
important crossroads.
For once, you want to avoid
doing something
you know is wrong
and would be destructive,
both to yourself
and to the people
you care about.
That's growth.
That's progress.
Just tell me
what I'm supposed to do.
You have to be honest
with yourself.
I know this is a powerful urge,
but if you can't
keep it in your pants,
you have to stay away from her.
You know...
Not long ago, you stood
in my outer office.
I recall you used the words
"drop-dead gorgeous" about me
and how you had to have me.
I said I wouldn't date you,
and look, you survived.
What a horrible
fuckin' job you have.
How do you do it?
But what happens now
is your choice.
Act, and create a bed of misery,
or you can look at this as
a chance to do something good.
You say she respects you.
Be worthy of respect.
See if you can remain
a--a friend to this woman.
A help to her.
You know,
Tony had ducks one time.
In his pool.
You need to find out
where Chris went.
I'm gettin' this vibe from him.
Who? Tony?
He's really nice,
and he listens.
He's kind of attractive.
Definitely an alpha male.
But what if Christopher
found out?
What?
I'm not gonna fuck him.
Then what are you talking about?
I love Christopher,
and sooner or later,
we're gonna get out
from under all this shit
and leave this fuckin' state.
Jesus Christ.
She's a good-looking woman,
and she wants to fuck
Barney Rubble?
"We really don't know him.
He listens."
Tony, hi.
Hey. How you doin'?
Well, why I'm here--
Patsy's bringin' somebody by.
I'm gonna need
to use the office.
No problem.
I made a resolution.
I gotta start spendin'
a lot more time on the floor.
Crack the whip.
I'm beat, tell you the truth.
I think I'm gonna grab,
uh, 40 winks
till Patsy gets here.
You don't have
Chrissy's cell, do you?
He called, but he didn't
leave a new number.
He'll probably try you again.
He's due back tomorrow.
Oh, excuse me.
- I'll come back.
- No, I'm all right.
Mole back there looked
irregular around the margins.
Every time I see anything now,
I think I got melanoma.
I can imagine.
Hi, it's Adriana
at the Crazy Horse.
Yeah, I need a car, please.
Just tell him to wait outside.
- What? Your car, still?
- Yeah.
They're replacing
the alternator.
You want a belt?
What I could really use
is some...
I wouldn't say no.
Get me motivated
to clean the house
before Christopher gets back.
Except I'm all out.
It's 2:00-- uh, cross-eyed Billy
probably left the Bing already.
I know a guy, Andre.
He's always up.
Well, cancel the car.
I'll give you a ride.
You know who
thinks you're cute...
is Marlene.
She's gotta be over 30,
isn't she?
She's 31.
You know who you
ought to introduce me to
is that friend of yours.
Who?
The one you brought over
to the house that time.
Tall, kind of blondish,
brownish hair.
Danielle from Whippany.
She's dead.
- What?
- Yeah.
She--she dr--
drowned on a picnic.
Oh.
You know, I thought
I picked up on somethin'
between her and me.
I'm not tryin' to be conceited.
Tony!
I've reviewed your chart
and ruled out internal injuries,
so you're free to go.
I'll have the nurse
process your discharge orders.
Whoa, whoa.
This was a very bad accident.
I mean, are you sure
you did all the tests?
I can afford it.
I did the appropriate tests.
I hold a medical degree
from Johns Hopkins.
My grandmother was the first
black woman licensed
to practice medicine
in Delaware.
All right, take it easy.
The young lady that I was with,
uh, they said she was okay.
But could I see her?
Ade.
Hi.
They say you're gonna be fine.
They just wanna keep you here
for observation.
You know, be on the safe side.
I don't even
remember what happened.
There was a raccoon in the road.
I swerved.
How's your car?
Escalade?
It's totaled.
Probably saved our life.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
They're gonna let me go.
I wanna go too.
Chrissy's comin' home today.
We should probably
talk about that.
Oh...
Yeah.
Right.
Dude, how you doin'?
I hit the fuckin' mother lode.
20 Gs of product a week.
Little Paulie's behind me
with the other half.
Fuck me.
Now, 20% of this load,
they can stamp the packs
for the vendin' machines.
The rest, the cartons can
go straight to the bodegas,
let them worry about the stamps.
I'm beat.
I'm gonna hit the fuckin' rack,
have Ade cook me up
a nice carbonara.
What's the matter?
Don't know how to tell you,
but Adriana's in the hospital.
She was in an accident.
What? When?
Last night around 2:00.
Jesus Christ, what happened?
Is she all right?
She got banged up,
but she's gonna be okay.
The drinkin' and drivin'.
I told her! Jeez.
Where is she?
- Mount Mercy in Dover.
- Dover?
Apparently, they swerved
to avoid a deer in the road.
"They"?
Her and Tony.
Tony? Soprano?
Uh-huh.
I-is he all right?
Not a scratch.
The fuckin' luck on this guy.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dover.
Right, she's got an aunt
she's close to out there
who's been sick.
She's, uh--she's friends
with Tony's aunt.
All right, somebody
take me to get my car.
I better get over there.
Fabio, put it up!
I thought I'd die in there
without a cigarette.
What, so you're
just not gonna talk?
I almost got killed,
Christopher.
I'm just curious.
What the fuck were you doin'
in the middle of the night,
in the middle of nowhere,
in a car with my uncle?
He was drivin' me home.
- Fuckin' Dover?
- We were talkin'.
W-we were goin' to get
somethin' to eat.
I get off of work,
I don't wanna go right home.
You weren't even there.
No, I was in a fuckin'
Ride-A-Rent,
bustin' my ass
with a bunch of rednecks,
makin' a livin'
to buy you alcohol and coke
and all the other shit
you shovel into your mouth!
2:00 in the fuckin' mornin'?
Don't fuckin' lie to me!
I can't stand it!
Nothin' was goin' on,
Christopher!
I should've made you walk home.
I swear to God.
You know how this looks?
Don't talk to me!
You shut your mouth!
You wanted to see me?
Adriana okay?
She's fine.
People who don't clean up
after their pets...
Pop this in that basket
for me, will you?
It was blind luck,
that accident.
Cop told me he thought
he was comin' up
on a fatality
when he saw the car.
I'd be thinkin'
the same thing if I were you,
but it's not true.
I don't know
what you're talkin' about.
Her car was in the shop.
I was drivin' her
home from work.
That's all.
We were lookin' to get a burger.
- In Dover.
- What difference does it make?
You don't seem to give a shit
she almost died.
She could've been paralyzed
or--or--or scarred up.
And you got a puss on?
What were you doin' out there
alone in a car with my fiancée?
We were talkin' about you,
you selfish prick,
and how you're the best thing
that ever happened to her.
Oh you don't think
this fuckin' devastates me?
Well, frankly, you scored
so far over your head
when you got her,
what do you expect?
The fuck are you talkin' about?
She's a knockout. A ten.
And look at you.
You're average, at best.
So you better reconcile
yourself with that,
or you're gonna be fuckin'
paranoid your whole life.
Oh, so this
is my fuckin' fault now?
Nothin' happened,
and I'm not gonna say it again.
And you should've married
that girl two years ago.
Everybody knows
you've been the biggest
fuckin' cooze hound around
the past four or five years.
Your mid-life crisis.
You'd fuck a catcher's mitt.
On everything I hold sacred,
on my children,
there's nothin' goin' on
between me and Adriana.
Tony walked away
without a scratch,
but Adriana suffered
a severe blow to the head.
Adriana got caught givin'
the big guy a blow job.
And when the paramedics
found them,
she had his cock
still in her mouth.
Well, a statistic shows that
most single-car fatalities
are the result of guys
popping their load
behind the wheel.
Apparently, he came
all over the sun visor.
Sanseverino.
Guess who went down
on Tony Soprano.
That's the truth. It's fact.
If it was my old lady,
the next thing she'd suck
is a tailpipe.
- That pretty little trim
can suck this pipe
anytime she wants.
Like you'd ever have a shot.
Hey, let me tell you somethin'.
When Christopher was in rehab,
she was callin' me all the time.
I was this close.
Then you got a problem,
'cause your braciole's
isn't even that long.
- What's so funny?
- Nothin'.
Didn't sound like nothin'.
I wanna hear the big joke.
- Take it easy.
We're just shootin' the shit.
We were just talkin'
about my braciole.
Oh, yeah, what about it?
So, deal you in, huh?
I asked him a fuckin' question.
What are you breakin'
my balls for?
I want a fuckin' answer.
What's so fuckin' hilarious,
you fuckin' parade float?
Ho!
I'm a fuckin' captain now.
You don't talk to me like that!
Oh, come on, guys.
Don't put your hands on me!
Chrissy, for Chrissakes...
Fuck all of youse.
- Oh whoa, whoa!
- Hey!
Motherfucker!
- Hold it.
- Easy.
Vinar, Jimmy, please join me.
So talk to me, guys.
How are we feeling in these?
Hey, hon. I already ate.
There's a casserole in the mic--
You fuckin' lyin' bitch!
Ow! Stop it!
What are you doing?
You were suckin' his cock!
Georgie told me everything!
The surgeon
on the operating table
said you were moanin'
Tony's name!
What are you talking about?
Fuckin' lie to me!
What were you doin'
in Dover, then?
See?
See? You can't tell me,
'cause I know
what you were doin'!
Your other dope dealer's there.
I remembered. Go ahead, deny it!
Okay!
I was goin' out to see Andre,
but I wasn't suckin'
anybody's cock!
How could you say that?
Oh, so you two
were just gonna go
toot up a bunch of lines,
go fuckin' bird-watchin'?
Oh, you son of a bitch.
I was gonna stay up all night
and clean this fuckin' shithole!
Everybody knows about it!
Everybody's talkin' about it!
No, please!
You want me to use, you bitch!
You're fuckin' killin' me!
No, I don't! I love you!
Stop it.
- You motherfucker!
- Fuckin' whore.
Ow!
Ow! My neck!
Get the fuck outta here!
I never wanna see you again!
I thought you had
an algebra test.
Oh, chill out.
What did you say?
L-look, I studied
for 45 minutes straight.
Don't I get a break?
Hey.
What's up?
A.J., how's it goin'?
Hey, Uncle Tony.
Did I come at a bad time?
I need to talk to you.
AJ, go upstairs.
Study.
Well, what about the pizza?
Now.
Study.
All right, what's up?
I went to the Belleville
Tavern after work,
and Larry down there said
our little cousin was
in there all fucked up.
Somebody told him what
was goin' on in the car.
Was nothin' goin' on in the car.
No, of course not,
but he thinks there was,
so he started drinkin' again,
and he beat up Adriana,
and he threw her out
of the fuckin' house.
Where's his fuckin'
self-control, this guy?
Little Paulie's out there
lookin' for him
to reign him in,
but he was sayin' some
crazy things about you.
Oh, this goddamn kid.
Christopher's not right
in the head, Ton'.
I mean, who the fuck knows
what he's capable of?
Well, he knows where to find me.
You see him, you tell him that.
Gotta use your john.
Get you a day early, huh?
I'll go to the store
in the morning.
Look, relax, all right?
Go whenever you want.
What the hell is wrong with him?
What do you want, Tony?
He couldn't
bring this in himself?
What, I can't even
come in and say hello?
What you want
is to know if I heard
the disgusting shit
they're saying.
At least have the guts
to come out and ask me.
It isn't true.
You know what? Fuck you!
Fuck me? Fuck you!
You gotta put your son in hiding
because of your
fucking philandering?
Afraid he'll get
caught in the crossfire?
Your own son?
Christopher's upset, that's all.
He could come over.
He could say some things
that a kid shouldn't hear.
Just please leave.
I don't even wanna look at you.
Motherfucker!
Motherfucking gun!
Give me two.
This kid ain't gonna show up, T.
He's probably in some gutter.
Yeah, hopefully
he's wore himself down.
Where are you, you fuck?
He's got a gun!
I know you're up there,
you motherfucker!
Why don't you come out--
You know what to do down there!
Fuckin' lucky!
You're fuckin' lucky
I ran outta loads!
Shut up, you little cock,
or I'll split
your fuckin' wishbone.
It's all over.
Everybody... enjoy the evening.
Unhappy customer.
Let me the fuck go!
I'll kill all of youse!
Fuckin' kill all of youse!
Ahh...
You draw down on the boss
of a fuckin' family?
Huh?
You lied to me!
You were scorin' coke with her!
- She admitted it!
- So what?
I can't relieve stress
every once in a while?
I don't got enough
fuckin' problems?
You sent me to North Carolina
so you could fuck my girlfriend!
What kind of fuckin' animal
you think I am, huh?
The thought never
even entered my head!
You're a man, you're alone
in a car with her--
You fuckin' pushed me to this.
You pushed me to this!
Way I see it, Tony,
he must've known
the gun was empty.
Look what he pumped
into your car.
What are you tryin'
to say, Paulie?
The fuck you tryin'
to say, Paulie, huh?
Either you tell me right now
that you can take it
into your heart
that I did not do this shit...
Or this is as far as we go.
Motherfucker.
Tony, come on!
Listen to somebody else
for a change.
Fuck him.
Tony, try it my way.
Listen to me.
Mr., uh, Sorriano,
what seems to be the matter?
Soprano. I'm fine.
It's my friend, here,
needs to talk to you.
Well, you know where
ER admitting is, right?
Look, uh, you got someplace
maybe we could talk?
It's 3:00 a.m.,
and I just finished
a 17-hour rotation.
Any gunshot wounds
or broken kneecaps?
Two minutes.
You're an excellent doctor.
That's why I brought him here.
Come on.
This gentleman here
is the fiancé
of the young lady
that I was with.
Now, he's got it into his head
that there was oral sex goin' on
at the time of the wreck.
- Listen, I--
- Hey, hey, hey!
Just a second.
Now, naturally, he's very upset,
so I need you to tell him
there wasn't.
He's obviously
feelin' the pressure.
He's just gonna fuckin' lie.
I'm not in the custom
of lying about anything,
but whether somebody was
getting something in the car,
how could I possibly
attest to that?
Well, as the attending,
you could explain
how medically,
it's not possible.
- Excuse me?
- Well for instance,
if she was wearing a seatbelt,
then there would have been
abrasions to the lateral
anterior aspect
of the clavicle, wouldn't there?
Or the right mid-sternum?
Are you a physician?
No, I'm a pre-board certified
massage therapist.
So did she have any
of those kind of things?
Actually, yes,
on the right clavicle
and the sternum
just above the xiphoid
process, which...
would indicate
an upright position
at the moment of impact.
So what he's sayin'
is that she was sittin' up.
All right.
Thank you, doctor. Come on.
For the kids,
the Make-A-Wish Foundation.
Whatever, here.
Thank you!
What do you want from me?
I guess I believe you.
You threw food at Vito.
That's gotta be resolved.
He was fuckin' laughin',
which was wrong.
But at this point, now
it don't make no difference.
Even if it wasn't true,
it's what people think.
They know you were out there
scorin' coke with her.
What do you care
what people think?
You know the truth.
I gotta live in the world.
And now I look like Joe Jerkoff.
No-no-no-no.
You know what?
I might as well have fucked her.
Thanks.
Hello?
I rang the doorbell six times.
Nobody answered.
What are you doing here?
I wanna talk to you.
If you came to pick him up,
he's not going.
Oh, so you believe all that
shit they're sayin', huh?
Am I that horrible?
Really?
Where there's smoke,
there's fire.
I don't know what you did.
What's gonna happen when
your children hear about this?
Meadow already suspects you.
Suspects what?
She saw you at the club.
She said she thought
you were coked out.
What are you talkin' about?
I don't do drugs.
She knows about the accident.
What do you think
she's gonna think?
And with Anthony at that age?
Oh, come on, the kids!
The kids-- this is about you!
Fine, so it's all about me!
What, do I mean nothing to you?
That I gotta live with
this swirlin' around me?
All right, look, forget
about what they're sayin'.
I-I'm asking you.
You think I'd have
sexual relations with her?
Adriana, who's gonna
be a member of this family?
Now, I want you
to answer me truthfully.
Look, I-I know I haven't been
a fuckin' saint, all right,
and you got plenty of issues
of your own on that subject...
but you haven't exactly
been a fuckin' saint yourself.
No, no-no-no-no. Come here.
You think I would go near
that girl like that?
Thank you.
Look, I'm askin' you
to pull with me
to put a good face
on this thing,
for the sake of the kids
and their--and this family.
I gotta bail you out?
It is never-ending,
your bullshit.
Use a fuckin' crosswalk!
Jesus Christ.
Don't get all excited.
Most of it's from the accident.
You okay?
What do you fuckin' think?
Kicked out of my house,
I may have ulcerative colitis,
and you call me up.
We'd like your permission
to put a listening device
in your business.
This relationship with Tony
could net us a lot of chatter.
Don't forget
it's him we're after.
There is no relationship!
The faster we get Tony
and put him away,
the sooner you can
get on with your life.
We can get a court order
to install a device anyway,
but this'll make
our lives simpler.
Fuck you.
I do enough for you people.
You're not buggin' my club.
Adriana, it's a syndrome,
protecting abusers.
If it would've been
Christopher alone
in a car with a woman,
I would've killed him.
Arthur's sending something
over, with his compliments.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
I'm gonna go over there.
Nice to see you, Ton.
Oh, thank you.
- Gravy's good tonight.
- Oh?
Nice to see you.
Hope you have
a pleasant evening.
Ladies.