♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon In your eyes ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one In a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
Don't tell me we're
fighting all the time.
I try to get along.
You can't just say whatever
comes to mind, Tony.
You were fucking horrible.
That shit about the roadies.
You hit below the belt
yourself, Jan,
not to mention you started it.
No cheese for Sophia.
Those kids seem to like you,
sort of.
I leave them completely free
to do whatever they want.
How else are they gonna learn
from their mistakes?
Anyway, thank you
for having us over.
What's this you're watching?
Beethoven.
- Can we get a dog?
- Please?
I'll walk him, and I'll
pick up the poo and pee.
Pee? Right.
Start with your underwear.
We had a dog.
Remember? Tippy?
He got worms, though.
Had to move to the country.
Tippy was gassed, Tony.
Daddy took him to the pound.
He used to drag his ass on
the carpet just to scratch himself.
My mother went crazy.
Gassed?
And he's so cynical
about everything else.
Father told me
he took him to live on a farm.
That's what they always say.
That same farm must have
17 billion dogs on it.
Dog shit up to the rafters.
Hello?
What?
Oh, no, that's terrible.
What? What's the matter?
It's Cousin Josephine.
- Aunt Concett' died.
- What happened?
They think it was
a heart attack.
Uncle Zio found her on the
couch after Meet the Press.
We hereby
commend Concetta to the Lord,
embraced in His divine goodness.
Let us go in peace.
Amen. Amen.
Listen, as long as we're here,
I was gonna go visit my father,
if you'd like to join me.
Five hours, they let me out
for these funerals.
I gotta spend it being maudlin?
It's a beautiful day.
Excuse me, I thought you might
wanna go pay your respects
to your brother.
By crying to a chunk of marble?
I can pay my respects
from the after-party.
After-party?
It's those uptake inhibitors.
We were skeptical at first,
then his mood really improved.
His memory too.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Hi.
Oh, hello.
You knew my mother?
You're Anthony.
Oh, my God.
Do I know you?
Oh, no.
No, no, you're not annoying me.
No, no...
Do we know each other?
Oh, we met once.
I was a friend of your father's.
Oh.
You're the lady
from Bamberger's.
From the fur department.
Fran Felstein.
Tony.
How you doing?
So, what, you...
you come visit?
I miss your father sometimes.
It's...
It's foolish.
No, don't say that.
No, I was sorry to hear
about your mother.
At least she didn't suffer.
She made all of us
suffer instead.
Oh, it was a joke.
She made all of us suffer.
Believe me, I heard
the stories from your dad.
Yeah.
You'll have to forgive me.
My hearing the last few years...
Well, how about a hearing aid?
They got the little ones now.
You can't even see them.
I'm too vain. Anyway...
Johnny was very proud of you.
You were very special to him.
I'm sure you were too.
You know, Johnny told me
if I ever needed anything,
I should always call his son.
What do you need?
Not a thing.
Fran Felstein?
That was class.
Got great legs for an old broad.
I was in love with that woman.
She was the reason
I never married.
I wanted to propose.
I had the ring all picked out.
So what? She turned you down?
I hesitated. How could I bring
this life we live on a woman?
Anyway, she took it as a sign
I wasn't interested.
And then one night
we were all at the 500 Club
to see Enzo Stuarti.
Your father shows up.
Sy Devore suit, two-inch lapel.
That was that.
She never knew my feelings.
What could I do?
For years,
I suffered in silence.
Mario, did you bring
your guitar?
Not to this.
♪ Volare, oh-oh ♪
Angie, come on. Sing us a song.
You sing, Junior.
Nobody wants to hear me.
Mario, remember?
Thank you.
Thanks, my name's JT.
I'm an alcoholic and an addict.
Hi, JT.
I'm also a TV writer which,
by default,
makes me a douchebag, but...
you would've figured that
out for yourselves in a minute.
Uh...
About 15 years ago, I moved
from Jersey to Hollywood,
broke into the biz.
It was a dream come true.
I was making money.
I had the Beemer,
the actress girlfriend.
Best of all, I had all
the flake I needed
to keep me churning out
that snappy dialogue
for Corbin Bernsen.
Drugs, alcohol.
That shit practically comes
with the Writers Guild card.
Anyway, before too long,
I discovered heroin.
Then things really
started to fall apart.
It got so bad that I blew
a deadline on a Nash Bridges.
I got my ass fired.
I didn't work for 18 months.
By the grace of God,
I got myself into a rehab
program in Pennsylvania,
and with the help
of some good friends
that I made there,
I got through it.
Chris, where are you?
There's my man Chris, everybody.
Anyway, I wanna
talk a little bit
about taking a moral inventory.
So we talked for, like, an hour.
Well, it turns out
that they had a thing,
her and my old man.
Right up till he died.
He got from this woman
what he couldn't get at home.
Support.
You know, love.
A smile when you walk
in the fucking door.
Do you think that justifies
his infidelity?
She drove him into
that woman's arms, my mother.
To all his women.
I'll tell you one thing.
Over the years he was rotting
in that grave,
I can't remember once
my mother going to visit him.
But this lady, Fran...
It's possible your mother
found it very painful.
Oh, poor her.
What was it like
sitting there with Fran?
It was a little weird at first,
you know...
Here I am comforting
my father's mistress.
My mother's lying there, dead.
Are you attracted to her?
Come on, she's old enough
to be my mother!
Oh, Jesus Christ,
it's an expression.
Don't cream yourself.
I did not want
to fuck my mother.
You should've seen her in her
housedress, with that hairnet.
This conversation'd be over
in two seconds.
So, I figured,
why not move back to Jersey?
Clean slate. It's better.
My new agent,
next week he's got me
set up to meet Dick Wolf's guy.
I seen Dick Wolf
at Rao's one night.
Guy's got his own limo.
That Law & Order money?
The guy could have
his own battleship.
But enough of my shit.
How are you doing?
Good, you know.
Working the program.
Oh, yeah?
I had some fucking wine,
all right?
Is that what you wanna hear?
Christopher, when was this?
I don't know.
My fiancée was in a car crash.
I didn't even like it.
I went to a meeting
the next day.
But no slip since then?
I've been sober,
and I've been high.
Sober's better.
You know you can call me
anytime, right?
What, do you got a date?
I got to meet somebody,
a friend.
Go ahead, I'll get this.
Thanks, bro.
Listen, call me. I'm serious.
Harold Melvoin.
Mel, it's me.
Corrado, what's up?
There's a funeral
I need to attend.
I want you to call the feds.
Vincent Patronella.
Is he a relative?
You know the rules.
He's my niece's godfather.
I think I met him at a barbecue
once for the bicentennial.
All they can say is no.
Your father used to bring me
flowers all the time.
- Flowers and lingerie.
- Oh.
I'm making chicken.
Cuban-style with black beans.
Oh.
What's this?
Ketchup? Sure. If you want.
No, the kid and the dog.
Oh! My son, Bruce.
He married an Israeli girl.
He's a food service director
with El Al.
No, no, no, the dog.
Oh, Freckles?
He was a gift from your dad.
What?
Oh, when?
Oh, this is my fucking dog!
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
This was my dog.
His name was Tippy.
Your dad never said.
I don't fucking believe this.
My mother made him
give the dog away.
Well, Bruce loved him.
He had him for almost ten years,
till he moved to Tel Aviv.
Then I had to put him to sleep.
Those are the pictures,
on the coffee table.
The slippers were your dad's,
too.
Look at this.
The two of you.
He used to remind me
of Victor Mature.
Thanks.
Oh.
Outside the Latin Quarter.
Holy shit, look at Hesh.
George Gershwin.
He was a whoremaster, and cheap.
You know, he screwed me
out of my retirement money.
Against your dad's wishes,
by the way.
What are you talking about?
Don't get me started.
No, come on, what happened?
Your dad owned a racetrack.
With the midget auto racing.
Yeah, the Chickamauga Raceway
over in New Egypt.
Him, Herman, some other guy.
Phil something.
With the hair, from New York.
Yeah, Leotardo.
My father cut him in
to pay off a poker debt.
Johnny always told me
his piece would go to me.
Couldn't put me in his will,
obviously.
When he passed, your dad,
I called Hesh.
He sent me 500 bucks.
That's it?
I'm sorry.
No.
Jesus Christ,
I wish you'd called me.
Bruce sends me money
occasionally.
Well, that's not the point.
It's my father's wishes.
Look, forget it.
Seriously, I'm sorry. I...
I shouldn't have even
brought it up.
Listen, after we eat,
you wanna take a ride?
So I saw my Uncle Jun.
He says to say hello.
Junior?
Jesus.
How's he doing?
I don't know if you know it,
but he was always
a little hot for you.
He was practically a stalker.
He said he suffered in silence.
Suffered in silence?
He used to skulk outside
my building, all hours.
Weird phone calls.
I always had a hunch
he told Livia
about me and Johnny.
Jesus Christ.
She was a handsome woman,
your mother.
Not sexy, exactly,
but statuesque.
Little nip?
What is it?
It's one for the road, honey.
And this looks like road to me.
Rémy Martin, VSOP.
Mm.
Whoa.
They can't be making much,
but if I know Hesh,
him and Phil got something
going on out of here.
So tell me about your women.
Your wife, what's she like?
I don't know.
What's to tell?
Good woman, good mother.
Marriage hit the rocks,
that's all.
What are you gonna do?
How about your girlfriend?
She's an art dealer.
Very sophisticated.
Dark hair, dark eyes.
She's Latin.
You know, from Spain.
That's it.
Oh, man, I am so glad
you called.
I really needed this.
So?
So, what?
What, there's nothing
you wanna talk about?
I was honest with you
the other night.
What, you're telling me
you're not using?
What?
You ran out of IHOP
like you were on fire.
You were jonesing
like a motherfucker.
I was meeting a girl.
We were going to the track.
The Meadowlands.
I didn't wanna miss
the last race.
I am totally clean and sober.
Jesus Christ.
I was positive
you fucking slipped.
Thank you, man.
I appreciate your concern.
I could have saved you a trip.
I'll take your action.
You take a dime each
on the Yankees and St. Louis?
Whoa, high roller.
Just got a three-grand residual
on a That's Life episode.
What, that fake guinea-fest
with Paul Sorvino?
That was totally unrealistic.
So dusty here.
Yeah.
That silk?
It ain't Kleenex.
It's linen.
You know, you're very...
I don't know,
you got a lot of class.
Just like your girlfriend.
He told me to look out for her,
so I sent her some money,
which is a helluva lot more
than anybody else did.
Then all these years, you decide
to keep his end for yourself?
Oh, I should give it
to some trollop, huh?
Besides, I thought
I had it coming.
With Phil Leotardo
in the can for 20 years,
who do you think's been
running that place, huh?
Collecting the rent,
filing the taxes,
all that bullshit?
What about my share?
All those years,
I never saw a dime.
You're my father's friend, Hesh.
My friend!
Oh, I'm such a good friend,
how come I never see you?
What? I see you.
I'm fucking busy.
Never too busy to call me at 2:00
a.m. to hear your problems, though.
One time, that happened.
My therapist was on vacation.
Listen, you want his end,
kid, you got it.
It's 25%.
The closing is not
for two weeks,
and I would appreciate it
if you called Phil Leotardo
and tell him that he should
assume part of that burden.
Well, despite how you feel,
my father loved this woman.
She's not such a bad person.
But I don't know.
Something about her always
rubbed me the wrong way.
Maybe because she was
rubbing him and not you.
How long you know me, bub, huh?
She's a little pale
for my taste.
Mr. Patronella was last week.
This is a different one.
Yes, I'm aware he's been
to two funerals in a month.
Well, people die, Counselor.
The deceased in question now,
Mrs. Crilley,
was the sister
of Mr. Soprano's cousin.
By marriage.
So she's not
a blood relative per se.
Are we quibbling now?
For God's sake,
the man wants to pay
his respects.
Well, perhaps my next call
should be to Judge Runions.
Get him involved.
Five hours.
It's not a Hawaiian vacation.
He'll attend the church service,
then pay his respects
to the family afterwards.
Thank you, Counselor.
We appreciate it.
You're worth every fucking cent.
They're gonna have Scottish
bagpipes at the funeral.
It should be interesting.
Don Provolone.
See that fucking game?
Diet Coke and whatever
he's having.
Ginger ale?
Remind me to send Jeter
a dozen roses.
You wanna parlay it?
I was thinking I'd go check out
that Indian casino,
play some poker.
You want in a real game,
I'll hook you up.
High stakes,
exclusive clientele.
- David Lee Roth.
- I'll tell you, man,
playing cards, games of chance,
I never really dug it before.
I was never that good at math.
But there's something about
that excitement that's so...
I don't know.
What is wrong? I win one bet,
you look like you're gonna cry.
I fucked up again.
My super came by this morning
to fucking caulk
around the toilet.
He had some weed.
You have got to call someone
before you use, not after.
I know, I know.
I just wanted to see if I could
get high like a normal person.
You're not normal.
Neither of us are.
And on top of that,
you ask me to meet you at a bar?
Come here, you maniac.
625K for the track
plus all that land?
That's it?
Problem's the zoning
restrictions.
We're lucky we got
a buyer at all.
Here's what I propose.
Tony gets 150.
25% comes from you,
the other 75% of that
comes from Hesh.
Jesus Christ,
that's like 40 grand.
You gotta be fucking
kidding me, John.
Am I smiling?
You got some balls, kid,
I'll give you that much.
You'll give me
what I tell you to give me.
- Whoa, Tony, come on.
- Take it easy.
- Fuck that!
This ain't the '70s.
And I'm not a kid.
Relax, it's an expression.
Well, here's another expression.
You got five days
to give me my money.
Come on.
That was out of line.
Philly, he's a boss.
Jersey?
Come on, huh?
Well, I talked to Phil and Hesh
about the racetrack.
How bad did they bullshit you?
Well, actually,
we straightened it all out.
So when the sale goes through,
you're looking at a nice
piece of change.
- You're kidding?
- No.
Hey, that's wonderful.
I wanted to show you something.
You were admiring
my handkerchief.
Check out the initials.
JFK? Holy shit!
This was his?
You know, I have a hat of his.
A captain's hat
I bought at an auction.
A lot of the friends
don't like him.
You know,
Ruby and all that shit.
But, fuck,
I was in grammar school.
That's my lipstick.
We had a little thing.
When he was president?
March '61.
Right before the Bay of Pigs.
I was at the Copa
with a girlfriend.
I'm wearing a new sable,
and we meet Lem Billings.
Now, Lem is a school friend
of Jack's from Choate,
but of course we had no idea.
He insists that we join him
for some affair
at the Pierre Hotel.
He won't take no.
He has a limo, we figure,
"What the hell?"
You know, so...
We go over, and he tells us
he's taking us
to the presidential suite.
So we get up,
out of the elevator.
We go in the suite.
It is crawling with models,
celebrities.
Peter Lawford, Sinatra.
Jackie Gleason.
- No shit.
- Yeah.
I'm looking around.
And I glance across the room,
and suddenly, I am locking eyes
with John Fitzgerald Kennedy.
Yeah, I mean, he comes over.
He is a perfect gentleman.
He takes my coat,
he brings me a cocktail,
introduces me around.
And finally, at the end
of the night-- now, get this--
"In the interests of
national security," he says,
he needs me to stay.
Since I'm wearing a sable,
he needs to personally
interview me,
make sure I'm not working
for the Russians.
He said that?
Some line, huh?
What was he like?
- Wonderful.
- So were you two an item?
No. He called.
But after all,
this man was the leader
of the free world.
I mean, you know...
I remember one weekend,
I was supposed to go
down to D.C.,
stay at the Ritz-Carlton.
Last minute, emergency meeting.
Steel workers
are going on strike.
So, what, it was just
that one time, or...?
Except for, you know,
after the Bay of Pigs,
he was probably pretty busy.
Yeah, I knew there were others.
Judy Campbell.
And Marilyn, of course.
We had something special,
though.
Crazy passion.
That was something
your mother never understood.
When you're married
to a powerful man,
you damn well better
make him feel powerful.
My mother?
Please.
I saw a picture of Livia
on New Year's Eve.
She was dressed like a refugee.
Listen, I think I'm going
to skip the coffee.
I got a meeting in the city.
Are you-- you sure?
Look...
consider this an advance.
Get your phone turned on
and pay your rent.
Your dad would be so proud.
He raised a real gentleman.
You trying to buy this pot?
800 and you'll know.
What the fuck.
Cowboys and three
little Indians.
Fuck me!
I got a lot of big people
coming next week.
So when you write on TV,
what do they have, like,
one guy writes the words
for Dylan McDermott
and one guy writes
for Nicholson's girlfriend?
That the way it is?
You write it all yourself.
Oh, interesting.
So how you doing?
You wanna take off?
I'm getting killed here.
I'm gonna go. I'm fucking shot.
I'll call you tomorrow.
You wanna work out?
Sure, yeah, whatever.
Four of clubs to Joe Hollywood,
jack for the car-wash king.
Ten for Mr. Vito.
Show Valentina you love her!
They were out of the Citrucel.
Where you goin'?
Gotta order some flowers.
Sal from the dry cleaner's,
his kid died.
Drowned in a Jacuzzi.
Seven years old, you believe it?
Fuckin' tragedy.
Harold Melvoin.
It's me.
I got another funeral. A kid.
His father does my shirts.
Corrado, it has
to be a relative.
It is a relative, goddamn it.
My old man came over with this
kid's great-great-grandfather.
The guy had a club foot.
That's rather tenuous,
don't you think?
The whole fuckin' village
of Avellino
settled in this area.
We gotta be related
somewhere down the line.
- Corrado...
- Corrado, my balls!
I gotta get out of this house.
I'm going fucking stir-crazy.
Seventh Street coming out.
Holy shit.
You're still here?
Called you all day yesterday.
We're in a hand here.
What do you wanna do?
Fold.
Here, fuck it.
I'm all in.
Call.
Pair of tens.
Flush.
Caught it on the river.
Motherfucking...
fuck!
How bad?
He owes the house 57.
Thousand?
What are you, fuckin' crazy?
Define crazy.
I'm good for it.
I'm up for this Dick Wolf thing.
If I get on staff,
it's like a month's salary.
Well, how about
this fuckin' month?
Hey, you think you could
spot me for a while?
I-I got some child support too.
I'll cover this.
I'll give you three grand
for incidentals.
That's 60,000 altogether.
I've only been up two days.
I can still add.
Good. Then add two points
every week
till I'm paid in fucking full.
You're charging me vig?
On top of the principal.
It's compounded if you're late.
That's 1,200
one week from today.
Don't give me that look.
This is your problem.
I will not fucking enable you.
♪ Shareef don't like it ♪
♪ Rock the Casbah,
Rock the Casbah ♪
There he is! Philly!
Phil.
Phil, where are you going?
Hey, Tony, I gotta meet John
down the restaurant.
You fuckin' cocksucker!
♪ ...Was out of their hair ♪
♪ Rock the Casbah,
Rock the Casbah ♪
Where you gonna go, huh?
Where you gonna go?
You motherfucker!
Jesus Christ.
Mister, you okay in there?
Oh, my neck!
- Oh! Oh!
- You all right?
You run from me,
you fucking cocksucker?
Where's my fuckin' money?
I'll get it. I'll get it.
My neck, Tony.
What do you think,
I'm an asshole? Huh?
No, no, no. No, Tony.
- I can't hear you.
- No, no. Please, Tony.
You got 24 hours.
Called 911.
They're on their way.
He's all right.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my baby.
Take her upstairs, Andy.
My baby...
She should probably take
one of those tranquillizers
her mother gave her.
We should go, Junior.
Relax, we just got here.
Chicken's nice and spicy, huh?
I know you're in there.
You're casting a shadow
over the peephole.
Hey.
What, are you ducking me?
No, what are you...?
I thought you were this girl.
She's a pain in the ass.
So, what the fuck?
Where you been?
Working, man.
I got those TV pitch meetings.
I was gonna call you.
Yeah, so why didn't you?
All right, look.
You want the truth?
I was away. I went to AC.
- Where's my money?
- I don't have it yet.
But you went to AC.
I have a meeting next week
with René Balcer.
Dick Wolf's right-hand guy.
He likes my stuff.
He told my agent.
I'm gonna be on staff.
I got out of that business
'cause people fuck you over.
Jon Favreau?
Faggot cocksucker
tried to steal my ideas.
Bro, listen,
I swear on all that's holy,
I'll have your money next week.
That wasn't the deal!
I'll be back tomorrow.
Don't make me a jerkoff.
Damn, I'm happy.
Get a load of these.
My new kicks.
Bottega Veneta,
marked down to only 600.
Thought you were paying
your phone bill.
Oh, I should've, I know.
But it's been so long since
I've been able to treat myself.
Oh, thanks.
So, turns out my Uncle Zio's
going downhill.
The day we met,
I told you we were there
at the cemetery to bury
his wife, my Aunt Concetta.
Seventy years,
they were together.
Poor guy's taking it very hard.
Oh!
My knight in shining armor.
So?
Yeah, good morning to you too.
- You got it?
- Jesus.
You are a fuckin' trip.
I'm J.T., by the way.
What is this, fuckin'
Pulp Fiction?
Am I supposed to be afraid?
I don't know. I didn't see it.
You're really being
a prick, huh?
I told you, I need more time.
I don't have the money.
Then fucking get it.
Chris, you know me.
What could you possibly do to me
that I haven't already
been through?
I'm positive
we'll think of something.
Ah! Oh, my God!
And 66 years
after taking those sacred vows,
"till death do us part,"
Concetta left him
and went home to God.
In the two weeks that followed,
Nicolo struggled without her,
finally succumbing
to irredeemable loss.
The enormity of his grief
can hardly be imagined.
How much they went
through together.
Seeing their children grow,
and looking joyfully on
as their grandchildren
had children.
Sickness and health.
Good times and bad.
But through it all,
one thing remained constant.
They had each other.
It was Nicolo's love
for Concetta
that made him leave this earth
a mere 15 days
after she left him.
We take comfort knowing
they're together again,
seated at the foot of our Lord.
Let us join together in prayer.
- Hail, Mary...
- ...full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women,
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour
of our death, amen.
Junior, what's the matter?
Oh, this fucking shit!
What's the point?
Shh, Uncle Junior.
I can't take it anymore!
Okay. You need
to lower your voice.
Come on.
...and forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
It's a fucking Emmy.
It's gold-plated.
Then melt it down, man.
Look, I told you, $15.
Oh, fuck, man, come on!
This is, like, huge, this shit.
If you had an Oscar,
maybe I could give you
a little something.
An Academy Award.
But TV?
- What else you got?
- I don't know.
I got a laptop in my car.
Yeah, okay, cool.
I'll check that out.
From your friend.
All 1,200.
He give you a hard time?
Hardest thing
was keeping him awake.
He's hitting the vein.
Nodding out.
Son of a fuckin' bitch.
Cheers.
Mm.
I'm grilling us
some filet mignon.
And you, take a load off.
Here, this is the money from
the closing of the racetrack.
It's 150 grand.
That's great.
How's your pal Hesh?
Good.
I remember once,
your dad and I
drove down the shore.
Hesh had rented a place
at Point Pleasant.
It was right before Labor Day.
Actually, it was a couple
of months before he died.
We stopped at a liquor store.
He had to pee,
I needed some cigarettes.
And anyway, the man behind
the counter was blind.
Your dad looks at him...
Whoa, wait a minute.
This is after my dad got sick?
Yeah.
My dad caught emphysema,
and you kept smoking?
He didn't mind.
He could barely breathe.
We had the oxygen tent
set up right in the house.
I mean, Jesus Christ,
even my mother quit.
I offered to stop. I mean...
And he didn't want me to.
He was fine with it, really.
All right, whatever.
Finish your story.
It was dumb.
Your dad got the guy
to give us some champagne.
Water chestnuts
wrapped in bacon.
And dip them in the duck sauce.
All right.
Mm. Delicious.
So, what's in the bag?
Oh.
Yeah, I wanted to show you this, uh...
It's the hat I told you about.
JFK's.
Oh, my goodness.
Look at this.
- May I?
- Yeah.
Oh.
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ Mr. President ♪
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ To ♪
♪ You ♪
I met with the Dick Wolf guy.
They hired some kid from Yale.
Plus, now the money I owe you,
my ex-fucking-wife...
How many times have you shot up?
Five, six.
I thought I had it
under control.
I lost it.
You stupid fuck.
You were doing so good.
Now you fucked it all up.
Where do you get the right?
We're in the program.
You're gonna use, why
didn't you call your sponsor?
I couldn't get him.
So why the fuck
didn't you call me?
Yeah, but I don't fucking
live with my mistress.
I mean, his fucking slippers?
Go on.
Well, when I left there, I...
started thinking about it.
When I was, I don't know,
16 years old...
my son's age...
I came home from school,
and there was this note
from my Aunt Quin.
My mother had been pregnant
with another kid
after my sister Barbara.
Change-of-life baby,
they called it, and...
Well, she started bleeding.
I was supposed find my father
and get him over there ASAP.
I called every number I had.
I left messages all over town.
And finally, that night,
about 10:00,
he called me back.
Hello?
Anthony, what's the matter?
Ma's in the hospital.
I-I think she was--
she was bleeding.
The baby.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, shit!
- Okay, pal.
- The lamb chops
are gonna be overcooked.
I'm tied up,
but I'm gonna get over
to the hospital right away.
He came and got me
the next morning.
We went over to the hospital.
Walked into her room.
You're okay, baby, you're okay.
No, you're okay!
Your life is just
so wonderful and okay!
Lee...
Where were you last night?
I was at the Yankee game.
You were with that whore.
What do you take me for,
an idiot?
No, Lee, that's not true!
I picked up Anthony from school,
we went to the game.
Nicky gave us the tickets.
You're a goddamn liar.
I swear to God, Lee,
the car broke down!
The timing belt!
We had to stay
at Cousin Jimmy's.
Marone, when we got home
and saw that note,
I was worried sick.
Ask Anthony,
you don't believe me.
Where were you last night,
Anthony?
We were at Cousin Jimmy's, Ma.
She could've fuckin' died
from her miscarriage.
Fuck her.
Was there any blame on his part?
This man you emulate?
The lies?
The betrayals with other women?
Listen to me.
This is very important.
Your mother had her faults,
but after all this time,
what should we do
with the old woman?
Have an auto-da-fé?
Burn her at the stake?
You need to forgive her
and move on.
She made my father
give my dog away.
I thought your father
was a big, tough guy.
He probably didn't want
to hear her bullshit anymore.
He gave my dog away
to his girlfriend's kid.
Big fuckin' deal.
If it was up to her,
she would have had it killed.
All right, thanks.
Book value's 17 grand.
I'll knock that off
the principal.
I fucking love this car.
So you'll get another one.
Is that your sponsor?
I'll see you when
you get out of rehab.
We'll figure out the rest
of the payments.
You can do this, man.
I have faith in you.
There's no chemical solution
to a spiritual problem.
It could've been another TIA.
It's hard to tell.
Was any of this accompanied
by a lapse in memory?
I don't know.
Had you brought him in right
away, I might have more answers.
That medicine stopped working.
I took more,
and it didn't do shit.
I'm like the walking dead.
Medication's like cooking.
Sometimes we just need
to adjust the ingredients.
Who gives a shit?
I'm so fuckin' blue.
Well, what do you expect?
All you do is go to funerals
all the time.
I'm trapped.
What's the goddamn point?
Goddamn house arrest.
My life is only death.
I'm living in a grave.
I beat prison, and for what?
I have no children.
Would somebody please
explain this to me?
So, Hesh tells me
you met your dad's goomah.
Yeah.
You had to see this woman
in her prime.
Nice, huh?
Nice?
She was JFK's girlfriend
for, like, three years.
No shit!
Right, I remember
hearing about her.
Fucking knockout.
Beautiful, classy.
JFK, huh?
How do you like that?
Yeah, he'd have her up
to the White House
on the weekends,
when his wife was out of town.
This woman was like a...
like a princess.
I'll tell you what.
For a while there,
Jackie Kennedy thought
the marriage was over.