♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon In your eyes ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
Here he is, Mr. Clean.
Want some coffee?
Where's your dirties?
I'll get 'em.
What?
I don't know, it's, it's...
It's hard seein' you like this.
What, workin', with a real job?
It's like I been tellin' Feech,
it's been a long strange trip.
Feech.
Anyway, it's the luck
of the draw, that shit.
Could've just as easily
been me that went away.
Come on, I was gonna be there
that night of the hijack.
Well, it ain't like you
came away totally unscathed.
No, a couple of goons jumped me
and cut my head open.
I couldn't go. Still...
They could've killed ya.
- You ended up in the E.R.
- Got 16 stitches.
You got 15 years.
You always were a lucky fuck.
Well, that's not
completely true.
I got other sorrows in my life.
Like him, for example.
- Thanks for lunch.
- Stick with me, kid,
I'll have ya eatin' lunch
like that every day.
I'm serious about
this massage therapy.
Well, you should keep a square
job like that, for appearances.
Look at me with the bakery.
I told my cousin
I wanna stay a civilian.
Ah, yes.
The boy king.
Can I trust you if I talk to you
frankly about him?
What are you doin'?
I gotta make a stop.
The fuck you doin'?!
- Excuse me?
- What the fuck you doin'?
I'm trimmin' a lawn.
My nephew does the lawns
in this neighborhood.
I been workin' this
neighborhood for 26 years.
Are you fuckin' deaf?
I said my nephew has this area.
Gary La Manna.
Fuck off, huh?
I'm busy here.
You want me to fuck off?!
How about I fuck off all over
your stupid fuckin' face?!
You fuckin' mutt, huh?
You don't work
this neighborhood!
Jesus Christ, we're on parole.
The fuck you doin'?
Anthony said the cable box
has to be on.
It's on, I'm doin' it.
But let me tell ya,
our glass house couples
could probably decorate
in about 24 hours.
They have to. Each week...
Tony's whole life was horses...
- No, it's not her.
- That's Judy!
- No, it's not Judy.
- The fuck.
Yes, it is, of course it is.
- Why am I on there?
- Holy shit.
- What?
- I've seen Judy, that's Judy.
- That's not you.
- Judy has brown eyes.
What's that, my trial?
- You don't know the eyes.
- No, I do know the eyes--
Come on! I see my
daughter call her Judy!
Sweet Judy brown eyes...
That's Bobby.
The fuck is this?
Junior, this is not you,
it's a TV program.
A movie.
- Judy.
- What?
Ton'.
He's here.
Tony, hey, thanks for seein' me.
How are ya?
So you want somethin',
uh, coffee? Bialy?
Nah, I'm good, thanks.
What's on your mind?
Well, honestly,
I'll get right to the point.
As regards to your uncle,
'cause of the promotion and all,
I kinda thought I'd be
out on the street more.
Stayin' off the street nowadays
is a good thing, no?
It's a joke.
I know. I mean,
I'm not complainin'.
It's just it's over a year,
and I'm still pickin' up
prescriptions.
What do ya need, money?
I mean, all I want's a chance to earn.
I mean, I'm happy to do it,
it's just 40 minutes I spent
at Rite Aids yesterday
gettin' him some stool softener
that was on sale.
With Jan and the kids
to feed now...
How's she doin', anyways?
My sister.
She sleeps a lot.
It's hard.
Still with the Epstein-Barr, huh?
It's tough on her. I don't know.
Two kids, a ready-made family.
She's prone to depression,
frankly.
Mm.
I mean, not that
I have any regrets.
No, no, of course not,
she's a good kid.
Look, Bobby, marriage...
or any partnership
for that matter,
is a give and a take.
All right, look...
I hear what you're sayin',
but the truth is
I depend on you.
Beppy? Tommy? Come on.
You're the only one
I can trust over there.
And believe it or not, it's
important to me that he's cared for.
All right, let me figure out
how to take care of you.
Maybe you could make more
collections or somethin'.
Thanks, Ton'.
I appreciate it.
Yeah, all right.
All right.
And Friday we have fish--
if you're Catholic--
so that's nice.
- Sounds like the Ritz.
- Mm.
Ya gotta see her, Aunt Mary,
she's the belle of the ball
over there.
Here, Ma, rest those dogs.
Hey, what's goin' on?
Nobody cuttin' the lawn?
Oh, Marone. Mr. Vitro,
the gardener?
Somebody beat him up,
broke his arm.
God forbid.
Sal Vitro? Who beat him up?
Some men in a Cadillac.
He was mowin' a lawn
on Kimball Street.
Man said he didn't want him
in the neighborhood.
Poor Sal, what a nice man he is.
He put my garbage cans out
every time he cut my grass.
What's his name, Aunt Mary?
- Salvatore Vitro.
- Ma!
The guy that beat him up!
Man came by and said
he was gonna cut the lawns.
I said, "No, I want Mr. Vitro."
E. Gary La Manna Landscapin'.
Do you know him?
Eat your scones.
I'll straighten it out.
95.5, WPLJ in Brooklyn.
Sorry, we're not open.
What not open?
A man in your position turn
away fuckin' business now?
I didn't know
it was you, Lorraine.
Here ya go. That's most of it.
Let me ask you a question, Dan.
Say I'm some big nigger
standing here, instead of a woman.
You still gonna tell me
you got most of it?
Let's go, chop-chop.
Pay the woman.
Phil, hey.
I was just thinkin' about you.
Those Islander tickets, right?
How about this humidity?
Hey!
Guys, please, whatever this is--
Shut up.
Two times you were told to
kick up to fuckin' Johnny Sack.
And what do you do, huh?
You kick up to Little Carmine?
- Tape her.
- No, no!
Little Carmine,
he was my father's friend!
Philly, Joey, look,
Okay. Okay. Okay.
You're right, I'm sorry,
I'll pay you, okay?
I'll do anything you want.
I'll suck your cock, okay?
All of you guys!
- You'll suck our cocks?
- Yeah!
She any good?
What am I askin' you for?
You probably showed her how.
- Shut up.
- Please, guys.
Relax.
This'll muffle the shot.
Adios, you fuckin' skank!
Hey, look at this, Joey.
Today's her lucky day.
Only made it to the R's.
Next time...
there'll be no next time.
Come on.
Take as long
as you like, no rush.
I've got my Times crossword
and Agnes here will get you
anything you need.
Thanks, Mel.
So how's it bein' home, Angelo?
Enjoyin' livin'
with your daughter?
It's like paradise.
I eat like a pharaoh,
I got my own room, cable TV.
I have cable.
My grandson,
he asked me, he says,
how come he never met
his grandpa before?
I said, "Because Grandpa's
been in Special Forces."
First he was afraid of me.
But I said, "Come on,
we'll get some ice cream,
we'll go to the park,
it'll be--"
- Well, anyway, here we all are.
- Right.
I called you boys because
Lorraine calls me and she said
there's a situation in our
family that's gotten outta hand
with John and Little Carmine.
This fuckin' Johnny.
He wouldn't even let
the maggots get on Carmine
before he's tellin' me
to kick up direct to him.
Problem is, Carmine
never named a successor.
Now, we all assumed
it'd be Johnny 'cause the, uh,
son's down in Miami with
the discos and the whatnot.
He's grabbin'
with both hands, John.
This could get ugly.
There's a lot of potential...
for bloodshed.
Potential?
They almost killed us.
Jason, men are talking here.
Now, you're close to John.
- You have any ideas?
- What are you askin' him for?
He never even had the makin's
of a varsity athlete.
Your point bein' what, Junior?
Oh, forget it, he's j--
he's just breakin' balls.
All right, one thought I had
in the interest of harmony...
maybe there could be
a power-sharin' situation.
The Sopranos have two bosses.
That's not all it's cracked up
to be, believe you me.
Let's not get into that
right now. Okay?
What I was thinkin'
was three bosses,
a triumvir-thing, like Caesar.
Little Carmine, Johnny and you.
I'm retired.
You were Carmine's consigliere
for over 30 years.
If it wasn't for that little
construction beef down in Yonkers,
it'd be you runnin'
that family today.
Things happen how they happen.
Think about it.
Doesn't have to be nine-to-five.
You could still take
your grandson to the park.
Things get heavy, you're just
another voice to weigh in.
And John still does
better financially
than he ever did under Carmine.
There he is.
Salvatore, my Dali.
My aunt told me about it.
I mean, what'd I ever do
to this guy?
They released
these fucks from the can--
obviously, he wasn't
rehabilitated.
There's my livelihood.
I don't have a yard no more,
Sally, I'm in a condo.
Otherwise, you know, I'd have
ya out there with your snippers,
even with your bum wing.
My wife, at this point...
she's got me thinkin'
about goin' to the cops.
What are you talkin' about?
Where you from?
I don't know what to do.
You got friends, don't ya?
Well, you know I always
steered clear of stuff.
What stuff?
I go, I talk to the guy for ya.
Get you back your stops.
I know him.
Yeah?
So you give me a token.
I don't know, couple percent.
Thanks, Paulie.
This one and the next one.
There he is,
the king of breadsticks.
I'll give ya a breadstick
up your ass. Come here.
Hey.
Come on. Sit down.
So... how's the kid, huh? Tony.
He's good, you know.
But ask me, he should've
stood with Carmela.
Some men need wives, huh.
Tell you when to shit
and when to scratch your ass.
Who needs 'em, huh?
What can I do for ya, Paul?
I got a guy, I think
you may have run into him.
Gardener name of Sal Vitro?
Does my aunt's grass.
He says your nephew's
movin' into his neighborhood,
- Franklin Parkway.
- His neighborhood.
He's been workin' there since
back when I lived there even.
Anyway, I'm here puttin'
in a word for the kid.
So do me a favor, huh?
You and your nephew
over there, lay off.
Hey, biscott'.
No.
You know Mr. Jerry, the fruit,
owns those hair salons, huh?
He came to me the other day.
He asked me to take
his action on the Knicks.
Jerry's my fuckin' customer.
For years now.
Which is why I told him no.
This fuckin' gardener, Paulie,
he cut the hair
on your balls, too?
He's a friend of my Aunt Mary's.
Which is why he don't
belong to nobody.
Well, what do you know
about who belongs to what?
You been away 20 fuckin' years!
Which entitles me to earn!
Which entitles you to shit.
In my book, you get points
for stayin' outta the can.
Good thing for me, then, that
your book don't mean ugatz to me!
What's yours is yours, Paulie,
but what ain't
is anybody else's!
Now do yourself a fuckin' favor
and get the fuck outta my store!
So we're pickin' Bobby up, or
he's gonna meet us at Uncle Jun's?
He took the kids
to the 12 o'clock mass.
I didn't know he was religious.
At this point
he'll try anything, I guess.
Bobby Jr. started
wetting his bed again.
Practically every night.
Bobby came by
to see me the other day.
Really?
So we discuss his career.
I'm his wife.
Sometimes he needs a push.
Well Junior's your uncle too,
in case you wanna play a little
more of an active role--
I try, believe me.
Despite all the work
I have with my own family.
You know, Tony, I cook for Bobby
and the kids every night.
I did Sunday dinner at my house,
and now I gotta
prepare the starters
and schlep 'em to Uncle Jun's.
Yeah, Barb's helpin' out
all the way down from Brewster.
Barbara's kids are normal.
This family stuff,
these Sunday dinners--
they're important, Janice.
Hey, Jan.
Julio, help me get this order?
Okay.
You know, every day
I understand more and more
what Ma went through.
I mean, we bitch about her,
but I tell you,
it is less and less a mystery
why she was the way she was.
She chose to be that way.
You don't choose that, Tony.
An ungrateful husband,
selfish kids...
How's all the food
that Janice prepared?
Two more minutes. Artie's
re-sautéing the mushrooms.
Could I get you guys
a glass of wine?
- Somethin' to drink?
- No, I'm good.
I'll have a pinot grigio.
Twenty minutes,
start the shells.
Just redoin' the mushrooms.
Uh, two minutes, tops.
Well relax, I just, uh...
came in to say hello.
So how ya doin'?
Hangin' in.
Heard you were over there
at the Motel Six.
My aunt took the house back.
I'm movin' in with my cousin
at the end of the month.
Look, you know, if you want,
I'm stayin' over at my mother's
and the place is empty.
You can
bunk with me for a while.
No. Thank you.
I was talkin' to
my cousin, Tony B.,
and he said it's fuckin' stupid
that we're on the outs.
I'm tellin' ya, the place
is just sittin' there.
Two extra bedrooms.
I don't know.
Why not?
Artie, we're like brothers.
How long are we gonna
hold a grudge?
Thanks, Ton'.
Thank you, very much.
Alright.
All right.
Uh, listen, uh, I gotta
talk to ya about your linens.
You know, the napkins
and tablecloths, all that shit.
I got somethin' goin'. I
think I can save ya like 70%.
There's been a lot of
progress to the facade.
In some instances,
all of the paint comes off.
Now tell me, what
product is used...
I don't get these
old antique houses.
They're grimy lookin'.
We gonna eat today or what?
Barbara and Tom aren't here yet
with the entrees, Uncle Jun'.
When were they supposed to come?
Two o'clock, I told you
five minutes ago. Here.
Why don't we start
on the macaroni?
Everybody come on!
Bolognese has meat, obviously,
the marinara doesn't.
And Barb'll be here with the
chicken parm and the veal pizzaiol'.
So Anthony, how'd you guys do
against Delbarton last season?
Not so good. We lost both times.
- It's that line coach.
- Star-Ledger says Delbarton's
gonna be even tougher this
comin' year with that Chinese kid.
Your father never had the
makings of a varsity athlete.
Oh, what the--
What the hell's with you?
- What?
- It's not true.
I lettered in football.
You never played college ball.
College?
Those guys from Seton Hall were
seven feet tall, some of them.
Took an academic leave anyway.
Small hands,
that was your problem.
Oh yeah, Daddy always said that.
That's not the point.
What is it with you and this
obsession with this varsity crap?
The other day you said it.
And when I was a kid, you told
the girl cousins the same thing.
It was very hurtful.
Tony, relax,
it's not a big deal.
It's undermining.
And it's the kinda stuff
I'm teachin' my kids not to do.
So, I don't wanna hear it again!
End of subject!
Honey, pass me
the ricott', please.
- Hello?
- In here!
Hi. Sorry we're late.
- The Tappan Zee was a nightmare.
- Checkin' the trucks again.
Well, sit down and dig
into this medley of pastas
that Janice whipped up.
How you doin', Uncle Jun'?
I don't like tardiness.
Let me unwrap these.
- This looks great.
- Thank you.
So comin' down
I heard on the radio,
looks like the Jets are gonna
grab that kid from Tulsa.
That tight end.
We still get those season
tickets, big brother?
All I know is you never had
the makings of a varsity athlete.
- Aw, son of a bitch!
- What?
Did I just tell you
not to say that again?!
Say what?
You don't like the way I
talk, get outta my house!
Here we go.
- Tony--
- "Tony," shit!
Get your coat. We're leavin'.
- I don't have a coat.
- Then get movin', goddamn it.
Will someone please
tell me what's goin' on?
It's my last Sunday dinner here,
that's what's goin' on.
Uncle Jun', was that
really necessary?
He's a goddamn hothouse flower,
that's his problem.
Thank you for getting
my TV fixed, Paulie.
Such a sin.
He fired his Spanish helper.
Took his boy outta college
'cause he couldn't afford it anymore.
He said it's his
last time comin' here.
You speak to the man?
I'll see ya later.
So. What's up?
Nothin', uh, thought we'd be
first in line for openin' day.
Peanuts are on me.
- Angelo Garepe came to see me.
- Mmm-hmm.
Lorraine Calluzzo reached out.
Fucking twat.
Didn't you fuck her once?
Yeah, a million years ago.
What, is nothin' a secret?
Obviously you wanna
maintain stability,
but havin' Phil Leotardo smack your
shies around, is that the smartest thing?
I gotta nip this
Little Carmine shit in the bud.
Otherwise I could see a lotta
people start fuckin' around.
Power vacuum,
the capos bide their time,
nobody's sure who to pay,
so nobody gets paid.
All right, I hear ya.
No one likes that cunt anyway.
Any problem, she's, "Whack
this one, whack that one."
Never enough body count
for Lorraine.
Fuck her. Let her
taste her own medicine.
All right, whatever.
I'll tell ya somethin' else.
In large measure I blame you for
this shit with Little Carmine.
The fuck did I do?
You legitimized him.
Man of your stature goes
to Florida to see that schmuck?
All right, come on, huh?
We both agree
that Little Carmine's
a fuckin' asshole.
But the fact is,
he's got a followin'
- loyal to his old man.
- So?
So, Angelo had an idea.
What if...
and he's just floatin' this
to keep the peace...
Mmm-hmm.
...what if there was
a power-sharin' situation?
- Power-sharing.
- You're all in charge equally,
but no major decisions
can be made without
- a majority of two.
- What the fuck?
Hey, this way you're not
such a big target for the feds.
Three of the other families
have this kind of arrangement.
What's this,
the fuckin' U.N. now?!
- Alright, forget it! Forget I said it!
- Fuck that!
Everyone deserves
To choose how they feel.
To experience the love, the joy,
the happiness, the passion...
Where's Junior?
Upstairs takin' a nap.
The garage is open,
his car is gone.
Where is he?
I'm tellin' ya, I don't know.
You don't think somebody
put the snatch on him, do ya?
When did you see him last?
An hour ago? Two?
I fell asleep.
Maybe he drove to the store?
His wallet's here, his watch.
With his bail, he's not allowed
to leave the house anyway.
Junior.
So when they say they're
not interested, you say,
you're not interested
in keepin' kids off drugs?
What, Shabazz?
Nobody wants them
Turkish taffies.
You push harder. What did I
tell you about profit margin?
- Where's Johnny?
- We closed now.
- Lemme talk to Damiano.
- We rented the hall today.
I'm lookin' for
Johnny Soprano, goddamn it.
Hey! This here's a church!
You can't talk
like that in here.
Get out. Go on.
We're workin' here.
- I wanna see Johnny Soprano.
- Ain't no Johnny here.
I'm his brother, damn it.
He owns this place.
Hold up, now.
Back in the day this was
Italian neighborhood.
Some fellas had this place here.
Kept those vending machines.
Well, there ain't no vending
machines here no more.
Come on, fool, go on!
All right, Roberta, thanks.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Bobbi Sanfillipo?
Junior hasn't kept time
with her in years.
Yeah, I realize that.
You know, now that
I think about it,
Junior was actin' a little
peculiar when I got here today.
Said he wanted to see Johnny.
What Johnny?
- His brother?
- I don't know.
Also there the other day,
we were watchin' the TV,
he thought he saw himself
on one of the programs.
...in my home.
We have got
the dishwashing liquid...
- Hello?
- Yeah, it's me.
Did you drop off
the dry cleaning?
Your uncle's missing,
he took his car.
- He didn't call you, did he?
- No.
- Where the hell is he?
- He's like an old woman, Bobby.
He's probably gossiping
with one of the neighbors.
Did you check
the Ramirezes' next door?
I'm afraid he might've wandered.
My grandfather did this.
Maybe you better call Tony.
I can't just dump this on Tony.
I gotta find him.
I need you to come here
in case he comes back.
- Bobby, I just can't--
- I need your help here!
Jesus Christ! Sometimes I think I
love Junior more than you do!
We may know that there
are five essentials for victory.
One, he will win
who knows when to fight
and when not to fight.
Two, he will win
who knows how to...
You Gary?
I'm Jimmy. Gary's up there.
Hey! Come down here!
What?
I said get down here!
I wanna talk to you.
What do you want?
I'm a friend of Sal Vitro's.
My aunt lives on this street.
So?
So I'm guessin' Sal Vitro
used to do this yard.
- A lotta things used to be.
- Maybe so.
But you're gonna make good
on his busted arm.
Oh yeah? Why am I gonna do that?
- 'Cause I said so, that's why.
- Eat shit, pal.
Why don't you take a walk, huh?
Unh!
Aaah!
Ohh!
Gimme your wallet, you prick.
This and the mower's
a down payment.
By next Tuesday I want Sal
Vitro's whole orthopedist bill paid.
Let's call it 1,200.
Top of that, from now on I get 10% of
whatever you make in this neighborhood.
You motherfucker!
Shut up, I'll give ya a crack.
Time is it?
Don't worry, we'll
take the tunnel.
All right, this meetin' today.
We're tryin' to nail down a new
contractor, now with Massarone gone.
That office park by Troy Hills?
And listen--
and this is very important--
if any of this shit between little Carmine
and Johnny comes up, you clam up.
- You got it, Ton'.
- Say nothin',
'cause you say
the wrong thing...
- What?
- Tony, it's me.
Listen, it's your uncle.
He's gone.
- You mean he's dead?
- No, no, no, no.
We think he might've
wandered off.
You know, I didn't wanna call you, but
it's been a couple hours now.
- Fuck him.
- He said he was goin' to see Johnny.
You think he might've
meant your dad?
- What?
- He's wanderin', Ton'.
He can wander off
the Palisades for all I care.
He's fuckin' dead to me.
I called you almost an hour ago.
Where the hell have you been?
Hello? I was picking
up your daughter?
Stay here, I'm goin' out.
Where the hell is Tommy?
- I sent him home.
- Oh, wonderful.
He gets the day off
and I get to wait by the phone.
It's because of him
Junior escaped, Janice.
- Dad, can I go with you?
- No.
Can Janice go
and we just stay here?
What'd I tell you
about bein' impolite?
If anyone cares,
I'll be upstairs lying down.
One hour of television, then
you both finish your homework.
And you, lay off the Snapple.
What galls me is that before
Little Carmine went to Florida,
I was actually close with him.
I was in his wedding party,
for chrissake.
Organized his whole
fuckin' bachelor party.
Lesbian show, whores--
fuckin' disgusting.
Then when they had that kid
with the lung problem,
who you think got him that
doctor on Park Avenue?
Water over the dam, huh?
I had no idea you guys
were that close.
Close. We were like brothers.
It's a shame that you can't
find a way to work things out.
Gimme me piece of bread, huh?
Have you thought about this?
Maybe you let him keep Lorraine,
and you take a bigger piece
of his Florida shit, the clubs.
If I wanted to worry
about Florida,
I would move to fuckin' Miami.
You know, it wasn't long ago I
remember you used to wait in the car.
And as far as I'm concerned
you should still be there!
- John. He was just tryin'--
- Fuck he was "just"!
Everybody's got
a goddamned opinion?
I didn't say nothin', Ton'.
What the fuck did I say?!
- I'm sorry, T., I just thought--
- Now I gotta
un-fuck what you just fucked up.
Gotta do somethin' nice
for Johnny. Like what?
What the fuck
am I supposed to do?!
You gotta understand, this shit
between Johnny and Little Carmine is bad.
The instability. But worse comes to
worse, it could work to our advantage.
How?
They fight, we pick up
any crumbs from the fallout.
The odds are that Johnny'll
end up on top, but who knows.
So keep your ears open
and your mouth shut!
Apparently there's a new
president at the electrician's union.
Tony sent Chrissy
over there to talk to him.
Something I've always been
meaning to get straight.
Tony calls Christopher
his nephew,
yet sometimes
you refer to them...
as cousins.
Yeah, right. See,
Chrissy's not Tony's nephew.
Chrissy's Carmela's cousin.
She was first cousin to Dickie
Moltisanti-- Chrissy's dad?
But he was always kinda like
a big brother to Tony, Dickie.
So Tony calls
Chrissy his nephew.
- It's an Italian thing.
- Okay.
Although technically
Tony and Chrissy are cousins.
Joanne Blundetto, Chrissy's mom,
is Tony's cousin
on his mother's side?
But, like, way back.
Like, from the old country
or somethin'.
Robyn?
What?
How much longer am I gonna
have to keep doin' this?
Major RICO against Tony Soprano?
Those things
take years to build.
This recent case against
Joe Macino in New York?
It was seven years before
indictments were handed down.
Hello, handsome.
Where you livin' now?
'Round here?
- Do you know me?
- Do I know you?
Jupiter Club, on Sixth Street?
Caught fire, that place.
Lotta people died.
Do you know my brother Johnny?
Hmm.
You got all the looks,
I'll tell ya that.
What are you sayin'?
You and I had relations?
Sumbitch taxicab
run me right over my foot.
- I have a car.
- Want a date?
I'll give ya half-and-half
in the backseat.
I wanna go home.
Well, lemme get a ride
by the shelter.
I have to find my car.
How ya doin'?
I don't gotta tell you shit.
See some I.D., sir?
Fuck you, copper, I
know my rights.
Hey, take it easy now.
My car was stolen, I
want my lawyer.
What's his name?
Mel.
Okay. Mel what?
See you went out and forgot
your shoes. Where do you live?
- Belleville.
- Sure you don't want to tell me your name?
You're not in any
trouble or anything.
Corrado Soprano.
Tell you what, sir.
Why don't you come and get in the car
where it's nice and warm,
we'll try to figure out
how to get in touch
with your lawyer, all right?
Oh, Jesus, Uncle Jun',
thank God!
This gentleman
reside here, ma'am?
He's my uncle.
Where have you been?
We were worried sick.
I'll need to see some
identification, ma'am.
Oh, okay, I'll get my bag.
His, actually.
Bobby, get Uncle Jun's wallet.
It's upstairs on his dresser.
Uncle Jun', you're freezing.
We found him walking across
the Clay Street Bridge in Newark.
Newark? Where's your car?
- They stole it.
- Who stoled it?
You know who.
It's him.
Junior Soprano.
- Here ya go, sir.
- Go shit in your hat.
Uncle Jun', stop!
Thank you, officers. Thank you.
Uncle Jun', did you tell Tommy
you were goin' to see my father?
Of course not.
What are you doing?! Sit!
I have to use the facilities.
Bobby, go with him.
Goddamn it,
I can piss by myself!
Okay. Okay.
I'll open some soup.
You go out for some exercise,
people give ya
the goddamn third degree!
- Hi, Ellie.
- Hello, Louie.
How's the big slot machine king?
Oh, I ain't doin' that
no more, I'm retired.
Tony, it's me.
What's the matter?
It's Uncle Jun'.
They found him in Newark...
in his slippers.
He was looking for Daddy, Tony.
He may have Alzheimer's.
I don't know.
Good, maybe he'll forget
my phone number.
Jesus Christ.
Moozadell en carrozza.
- Still warm.
- Artie?
We're in the middle of
a family meeting.
I'm not even here.
He's our uncle, Tony. There may be
something seriously wrong with him.
Listen, Janice, like I
told your husband.
He's fuckin' dead to me.
Are you that fragile?
You don't know the half of
it when it comes to us,
and if you're so concerned, take him
to the fuckin' doctor. 'Cause I've had it.
You're the only one he
relates to, Tony.
We won't even be able
to get him in the car.
Fuck him. You reap what you sow.
You sure did.
You think maybe there's a reason
you're living all alone here, Tony,
without your family?
Oh-ho. Wait a
minute, wait a minute.
You're gonna give me
advice on marriage?
You know Tony, there's a lot I can
say right now that I am not gonna say.
Fuck it! Say it, say it!
Who gives a fuck?
Think I don't know what
you're doin' here, Janice, huh?
Tryin' to pawn
this shit off on me?
Your whole fuckin' life,
whenever there's a family problem
you either shirk your duties
or you run the fuck away!
- Ran away?
- Tibet or fuckin' Berkley...
I was 18 years old!
And I was 16 when
you left me in that house
with our head-case of a mother,
who you all of a sudden relate
to so fuckin' well!
- I was merely saying I understand--
- Free-spirit Janice,
rebel without a cause.
While I sit here
mired in her bullshit,
tryin' to be a good son
while you're off droppin' acid
- and blowin' roadies!
- Roadies?
Oh, you don't wanna know.
That--That is not true, Tony.
Now you--you tell him that
that's not true!
Poor fuckin' Janice,
she's so fuckin' depressed.
she can't get up off the couch
'cause she's so fuckin'
tired from her Epstein-Barr.
Poor fuckin' Janice--
va fongool.
- Why don't we just calm down?
- Know, what,
maybe you were the smart one
'cause you got
outta here for a while.
But your hippie string ran out,
and now you're back,
and you're gonna do to this man
what you do to every one of 'em.
- Fuckin' piece of shit!
- Ah, you stupid cunt.
- Agghhh!
- Just like your mother, huh?
Now you can do to him
what she did to Daddy!
Enough!
Cocksucker!
You want more responsibility?
Start with
controllin' your wife.
And then from nowhere,
he cracks the one kid's head
with the shovel,
then the other one
he knocks out of a tree.
He jumped out the tree,
and come at me with a chainsaw.
I got a right
to defend myself, Ton'.
All right, take it easy. Relax.
Sal Vitro's been
workin' the area
since my ma was still
workin' at Kresge's.
I should be able to help out
a kid from my own neighborhood.
All right, how about this. Vitro
and your nephew split the area.
East of Dyer is yours.
West of Dyer goes to him.
As for the broken arm,
I don't know,
give him 500 bucks.
I already told the guy 12, T.
Well there's fuckin'
compromises in life, Paulie.
All right, make it a grand,
for the pain and sufferin'.
Naturally, I want my taste,
retroactive,
'cause this is the first time I've
been hearin' about any of this.
It's a new venture. My
nephew's barely on his feet.
I mean, I didn't
wanna start kickin' up,
then pull it back
if it don't work out.
And of course, Vitro'll
do your grass too, Ton'.
No charge.
Remind me to talk
to you about that later.
There he is. Salvatore, my boy,
how's that pitchin' arm?
It's gettin' there.
Paul, say hello
to Mr. Gaultieri.
That's my middle name. Paul.
So I talked to that guy.
Good news.
I gotcha 500 for your arm,
and you keep half your area.
- Half?
- It could've been nothin'.
Lucky you know me.
West of Dyer's yours,
east belongs to him.
Paulie, my wife's gonna sh--
All right, thank you, Paulie.
Oh, one more thing.
You're gonna have to cut
a couple of lawns on the comp.
Some friends of ours.
Some shot, huh,
the way it hooked?
Ya got a fuckin'
horseshoe up your ass, you.
Mr. Soprano!
Harry Winer. I was your
mother's neurologist.
I did her work-up
from Green Grove?
Ah, yeah, how ya doin'?
So I assume your sister told you
I'm treating your uncle.
Oh yeah, yeah, she mentioned it.
- Catch you in there, T.
- Yeah.
I think with the right meds we
can control these things.
What things?
The infarcts.
They're akin to mini-strokes?
He suffered some significant
brain trauma the other day.
You probably noticed him
acting differently
over the past six months,
a year, maybe?
Oh, well to tell ya
the truth, me and my uncle,
we don't talk much anymore.
Oh, I'm sorry
to hear that, uh...
Don't be. He's a hostile prick.
Well, unfortunately obstinacy is
consistent with his condition.
Impatience, forgetfulness,
particularly with
short-term memory.
Do you find he'll ask the same
question every three minutes?
What time it is...?
I don't know. Maybe. Yeah.
Well it's frustrating, I know, but anyway,
the last thing I wanted to do was
get in the middle
of a family squabble.
I just wanted to say hello.
- Well, nice seein' ya.
- Okay. All right.
Members of the squirrel family,
the prairie dog
makes it home mainly...
Tommy?
Brought you some fish.
Tryin' to clean out
my refrigerator.
Make sure you form a seal
when you shut that freezer door.
Of the two main species,
the black-tailed prairie dog
is much more widespread,
inhabiting much of the Great
Plains and the Great Basin.
So how you feelin'?
Heard you had a little problem.
What problem?
All right...
but your doctor
said somethin' different.
Who, Kennedy?
Kennedy's your cancer doctor.
I knew that.
You said doctor.
The white-tailed prairie dog
lives at higher elevations,
hibernating
throughout the winter.
Just take your medicine,
Uncle Jun'.
Make ya feel better.
Help with your memory.
Believe me, there's plenty
I'd like to forget.
Yeah, you and me both.
Feech was here?
What? Yeah, he came
to pay his respects.
So what's this I hear,
you ruled against Feech?
He's an important man.
Why is he bitchin' at
you about shit?
I'm still the boss
of this family.
Despite any arrangements.
Yellow in color,
they often have dark...
These prairie dogs,
they'll sleep during the day.
Oh, yeah?
Look, the doctor said you...
may not have known
what you were sayin'.
What are you talkin' about?
The varsity shit.
So what else did Feech
have to say?
Gettin' a new top
on his convertible.
All right, let's assume that you didn't
know what you were sayin', that...
that you forget when
you say shit over and over.
Yeah?
Why's it gotta
be somethin' mean?
Why can't you repeat
something good?
There's the coyote.
I mean, don't you love me?