♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon In your eyes ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
Walter, hey, you looking for me?
Yeah, the Crazy Horse.
That's you, right?
Yeah, you got something?
Yeah, pole camera,
three days ago.
She locks up the club
for the night.
She's throwing away the garbage.
Yeah?
But then she changes her mind.
Finis.
Interesting.
The good news is, no polyps.
The bad news is, as you can see,
you've got a fairly severe case
of ulcerative colitis.
- Jesus Christ.
- She was getting better.
Then last week,
another flare-up.
How are you doing
with the Prozac? Is it helping?
She can't even sleep.
- Ma.
- Well, look at her.
I'd like to start you
on a regime of Prednisone.
It's a steroid.
Like for weightlifters?
I've had great success with it
treating this type of condition.
I do need to warn you, however,
there are certain side effects.
Now mind you,
these are temporary,
but there's a good chance
of weight gain,
accompanied by
Cushing's Syndrome.
That's a swelling
of the facial features,
a sort of a moon face.
What?
You've seen Jerry Lewis
in the last year or two.
- Oh my god.
- She's planning a wedding,
for Christ's sake!
It was fine one day,
then suddenly I get
audio and no picture.
Somebody been
fooling around with this?
A.J. had his friends over.
Huh. How'd he do over there
with your dad?
- You know, raking the driveway?
- Fine.
Except my mother
kept hounding him,
asking him if we were
getting back together.
You know, I had a dream
I moved back in here.
You know, just for the record...
I realize what I did was wrong.
My...
activities while I lived here.
Knowing you were wrong
isn't the half of it, Tony.
Oh, really?
What's the other half?
Well, suppose something
did happen. Where, theoretically,
we did get back together.
Any marriage
would need fidelity.
Like Popeye says,
"I yam what I yam."
Well, I didn't marry a cartoon.
Well, it wouldn't be a cartoon.
You had your own
indiscretions yourself.
The thing with Furio?
I did not sleep with him, Tony.
I'm just saying that, you know,
we're all human, that's all.
You know, the truth is,
I got myself where I am.
But your open indiscretion,
your total disregard...
You're right, it was--
it was horrible.
To have a knot in your stomach
every time the phone rings.
Like you were saying, you know.
Theoretically, though,
if we do reconcile,
that stuff will never
happen again.
Come on, you gonna go or what?
I'm coming.
I was finishing my drink.
Fuck!
You can't stay holed up here.
That's not healthy, Carmine.
How'd it get to this?
Retaliation, counterattacks.
We're at a fucking "stagmire."
We back down now, bunker down,
what kind of a message
does that send?
Not just to Johnny's people,
either.
Billy Leotardo.
What the hell was that?
This Blundetto asshole
went off the reservation.
All due respect, Carmine,
that's why you need
to get out there,
put your ear to the street,
let the guys see you
take the reins.
That's not how
I wanna handle it.
Hey, don't get me wrong.
I always liked your cousin.
But whacking Phil's brother
was a major poke in the ass.
You know, my cousin almost cried
when I put him in charge
of the casino?
After all I did
for that blue-eyed prick,
then he completely
fucks me over.
Now I practically gotta get
down on my knees to Johnny Sack.
Where the fuck you been?
You're late.
Highway was jammed
with broken heroes
on a last-chance power drive.
Oh, you're gonna get
fucking cute now.
Anything on Tony B.?
Nah, he's still
on a milk carton.
There she is.
My smelly Valentine.
Christopher, that's not funny.
The fuck are you doing?
I can handle a cocktail
once in a while, right?
You guys okay?
You need anything else?
You still feeling sick, hon?
Please.
They gotta replace
her colon with a semicolon.
Maybe you should be a vegan.
The doctor says I gotta relax.
From what?
She's got the world at her feet,
she walks around
like impending doom.
Come on, we gotta go.
Take it easy, now.
Listen, don't listen to him.
People got their health,
they take it for granted.
How's your thing, the...?
Just gotta keep
an eye on it, that's all.
So Carm and me are getting
back together, maybe.
That's great.
The kids'll be thrilled.
Yeah.
When we get settled,
we'll have you guys over.
You know, family dinner.
Feel better, huh?
John.
First off,
let me just say how sorry
I am for your loss.
We all are.
Take your fucking sorries
and stick them in your ass.
I could say nothing.
Be a heartless prick.
He tried to talk, he couldn't
even say his last words.
Anybody ever die in your arms,
you cocksucker?
A family member?
Somebody you love?
No.
Well, give it time.
See if I can't
make that happen for you.
- All right, that's enough.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Philly, why don't you
go have a drink?
Don't tell me what to do, Jimmy.
Jimmy's right.
Aspetta.
Fuck 'em, John.
Fuck all of them.
Was that fucking necessary?
He shouldn't even
have been here.
He's got a right to be here.
He's got a right to
a lot of things right now.
My cousin acted alone.
I did not sanction this.
The lone-gunman theory.
You know how close
he and Angelo were in the can.
He flipped the fuck out!
When he whacked Joey Peeps,
what flipped him out that time?
What do you want, John?
What do you want me to say?
I want your cousin
on a fucking spit!
I don't know where he is.
- Nobody does.
- Fine.
Maybe one of your
other relatives then.
What, I gotta stand here
being threatened now?
All right, Chrissy...
All right, all right,
nobody's making threats.
Look, Tony's in hiding, John.
You either deliver
that prick to my door,
or I will rain a shit storm
down on you and your family
like you have never
fucking seen.
We're done here.
There are over 200,000
species of mollusks,
and right there is
a good example of a conch,
which is also known
as a knobbed whelk.
See, these raised spines on it
help keep it settled
wherever it lands...
That's what I call my dick.
I heard that.
That's just nasty.
Oh, fuck! Yo, check it!
Oh, shit!
Hurry up!
Don't touch it!
Apprentice Delaney,
get back here!
Little Meadow in a bridal gown.
Marone. Couple more years,
Grandma and Grandpa.
Bite your tongue.
So, the other day,
what you said.
I processed it.
Mm-hm.
You know, your feelings.
It really hit home with me,
finally.
You know,
with you out of the house,
I've had a chance to do
a lot of thinking.
I mean, it's partly my fault,
but I need something else
in my life.
You know, with Meadow
getting engaged, A.J. almost...
You want another kid.
No.
Mm.
It turns out there is a lot
for sale over on Crestview.
A little over an acre.
I was thinking
I could build a spec house
and take my dad in as a partner.
I mean, my allowance
is what it is, but...
How much is the lot?
600,000.
Anyway, he would oversee
the construction.
Well, I'll call Ginsberg
and have him free up
a down payment.
And then?
I'll move back in.
Supposing that happened,
what about the other issues
that were on the table?
Well...
I swear to you, on our children,
that my midlife crisis problems
will no longer intrude
on you anymore.
Okay.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What, are you having dinner?
Hey, you, have you settled
on a caterer yet?
Can I talk to you?
What's up? You hear from Tony?
I just talked to Kelvin, or Calvin,
whatever the fuck his name,
that redneck prick
from North Carolina.
He got a call from the Bureau
of Alcohol and Tobacco.
Some fucking bodega in Newark's
been selling cigarettes
without the tax stamps on it.
Stupid spics, they were supposed
to stamp them themselves.
The feds are all over it now.
I don't got enough
on my fucking mind?
Any idea how
you're gonna handle that?
Handle what?
Our cousin, you know,
Phil and John.
I don't know.
I gotta think about it.
From now on, Paulie supervises
the entire cigarette run.
You split everything
down the middle with him.
- What?
- You fucking heard me.
I got a fucking wedding
to pay for.
Well, if I were you,
I'd cut out the open bar.
Fuck this piece of shit.
I'm done! You hear me?
Put my life on the line!
My fucking life!
Baby, I hate
seeing you like this.
Fuck family, fuck loyalty.
You cost him a dime,
you're a fucking pariah.
I gave that fuck pieces
of my soul, Adriana.
You know what he said to me?
He said I should have
a fucking drink!
When?
Up there, when we were up
at Uncle Pat's farm.
Well, you don't need
to listen to him.
Isn't that why
you have a sponsor?
Him and Tony B.,
breaking my balls,
teasing me like
when I was little.
I mean, what kind of fucked-up,
undermining shit is that
to tell someone
who's got the disease?
You know I could take him out
in a second, that fat fuck.
Bang!
His kids wouldn't even
give a shit.
Don't talk like that.
You're a better man than he is.
A better person.
Fuck all this shit
with Paulie and all.
You know what hurts me worse,
right to my heart?
Him and our ass-wipe cousin,
that two-faced cocksucker.
He could get us all killed
with New York, and him,
Tony has to think about
what to do with him now,
after all this shit!
Me, he don't need
to fucking think!
Well, maybe I need to think!
Ever thought of that,
you fat fucking scumbag?
That's the guy, Adriana.
My Uncle Tony.
The guy I'm going to hell for.
Long Branch cops.
What do you think?
Not your average bulls.
Detectives.
Call the Long Branch PD,
find out what's up.
So, you all set?
Don't look at me.
Ah, you look good.
And you're gonna look nice
with the short hair.
Like what's-her-name.
That actress.
Just take me home.
I can drop you off,
but I really can't stay.
Why not?
All right, look, first off,
like I said before,
as far as all the medical bills
and the prescriptions,
that's covered, ad nauseam.
- You motherfucker.
- Hey, take it easy.
This is how you leave me?
When I'm almost burned to death
cooking you a fucking snack?
Come on, honey,
you could've just as easily
been making yourself
something to eat.
Am I that fucking horrible now?
No. You're not horrible at all.
- I'm going back to my wife.
- You selfish fuck.
I hate you.
Look, there's no future with us.
I told you that right from the get-go.
That's why I didn't want you
hitching your wagon to my star.
No.
You'll heal up.
You'll meet somebody else.
Fuck you!
You know, I didn't
come here to fight.
I came here to pick you up
and end this like a gentleman.
I'm gonna fucking kill myself.
I gotta take this.
Hello?
Is that you?
I know you're there, just
say something.
Where the fuck are--?
Your call cannot be com...
Yeah.
- Bing.
- Yeah, it's me.
Your friend at the phone
company, have him call me.
- Who, Gerard?
- I want to put traps on all my lines.
Adriana.
Oh, Jesus. What?
We need to talk.
I was buying medicine.
- This way, please.
- Let's go.
But my car!
Hello?
- Hey.
Give me a hand, will you? Uh...
I got more stuff in the car, so...
Where should I put it?
The bedroom.
Oh, you made it. Hey.
I was just starting dinner.
Yeah, smells good.
What is this?
I got you something,
you know, small.
Oh, this is beautiful.
Tony! With my black coat.
It's a Hermès.
Supposed to be the best.
There's the whipped butter too,
if you like.
Oh, no, this is all right.
This is fucking weird.
A.J.
No, he's right.
It is fucking weird.
You know what?
We should celebrate.
Oh!
Here, give me your glass.
The trick is,
you gotta hold the cork.
Don't let it fly out.
Gab's uncle got
a detached retina
at his own retirement party.
He never saw out
of that eye again.
That's festive.
I, uh...
I wanna make a toast.
To the people I love.
Nothing else matters.
- Hear, hear.
- Salute.
Whoa, slow down, slow down.
You're supposed to savor it.
It's important in life.
Open the door for Mr. Muckle!
- What?
- Open the door
- for Mr. Muckle, the blind man.
- How about my kumquats?
What'd you say?
- Kumquats!
- Wait!
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
It's all right. It's all right.
All right.
So?
I was throwing the
garbage out. So what?
Isn't that illegal anyway,
to film people
without telling them?
And the reason
you didn't just leave
the garbage in the dumpster?
Bills and stuff.
Our account numbers were on it.
Friend of yours?
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
- His name is Gilbert Nieves.
There were partial traces
of an infrared stamp
on his hand
from the Crazy Horse.
I don't know him.
But you told
the Long Branch police
that he was at the club
that night.
Let me ask you a question,
Miss La Cerva.
Do you really think
we have you in here
because we don't know
what's in that garbage bag?
He was stabbed in the club.
You tried to dispose
of the evidence.
- I didn't do nothin'.
- Miss La Cerva...
I suggest in the strongest
possible terms
that you start telling us
what you know.
There's this guy.
His name's Matush.
He's a drug dealer. He did it.
I swear, not me.
What's Matush's last name?
I don't know.
He's foreign,
the Mideast or something.
Pakistan.
Anyway, Christopher don't
let him deal in the club,
but once in a while he'd sell
me some X or whatever.
Adriana. Hey.
Hey.
This is my friend Kamal.
Listen, I need a favor.
We're trying to get
an apartment.
I gotta fax the guy
a copy of my passport.
You can't go to Kinko's?
The guy's waiting for it.
It will take two seconds,
I swear.
It's in the office, but hurry.
Christopher sees you in there, he'll shit.
Thanks.
That's for you.
This guy was at the club,
the dead guy.
But I never saw him before.
Matush said
he sold him coke once,
but the guy said Matush
ripped him off.
Like, it was all laxative.
Oh, boy.
What's the number again?
Oh, it's...
Hey, yo, you can't
be back here, man.
Oh. Cool out, yo!
What are you doing?
- Give me my money.
- What?
- Give it to me!
- Don't get stupid in here.
- I'm serious.
- Fuck off.
I got no beef with you.
You still sell
that beat shit, huh?
Fucking baby powder?
- Look, I don't know...
- Get him!
I'll kill you motherfuckers!
I'll kill you!
Oh, my God!
We had to wait till later
to get out the mops and stuff,
after we closed up.
What if Christopher--?
Nobody has to know anything.
But you don't
fucking understand!
It's cool, okay?
We'll take him out
through the basement.
Dump him in the ocean.
Why'd you help this Matush?
I wasn't helping him.
I was afraid for myself.
Besides, he's nice.
I don't know.
I didn't wanna see him
get into trouble.
Sounds like a real sweetheart.
The guy was gonna stab him.
He's not a bad person.
He's very religious.
Religious?
He prays, like, all the time.
He went through this period
where he rediscovered
his religion.
He don't even do drugs anymore.
He just deals.
And every month, he sends all
his money home to his family.
In Pakistan?
His brother runs a prep school.
Some place for young boys.
I was very impressed with that.
He's buckled down. He's gotten
much more serious as a person.
Does Christopher know what
happened that night?
No! You crazy?
Right now, you're
guilty of obstructing
an ongoing investigation
into a drug-related homicide.
You are looking down the barrel
at 25 years.
But I didn't do nothing.
Take your head
out of your ass, Adriana.
You knew exactly
what you were doing.
We can arrest you right now,
have you formally charged,
send you right over to
the Women's House of Detention.
Or, in the alternative,
you can cooperate.
But I've been fucking
cooperating!
You've been giving us shit,
and I've had it!
I want you wired up!
I want Tony Soprano on tape!
Your boyfriend too.
No, I'm not doing it!
Then you're all out of options!
I wanna talk to my lawyer.
Fine, who's your lawyer?
I don't have an official one.
Maybe Christopher
knows a good lawyer.
Oh, you fucking piece of shit.
I'll call the Public Defender.
They'll send someone down.
Might take awhile, though,
this hour of the night.
Think I left
some shoes over there.
I can iron these tomorrow.
What for?
Send 'em to the cleaners.
I kind of miss it, actually.
My wrist is getting weak.
I could help you there.
Get out of here.
No, let's give it some exercise.
Tony...
- What?
- Stop.
Hi, it's Ade.
Ma, if this is you,
another gift for the registry
could be a decanter.
Yeah, it's me. Where are you?
May be doing it at our house.
We've only got the one leaf
for 16 people.
Could you do a buffet?
Maybe set a card table up
for the kids?
It's our first holiday.
Ronnie wants us all together.
Ade? It's been 40 minutes.
How long you
gonna stay in there?
How long are you gonna
let me go without a lawyer?
I told you, they're backed up.
We left four messages.
Eight fucking hours
I been here already.
Oh, Jesus Christ, look at me.
You want some coffee?
I can't. My stomach.
I wish you'd think
about our offer.
It's not a bad deal.
I won't wear a wire, I told you.
It's bad enough
how I betrayed him already.
It's not too late
to have a future, Ade.
There are other options.
Don't start with
the Witness Protection again.
You're young.
You love each other.
You both have your health.
Yeah, right.
I mean, living like this is
what's costing you your insides.
I really need a cigarette.
Okay. Come on.
There's no way
she'll wear a wire,
but she think she might be able
to get Moltisanti to flip.
- Why now?
- Problems with Tony.
Christopher hates him,
apparently.
That's confirmed by wiretaps.
And, uh, CI-12 mentioned it too.
Something to do
with Tony Blundetto, the cousin.
- What would Moltisanti want?
- I'm not sure.
He's got some interest
in screenwriting.
I'll put in a call
to Sam Goldwyn.
- You promise her anything?
- No guarantees,
but depending on
what he's offering,
maybe immunity and relocation
for the two of them.
She's got to understand
that if she won't wear a wire,
we can't offer her protection
or keep her surveilled.
- I explained all that.
- Tell her she's got
till 9:00 a.m. Monday
to bring him in,
or we turn her over
to Long Branch PD.
Ton', you got a call.
Jimmy Petrille, uh, Brooklyn.
- Hello.
- It's me.
That tennis match
with those guys?
My guy won.
- Oh, yeah?
- The other one, the son.
- He dropped out.
- What, he got hurt?
Nothing like that.
- It's settled, that's all.
- All right.
Little Carmine's out.
He's dead?
Seems like him and Johnny
worked out a deal.
I knew he'd cave.
He's a fucking pussy, that kid.
Johnny Sack, boss of a family.
Time was it would've been great
for us to have John as the boss.
Smart as a fucking whip.
He used to be a pragmatist.
Some people are better
at being number twos.
You thought John
had an ego before?
Forget it now.
Hey.
You sleep?
A little.
So where the fuck you been?
Christopher, we need to talk.
I asked you a question, Adriana.
I know.
There's something
I need to tell you.
It's that fucking Bobby DeMarco?
No.
Please, Christopher.
I gotta get through this.
About a year ago...
more maybe,
I-I-I-I don't know...
I was arrested.
For what?
What are you talking about?
For drugs.
Where, at the club?
Remember my friend Danielle?
She set you up?
She was an FBI agent,
Christopher.
She lied to me.
They wanted to arrest you too,
Christopher.
I was just trying
to protect you.
They said all they wanted
was some information,
and they would leave us alone.
I didn't tell them nothing,
I swear to God.
Just license plates,
some other stupid shit.
They wanted me to wear a wire,
but I wouldn't do it.
But now there was a murder,
Christopher,
and they know about it.
At the club,
Matush and some other guy.
I tried to cover it up,
but I had no choice.
They've been filming us
in the parking lot.
We're dead! you know that?
What did you do, huh?
How could you
fucking do this to us?
I fucking loved you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh...
Oh!
Oh, my God!
What are we gonna do?
Careful here, my son.
What I do for friendship.
Hello.
T, it's me.
You awake?
Look, I know you're mad, okay?
Ton', I'm sorry.
When I heard about
Angelo, I just--
Don't fucking say it.
Not on the phone.
I know. I won't.
What should I do, Ton'?
I'll tell you what not to do.
That's come back around here.
I know.
I know, but...
my kids, my boys.
Don't worry about that.
I'll look after them.
Yeah, well, that's why
I'm calling, you know,
to ask if you'd--
Sure. Why not?
Anything else I can do for you?
I don't know what to say, cos.
I'm leaving you with a real pile
of shit in your lap.
Hello?
The night you went away,
you know, 17 years ago,
I told you that I got jumped
by a couple of shines.
That's why I didn't show.
That was all bullshit.
I got in a fight with my mother,
and I passed out.
What do you mean?
I don't know. It...
it was like a panic attack.
I went down
like a house of cards,
and I cracked my fucking
skull open.
Why are you telling me all this?
Because I felt guilty
about it all these years,
like it was my fault
you went away.
Anyway, now we're even.
So the casino,
all that shit you did for me
is 'cause of that?
You just take care
of yourself, all right?
You too.
Hello?
Gerard, it's me.
He just called.
Give me a sec,
I'll dump the line.
You got a pen?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, go ahead.
He's at Roy's.
It's a business.
Kinderhook, New York.
That's upstate.
Yeah, I know where it is.
Thanks.
Hello?
Oh! Uncle Pat.
So how's life
at the old folks' home?
I don't like the people here.
Do you know what time it is?
Come on, I thought
you were a night owl.
Did I hear a rumor
there was a problem
up there at the farm?
Ah, the goddamn developer.
Some environmental crap.
They can't start the demolition
without some special permit.
And the house is sitting
there empty,
damn it.
Remember that...
that time at Lake George,
how you loved it?
We could live someplace
like that, maybe.
You could start writing again.
I could do my memoirs, finally.
And we'd have a fireplace
like you like too.
We could never come
back here, Adriana.
I don't wanna come back.
I just want you.
You couldn't even see
your mother again.
You want some eggs?
I need to clear my head.
You didn't even sleep.
This is a lot to process,
Adriana.
I gotta think.
I'll be back in a little while.
Stay, wait.
I'm just gonna get cigarettes.
- I'll be right back.
- Smoke mine.
Don't smoke.
Next you're gonna want a vodka.
What?
Come on.
I love you, baby.
I love you.
NPR's Margot Adler reports...
Hello.
- He wants to do it.
- Great. When are you coming in?
A couple of more hours. We're
just getting some things together.
That's not what we said, Ade.
Please, if I push him
he'll say no.
I know how he is.
I'm serious, Adriana.
You've got till 1:00.
Hello?
Yeah, it's me.
Look, everything's okay.
Jesus, I don't even know
how to say this.
It's Christopher.
He tried to commit suicide.
Oh, my God, is he all right?
He's fine.
He was up by Ramapo.
He apparently took some pills.
And this trooper found him in
a bathroom of this diner,
and they brought him
to the hospital.
His mom's on her way
up there now.
Did he say anything to you?
I mean, did he appear suicidal?
- No.
- Are you sure?
Because his mom said he's
very upset about something.
Anyway, I'm on my way
up there now,
and I'm gonna send Sil by
to pick you up then, okay?
- Jesus Christ.
- You know he's been drinking,
so he's probably fighting
that heroin urge again.
Anyway, Sil's on his way.
Okay.
All right.
I'll see you up there.
♪ If you ever want to get away
From California ♪
♪ Maybe in another life
You'd like to stay ♪
♪ And the devil may call you
When he thinks it's time ♪
♪ You know that
He'll be knocking ♪
♪ If you're still here ♪
I'd stop to eat,
but I don't wanna
get to the hospital after Tony.
I'm not hungry.
They'll keep him
a few days, maybe.
Observation. Do some tests.
Who knows?
♪ Just get in a car now ♪
♪ And take off and drive ♪
♪ Don't wait too long ♪
♪ 'Cause you're almost there ♪
He's a strong kid...
Chrissy.
He's tough.
Very resilient.
Why are you crying?
He's gonna be fine.
♪ No right, no wrong
You're selling a song ♪
Oh, no.
Oh, no. No, no...
- Come on.
- No! No, please!
Where are you fucking going?
- Come on! Come on!
- No! No!
Fucking cunt!
Please!
No!
- Come out of there.
No! No! No!
No!
This is long-term parking only.
Due to increased security,
cars being reclaimed
in less than 14 days
must be left in lots L, M or N.
This is long-term parking only.
Due to increased security,
cars being reclaimed
in less than 14 days
must be left in lots L, M or N.
This is long-term parking only.
The King of New York!
Congratulations.
Thanks, Tony.
You deserve it.
I want you to know
this is the last time
we'll meet like this.
It's undignified.
Okay.
So, what's the word
on your cousin?
I think I know
where he's holed up.
And?
I know this has to be done, John,
but I'm asking you now
as a friend.
Let me handle this myself.
I can't do that, Tony.
You can do whatever
the fuck you want, John.
You're the fucking boss.
I choose not to, then.
I want your promise
it'll be quick.
I'm not gonna lie to you, Tony.
I don't have to.
Phil's gonna do it.
And he'll do it his way.
John...
this is me now.
Come on.
Anything else?
No.
You know what, John?
I'll give you undignified.
Go fuck yourself.
You and Phil and whoever.
My fucking cousin.
Hey.
You all right?
Some funny shit.
The fuck is wrong with you?
I snorted a little H.
I know, but...
I can't stand the pain.
I loved her.
Fucking pain, huh?
You think you're alone in this?
It was a judgment call.
She sounded okay.
What's the status on Moltisanti?
Last seen yesterday, he was
leaving the Bing with Tony.
- Should we bring him in?
- That'll get us nothing.
She really could have fled.
She could be in China by now.
How should we handle the other
thing, the Nieves murder?
We have the terror possibility.
Take it over
from the Long Branch PD.
Well? What did I say?
Is it beautiful?
Yeah, it's a gorgeous
piece of land.
And with this view,
it's well worth 600,000.
The surveyor's coming
on Tuesday.
- You all right?
- Yeah. Yeah, me?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
♪ It couldn't have happened ♪
♪ To a better man ♪
♪ It couldn't be ♪
♪ Different than it was ♪
♪ And you're wrapped
In my memory like chains ♪
♪ Oh, I say that
The flowers will ♪
♪ Always be there in my heart ♪
♪ Like an old-fashioned movie ♪
♪ With all of you
Playing the part ♪
♪ Wonder if I'll ever ♪
♪ Be so unafraid ♪
♪ To walk to a river ♪
♪ And turn around again ♪
♪ And you're wrapped
In my memory like chains ♪
♪ Oh, I say that
The flowers will ♪
♪ Always be there In my heart ♪
♪ Like an old-fashioned movie ♪
♪ And I'll never
Forget your part ♪
♪ I'll never Forget your part ♪
♪ Stand up on that stage ♪
♪ And tell us what
You've been feeling ♪
♪ Before you started to fade ♪
♪ You gave me something
To believe in ♪
♪ And that's the best thing ♪
♪ That anyone can give ♪
♪ And you're wrapped
In my memory like chains ♪
♪ Yeah, you're only
A memory now ♪