♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon In your eyes ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
You were right.
Forensics has signed off on him.
The body can be released.
Phil, why don't you wait until
they fix him up over there?
I promised our mother I'd see
him like we knew him, Jimmy,
before they put on
all that pancake and shit.
Your funeral
director's car is here.
I'll go down and meet them.
John, how long I gotta wait?
Tony Soprano
left to his own device
is never gonna give up
that fucking animal Blundetto.
Philly...
An eye for an eye?
This is kind of fun.
But if I was you,
I'd dump this job.
I'd go to Italy.
This is no way
for a caretaker to live.
Well, a few things have
to settle down first.
My cousin'll send me
the funds to go through Canada.
Italy. Wow.
Nice cousin.
Oh, hey,
thanks for that massage!
My toe doesn't hurt
hardly at all now.
Watch the windows.
Ho!
Excuse me.
How you doing?
- You're Joanne, right?
- Who are you?
Well, we're friends
of your son's.
My son doesn't live with me.
We're from Alcoholics Anonymous.
What's your name?
Well, we're anonymous.
I see his car's out front.
He went to California or Vegas.
I don't know.
California or Vegas.
When did he leave?
Sorry, I have to go to work.
- Where the fuck is he?
- Phil...
Leave me alone.
I had a brother your son's age.
Please let go of my hand.
Where the fuck is he,
you fuckin' cunt?
I'll take that Discman,
and I'll ram it up your box.
Philly, Philly, please.
Please.
It's the guy's mother, Phil.
It's the guy's mother.
Oh, man.
Those jocks are juicers.
They'll do it
just for the free brew.
You're still here?
I'm driving to school.
I don't have to leave as early.
He'll bring some cool people.
- Hey, what are you doing up?
- Snowblower.
It seems to me you are not
sleeping that well, period.
- And look at you.
- I told A.J. to fix this leak
while I was still
living at my mother's.
What's going on with him?
Every time I go by the room,
he's flopped down on the bed,
on the phone.
I am so sick of nagging him.
And if he thinks he's gonna get
into East Stroudsburg State,
he is sadly mistaken.
Look at this kid out there,
the gardener's son.
Can't ask this one
to take out the trash.
Poverty is a great motivator.
You think we gave A.J. too much?
Then you look at Meadow.
Same house, same everything.
- She's doing great.
- She takes after you, maybe.
Don't do that. He's my son too.
Well, I got that appointment
with his coach today.
Maybe he's got a clue.
- Hello?
- In here, Dad.
Hey, there's my little
amaretto cookie.
Clear a place so we can
take a look at these.
They're only
preliminary drawings.
I've got scones
if anybody wants.
Hey, Meadow, take a look at the
house your mother's gonna build.
Well, and Grandpa, of course.
Tony, Ignatz is responsible
for those Normandy chateaux
up on Tisch Drive.
Oh.
Wow, look at that entry.
What is that,
like three stories high?
T?
Christopher, hi, it's Carmela.
- Is Adriana there?
- No.
I was just wondering
what was going on.
I stopped by Fortunoff's.
She was supposed to
get back to them
with a final decision
about her china pattern,
and she hasn't
returned their calls.
Is everything all right?
We broke up.
What?
Why? What happened?
Nothing. She left.
Broke my heart.
Moved out a couple of days ago,
I haven't seen her.
Oh, no,
that's terrible.
- Are you all right?
- She stiffed me on the club.
Never showed up for work.
Place is rudderless.
Oh, my God!
Is there anything I can do?
Nah.
Well, look, I gotta go.
Somebody's waiting for me.
I am devastated.
I wish I could reach her.
Is there a number?
Not that I know of.
Chris, listen,
there's other fish in the sea.
I know. Thanks.
Tony Soprano and Vito Spatafore
talking about
the bus station project.
Adriana La Cerva.
The way we make it,
she's either taken off
or maybe even gotten clipped.
- You hear anything?
- Clipped? Why?
Stepping out on her boyfriend.
I heard she took off.
Any idea where?
How should I know?
He's a dope addict.
Did I already give you that?
If you hear anything,
let me know.
Say hello to Ike and the guys.
T's held up.
He said to start without him.
- All right?
- Yeah. All right.
What can we say about this guy?
The ancient Romans
had a word for it:
"Asshole."
In all candor, though,
we love you, Raymond.
Buon natale. Cento anni.
Cento anni. Salute.
Thank you.
Take that setup away.
He ain't coming.
- Who, Chris?
- South with the geese.
Christopher is the logical
sacrifice bunt.
- To make up for the dead brother.
- I'm his brother-in-law.
You think New York is really
gonna come after you, Bobby?
Fuck do I know?
If you're them,
you want somebody
close to Tony as possible.
And who knows him
better and longer?
Don't think Johnny's not gonna
put a financial squeeze on all of us.
Tell me about it. I'm already getting
fucked with by Johnny's people.
- It's not good.
- All due respect,
I'm willing to die
for a good cause.
But this is bullshit.
There he is!
- Hey!
- Sit down. Sit down.
What's going on?
Vito misto, how are you?
Happy birthday, Ray.
Thanks for coming, Ton'.
I brought these plus...
that's a good one.
Acuto di Soprano.
I serve it at my house.
It's from Avellino.
My grandfather said that some
of my ancestors were winemakers,
but what the fuck do I know?
Thanks, Ton'.
That's gonna be a treasure.
Yeah, well, whatever.
Larry!
The fuck are you doing here?
I though you were
under house arrest.
Fuck them. I ever see that
prison doctor, God forbid,
I'm gonna say, "Hey, fuck stick",
"did they ever show you these
in medical school?
They're called balls."
Good for you!
Listen, I can't stay.
Oh, oh, oh!
I got a meeting I gotta go to.
Got something I wanna say.
My cousin Anthony
went into business for himself,
we all know this,
in a way for which
there is no excuse.
He's got a problem with rage.
He disappointed me, Anthony,
in ways that I can't
even begin to tell you.
And he put us all at risk.
Irregardless,
it's been made clear to me
that if they put
their hands on him,
he will not be dealt with quick.
We're talking torture.
For that reason, even if
I knew where my cousin was,
and I do not,
I would not deliver him
up to them.
I am offering him
the same protection
that I would offer any of you
in similar circumstances.
Now, I know what you're
gonna say. You're gonna say,
"Hey, Ton', I would
never do what he did."
God bless, I hope not.
But we are a family.
And even in this fucked-up day
and age, that means something.
So we are gonna deal with this
as a family, together.
No matter how it affects
anybody personal safety-wise,
financially-wise, whatever.
I see that my nephew isn't here,
and it's important
he lam it now.
It's my desire that you circle
the wagons, you support him.
Until and as such...
Raymond.
I'm sorry I can't stay.
Happy birthday, huh?
Thanks.
Gentlemen, enjoy your dinner.
See you, T.
Thank you.
That was great.
Thought you had Raymond's
birthday dinner.
I left early.
It's nice you're home.
There's chicken parm.
Was Christopher there?
Uh... no.
Did you know that him
and Adriana broke up?
No.
This kid, that's his trouble.
He keeps it all bottled up.
Then they wonder why they get
chemical dependencies.
Oh, man!
Do you think there was
somebody else?
Because there was
this one night,
it was way back, it was
movie night with the girls.
Adriana was very upset,
and she wanted to get
something off her chest.
Then she just ran
out of there, crying.
You know, I'll bet
she was seeing somebody.
You never know about people.
His plans were often startling,
instinctive, spontaneous,
and not infrequently, obscure.
His men idolized him
and had boundless faith in him.
After being promoted in 1916,
he joyfully returned
home on leave
to marry his sweetheart,
Lucie Maria Mollin.
She would be the love
of his life to its end.
Rommel saw the huge
assault on France forming,
and he saw that the new
armored weapon would be...
I still love
this old house so much.
I should do half so good
with my stupid project.
...Panzer division was almost
precisely what he had done
as a lieutenant
during World War I.
He was directing the efforts
of a single tank...
I'm sorry, did you
want to be alone?
No. No.
...but it was blitzkrieg
in its truest form.
It was Rommel...
He had what the
Germans call Fingerspitzengefühl,
which is a sixth sense
of sizing up a situation.
♪ They'll lay you down low ♪
♪ In the easy ♪
♪ And the lips that you kiss ♪
♪ Will say Christmas ♪
Hey.
Claude Rains.
Thanks for doing this.
About 1,500 there.
Should tide you over.
Hey, Sil. Hey, kid.
You want something? Fries?
- Fucking something, this situation, huh?
- Right.
I can't even get down to Milt's,
fence some jewelry.
Everybody with eyes
in the back of their head.
Shit, I was Tony's driver.
It's amazing.
You want me to be honest?
The favoritism Tony still
shows for our fucking cousin,
after what he's done?
What does Tony B.
have on this guy?
And I'm supposed to maybe
take a bullet for the skeeve.
After all your uncle's
done for you,
I need to get into specifics?
Said you went home.
Ah, Trisha.
Just heard her old man died.
I'll give her a call.
Actually, I've been hanging
around on purpose.
I gotta talk to you, Ton'.
About what?
Ton', look, I've been your
consigliere for a lot of years--
Don't go into
a fucking preamble.
Just tell me
what's on your mind.
You got some unhappy
people out there.
No shit.
Not just the young guys.
Talking about guys that've been
with you since the beginning.
Since before the beginning.
- Guys who worked for your father.
- Fucking Paulie, right?
I'm not saying nothing.
Yeah, well, goddamn him.
These guys, Ton',
would do whatever you ordered.
Except in this case.
Don't say it like that.
Forget that Tony Blundetto's
my cousin.
I give him up, we can give
the whole fucking thing up.
Here's where the conversation
gets difficult.
Go.
All due respect.
You were ready to hand him
your cousin a week ago.
So it's not about
standing with the guys
or upholding some rules.
Not really.
Then what's it all about?
Why don't you illuminate me?
It's about you don't wanna
eat shit from John.
You don't wanna bow down.
You told him to go fuck himself.
Which, to be honest,
wasn't exactly appropriate,
considering.
- Oh, is that right?
- All due respect.
What the fuck do you know
what goes on in my head?
I've known you since
you were a kid, Ton'.
Frankly, you got a problem
with authority.
This attitude of yours,
it's a lot of what's made you
an effective leader.
But we all got flaws.
Even you.
Seven deadly sins,
and yours is pride.
All due respect.
You got no fucking idea
what it's like to be number one.
Every decision you make
affects every facet
of every other fucking thing.
It's too much
to deal with, almost.
And in the end,
you're completely alone
with it all.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
This is the course I've chosen,
and those of you
that are not with me on it,
well, that makes me sad.
And it'll be dealt with in time.
You need me for anything else?
Benny, right?
How you doing, Mr. Leotardo?
I'm sitting listening
to WFAN and I go,
isn't that the kid
that used to drive for Tony?
I'm on my way to the hospital.
Well, that's up to you.
No, no, I mean my mom, she...
- Where's your boss's friend?
- What friend?
Don't fuck with me, kid!
Don't fuck with me!
Where's Blundetto?
I don't know! Ah!
It's a start.
Hey, Ton'.
Jesus.
He has a fractured skull.
Is he talking at all?
A little.
Listen, Ben,
I want you to know that...
it's all gonna be taken care of
through the plumber's
union health plan.
I'm gonna see to that.
You know what?
We were talking here,
and I think it's time for you
to get your own customers.
You're getting a little too old
to be beating people up.
- Where's Larry?
- He's staying home.
He's the boy's godfather.
It was him who called, said
he was gonna be with the kid.
House arrest.
All right.
This is fucked up.
What do you wanna do about it?
What do I wanna do about it?
I want that man there
to do something about it.
I want him to give us the okay
to drive over to Brooklyn,
clean some fucking
timepieces over there.
Tony Blundetto whacked
the brother of a captain.
If Tony tried to strike
at them again,
we should take him out.
Look, just give me
that first one.
The Oregonian.
$39.95.
You're sending a fruit basket
to the kid.
He'll appreciate it.
It's for Mel.
The poor guy had a stroke.
You believe it?
He's younger than me.
Melvoin?
Jesus Christ, that's terrible.
That's why I asked you
to come over.
His speech.
He'll sound a little stunad,
probably forever.
But get this:
nine months, maybe a year,
till he can work
a full schedule.
They'll have to postpone
my retrial.
No shit?
The question is,
should I use the stall,
but then get a lawyer
who's more with it?
So, you heard about
this thing with Phil and John?
Bobby said something about this.
That you're
losing money, probably.
I am? How much?
I don't know,
you gotta talk to him.
- John?
- Bobby.
Does John do your collections?
Look, Uncle Jun',
what do you think?
Phil just beat one of my guys
to within an inch of his life.
Next time he's gonna
kill somebody.
What can I do?
It's my cousin.
Did I give them
the office address or the home?
I'm talking to you.
The man had a stroke.
You want it to go
to the wrong place?
It's fruit, it'll rot.
Hey. I pinned myself
into a corner here,
and I don't see a way out.
But he wasn't made, right?
The kid. Phil's son.
It's okay, forget it.
I'm sorry, Anthony,
but I'm fucking nonplussed
with all this news.
Frankly, I don't know.
You're going a little
squirrelly in this house.
Tell Phil.
Tell Phil what?
Where you going?
You wanted to confer with me?
Nah, it's not important.
Make sure you eat a lunch today.
Poor fucking Feech La Manna.
Tony sent the wrong ex-con
back to jail.
You realize I had
an entire container
of imported provolone
coming into that port Saturday?
And fucking Phil and them
put it on a truck,
took it to Westchester
instead of Rahway,
where we always split the loads.
Oh, Jesus.
That shit is liquid gold.
Tony knows what has to be done.
Tell John where to find
Tony Blundetto.
He just won't do it.
As if he even knows
where Tony B. is.
Give me a fuckin' break.
Of course he knows.
It's Christopher I feel for.
Please, huh? Let me
tell you something.
Anthony Soprano is very adroit
at keeping his family
out of the fuckin' frying pan.
Both cousins.
The rest of us...
How's life now
that you're back home?
Carmela?
I had a dream
a couple of weeks ago.
Before I moved back.
A recurring dream.
I see my old coach
from high school.
What happens?
Well, uh...
See, he told me back then,
this guy, he said...
he said that I was special.
You never told me this.
Why now?
What, does everything I drag
in here gotta be a dead dog?
I went to see my son's
football coach.
See, he was starting
my boy and now...
the coach is going
to this other kid more.
What's the reason?
Well, A.J.'s just devoting
more energy to academics.
He's determined
to get into a good school.
How's things on other fronts?
Your cousin?
Well, you touched on something
there that's, uh, not so good.
What's the problem?
I really can't talk
to you about it.
This is very difficult for me,
treating you,
when so much of your life
is closed off.
How many times can I say this?
Look, I'm not trying
to be difficult here.
It's just that it
affects me tremendously,
this trouble he's gotten
himself into, so I'm upset!
Well...
And I care about him so much.
You care about him so much?
We spent hours
getting to the realization
that your feelings
for your cousin
stem from guilt and shame.
Do you remember that?
Do you care?
Yeah, it's just that
it doesn't matter now...
It's just that here we are,
as always, back at square one,
with you going into
high-sentimentality mode.
Sentimentality mode?
We were children together!
Look, it's a lot like
with your son.
Here's what I bet
the coach didn't tell you.
What you wanted to hear most
is that your son is special too.
What I'm saying is,
whatever you wanna do,
vis-à-vis your cousin,
your son, whoever,
own your feelings.
I'm very confused.
But...
we can't talk about it.
It's my mess.
All my choices were wrong.
- How much?
- It's five bucks.
It's five bucks.
Your cup's your admission pass.
Where they from?
Uh... Montville.
They gotta go.
Totally.
- Hello?
- Chiara!
No, you gotta come up
Greenbrook Road.
Patrick said to tell you guys,
some people have bogus cups.
They brought them with them
to get out of paying.
Hey, man, let me see your cup.
It's back in
the Athletic Department.
We're getting ripped off.
You think this is like
downloading music?
That beer is our property
unless you pay for it.
Fucking manners!
Yeah!
Oh, come on.
Speak.
Hello?
Who is it?
Open this door!
Wanna talk to you.
I hear you got some beefs.
You wanna phone everybody?
What the fuck?
I know you said
you wanted it burnt, T,
but the picture moved me.
That's 'cause you knew it
cost me a fuckin' arm and a leg.
It's museum-quality work,
I admit that.
But I told the guys,
a chance to hang
a picture of you on my wall?
I rescued it from the flames.
What's with the hat and shit?
- Huh?
- Don't give me "huh."
You know what it does to me?
To be reminded
of that fucking horse?
I'm sorry, T.
But you never come here no more.
I didn't figure
there'd be a problem.
I never come here no more
'cause they're watching
all our houses.
It's no good for us to visit.
I know.
What, do you and your whores
get a big laugh out of that?
- That's no joke, T.
- Then what the fuck is it?
That's no joke!
That cost me a lot of money
to get the retouching done.
What the fuck you do it for?
And don't bullshit me, Paulie.
Part of it, all right, was to fix
some fire damage on the guy's feet.
But while I was at it,
I also thought,
I don't have
a modern look in here,
so go with something
more traditional.
Something that catches more
of what you're really all about.
A goddamn lawn jockey?
That's not a lawn jockey.
That's a general.
What general? Who?
It's not a real general
from history.
It's you.
Get the fuck out...
♪ And they'll lay you
Down low ♪
♪ In the easy ♪
♪ And the lips that you kiss ♪
♪ Will say Christmas ♪
♪ And the miles
That you traveled ♪
♪ The distance ♪
♪ So believe no lies ♪
♪ Dry your eyes ♪
♪ And realize ♪
♪ That surprise ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la
La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ And we'll send you
Glad tidings from New York ♪
♪ Open up your eyes
So you may see ♪
♪ Ask you not to read
Between the lines ♪
♪ Hope that you will come
Right in on time ♪
Speak.
He's at 146, Route 9A,
Kinderhook.
Skip.
How's it going?
- Hey.
- Hey, Ton'.
We got you your bialys
and coffee.
Johnny Sack called for you.
Called a couple of times.
He seemed to be upset
about something.
Good bialy.
Any time, boss.
Catch you later.
Take it easy, Ton'.
What?
It didn't solve a thing.
- It's over, John.
- The fuck it is!
He's beside himself now.
The best thing for him,
for you, for all of us,
is to put this thing behind us
and get back to business.
How the fuck is that
supposed to happen?
It's something
we gotta talk about.
As a first step,
I'd consider giving Phil
a quarter of my points
in the Bloomfield operation,
which my cousin was running.
I'm at Columbia Pres all day,
my yearly physical.
An hour already, I'm waiting
for this fuckin' doctor.
Then I got bone density
tests, lipids.
Come into the city tonight.
We'll sit down.
No offense, John,
but I got an IQ of 136.
It's been tested.
All right.
Tomorrow morning, then.
My house, 6:30.
- What?
- I'm on a 9:00 a.m. flight to Miami.
- I have to get things in line down there.
- John...
You think I'm gonna
give you ammazz'
with Ginny upstairs?
All right, if you don't hear
from me, I'll be there.
Tony, you and you alone.
I'm not having Phil, nobody.
Who is it?
It's me.
You need to go up to the farm
and pick up your cousin.
I need you to go up there now,
this morning.
It may be over,
but watch your back.
Take him off the premises,
obviously.
He should be buried.
It should be you
that does it.
You got it.
We never got a chance to talk
in detail about Adriana.
I know.
If you let something slip...
if she saw anything...
There was a couple of times
I had her with me
picking up collections.
Esplanade.
The cigarettes.
She was always nosing around.
Did you ever say anything about
Ralph or the Bevelaqua kid?
No.
- Would you remember?
- I swear on my life.
You won't find any of that.
I'm reading,
I'm lifting weights.
I know what you think,
Ton', but you'll see.
I'm gonna prove myself to you.
I only chipped that once,
on the day with her.
She was willing to rat me out
because she couldn't do
five fuckin' years?
- I thought she loved me.
- She's a cunt.
Does no good to think
about that now.
All right, so...
Come on.
He does like her.
Because he told me.
I have heard you talking
in here all night.
- Could you knock?
- You said you would be
finishing your application
for East Stroudsburg State.
You're gonna stroke
out if you can't find
a way to control yourself about all this.
I know.
Hang that phone up.
Call me back later?
I don't know what to say,
you know?
If those applications are late,
you are cooked.
It's that simple.
And I do know this,
because I have raised you
from day one,
you are not gonna like
working at McDonald's.
Could you amp up
the drama a little?
You know what?
I don't like the sarcasm.
And I don't want you around here
next year sponging
off of us, so fine.
I am withholding all allowance
until those applications
are done.
That's not even practical
and you know it.
What's the matter?
He hasn't done his applications.
He isn't getting allowance.
No allowance.
Well, I have $300
of my own money.
How?
Me and Matt put on a party.
Five dollars a person.
We made 600 bucks
after expenses.
- What expenses?
- The band.
Is that what you've been on
the phone about for two weeks?
It may interest you to know
people said it was
the best party all year.
Well, there was drinking,
I suppose?
We just let people
into Matt's house.
What they brought with them
was not under our control.
Do your applications.
Now.
What?
You know, it's interesting.
I was talking
to his college advisor.
Who, Wegman?
No. A.J. got switched around.
Miss Merrow.
She mentioned that A.J.
talked to her once
about what might be good schools
to study event planning.
Event planning?
What the hell is it?
I am not really sure.
Gay, isn't it?
I don't know.
I know you're around
a lot of wealthy people.
Well...
And then he watches that DVD
over and over again.
The one with Mike Myers about...
What's his name?
Steve Rubell, the Studio 54 guy?
Oh, Jesus.
Yeah, but I mean,
you know, it...
Well, I guess, you know...
I don't know.
He's fired up
about something, at least.
So? Go ahead.
Phil has to know that
punishment has been meted out,
and that's all there is.
And that what
we are here for, in the end,
is to put food
on the table for our families,
our sons, the future.
That's what's important.
He doesn't accept that.
His family's smaller by one.
Well, then, my friend,
it's up to you
to make him accept it.
- Me?
- Let's talk, John,
about the 500-pound elephant in the room,
which is that you started
this cycle of bloodshed
when you whacked the girl
Carmine used to fuck.
Lorraine Calluzzo
was not a girl,
and what kind of a man
bangs his second cousin?
What are you,
the frigging cardinal?
Look, you wanna shut down
our joint construction jobs?
Eat K-rations? Fine.
You want Phil to put one
in one of my guys?
That's gonna go a long way
to making you the rich prick
that you always wanted to be.
What do you suggest?
Whatever his legitimate sorrow,
he's got a price.
He wants to provide
for his family.
- And?
- And what?
Meet his price, and that's it.
I don't wanna hear nothing else.
Oh, you don't?
I've paid enough, John.
I've paid a lot.
Maybe I could sell it.
Truth is, we've had discussions.
I gave him the sports book.
Why didn't you say that
right off, you cheap fuck?
Because I don't like it.
He's gonna want consigliere,
or who knows what?
All right,
let's not go backwards now.
These people you run
into who wanna be boss, huh?
They should know.
I told you.
You don't listen, you nut.
It's good...
seeing you again.
I still look forward
to working with you, John.
- I mean that.
- You want a coffee?
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, my fucking Christ!
FBI! Open up!
Oh, my God!
I'm the gardener. I'm the--ah!
Absolutely, put him on.
Anthony?
The feds just hit Johnny Sack.
You heard anything?
I had Gendler on my cell phone
all the way over here.
Jimmy Petrille was a cooperator.
Brooklyn AUSA took down
the whole Petrille crew,
plus Johnny.
Would've reached all the way
to Carmine Senior
if he hadn't died.
Jimmy Petrille?
He's a sweet old guy.
He gave them gambling,
homicides, trafficking.
Eighteen fucking years' worth.
It's a major kreplach,
my friend.
I was fucking there.
- What? Where?
- Johnny's house.
My car's still in the driveway.
I'm walking three miles
towards my house.
No law against parking your car,
unless it's
in front of a hydrant.
I'm not laughing, Neil.
No, of course not.
Anyway, you weren't named in
the indictment,
obviously. It's Brooklyn.
They weren't coming for you.
So, frankly, were I you,
I might actually
consider laughing.
Or rub a hunchback's hump.
Or something.
Yeah.
Be of good cheer.
Call you when I hear more.
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la
La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la
La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ And the businessmen
Will shake hands ♪
♪ And talk in numbers ♪
♪ And the princess will wake up
From her slumber ♪
♪ Then all the knights
Will step forth ♪
♪ With their armbands ♪
♪ And every stranger
You meet in the street ♪
♪ Will make demands ♪
♪ So believe no lies ♪
♪ Then dry your eyes ♪
♪ And realize ♪
♪ That surprise ♪
What happened to you?
Your shoes are soaking wet.
♪ La,
la, la, la La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la
La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ And we'll send you
Glad tidings ♪
♪ From New York ♪
♪ Open up your eyes
So you may see ♪
♪ Ask you not to read
Between the lines ♪
♪ Hope that you will come
Right in on time ♪
♪ Oh-oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ And they'll talk to you
While you're in trances ♪
♪ And you'll visualize
Not taking any chances ♪
♪ But meet them halfway with
Love, peace and persuasion ♪
♪ And expect them to rise ♪
♪ For the occasion ♪
♪ Don't it gratify ♪
♪ When you see it materialize ♪
♪ Right in front Of your eyes ♪
♪ That surprise ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la
La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la
La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ And we'll send you
Glad tidings from New York ♪
♪ Open up your eyes
So you may see ♪
♪ Ask you not to read
Between the lines ♪
♪ Hope that you will come
Right in on time ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ And they'll lay you Down low ♪
♪ In the easy ♪