♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon In your eyes ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
Into the bottom of the eighth.
A very tight game. A hot day.
Oh, it sure is today.
It certainly is, Roger.
Mets tying it up
two to two in the sixth.
Man on second...
Want another super nacho?
No, they been sitting too long.
The cheese is all sweaty.
This guy in the joint,
crazy Rasta fuck,
used to make grilled cheese
on the radiator.
He'd put the bread between
two sheets of paper.
Had a whole system.
What'd you do to your foot?
The other night
in fucking Irvington,
two black guys jumped me
outside a bar.
With half of them locked
up making grilled cheese,
you'd think there wouldn't be
so many around to make trouble.
Should I melt another batch?
Nah. I'm good.
I got dinner in the city.
So, Finn, you got any plans
for the summer?
Going back to Mission Viejo
to surf, or whatever?
Actually, I'm hoping
to stay here in the city.
- How's summer school going?
- It sucks.
I did summer school once.
You can still have fun.
Casa Carmela? He's looking
at maximum security summer.
Excuse me a minute.
Why don't you cut
your mother a break?
For the record, she's the one
holding this family together
during this current
situation and all.
- Can we get the check, please?
- The young man took care of it.
You paid the check?
I figured since you're always
so, you know, generous,
I should reciprocate.
You're lucky you don't get
your head handed to you.
- Dad.
- Let's get something straight.
- You eat, I pay.
- Mr. Soprano...
No, when you have
your own family, you pay.
Let's go.
Just take the money.
All right, listen, I didn't mean
to bite your head off in there.
No, it's fine.
I didn't mean to overstep.
I just wanted to say thank you.
You're a good guy.
I respect you trying.
And then he fell asleep
right after.
He did call me late
the next morning.
And he sent flowers.
But other than that, I haven't
heard from him all week.
- What'd he say?
- That it was nice, you know.
And it was nice.
He was very sweet, actually.
So, you think what happened
at the party is an overture
Tony wants to get back together?
I don't know. Maybe.
He's dropping A.J. off later.
This is the last thing
I need to get into right now.
Oh, please,
he never had it so good.
Oh, that's him.
You two should talk.
Let me just pee.
So, was your father
in a rush now or something?
No. Said he was tired.
To give you this
and a kiss on the cheek.
Thank God.
That's the last thing
I needed, was to talk to him.
You know who loved golf?
Was Joey Peeps.
May he rest in peace.
Yeah, it's sad when
they go young like that.
When they go?
Come on, huh?
It was Little Carmine behind it.
Payback for that whore
he was fucking,
Lorraine Calluzzo.
You don't know that
for sure, John.
Little Carmine knew how fond
I was of this kid, Tony.
I picked him out of the chorus.
Schooled him those years
he was my driver.
Anything from your cop?
Some homeless fuck
saw a guy limping away.
And then he wasn't sure.
I'll tell you,
I don't know how I'm gonna
get through Joey's funeral.
And forget about Ginny.
Every Christmas, Joey'd send her a
Grandma's of Maine
coffee cake.
Whoa! What's wrong?
You all right?
Is it his heart? No.
It's this fucking weather.
Sudden changes.
Fucks up your
respiratory system.
Come on. I got you.
Get some electrolytes in him.
We got you. Come on. That's it.
Sit down. Good, good.
That's it. That's it.
You're all right.
The point I am trying
to illustrate is that
of course no one wants
all-out conflict.
But historically,
historical changes
have come out of war.
Far as I'm concerned,
it's a new day.
All old treaties
and ways of doing things
are null and void.
Exactly.
And the Joe Peeps thing?
Where does that leave us?
When you've had
a quadruple bypass like I did,
it gives you a lot
of time to think.
The only thing Johnny
understands is force.
But the fact is, though,
we pissed on a bees' nest.
So, what's the other option?
Roll over?
We could've had a sit-down.
The other captains, maybe.
This isn't the UN, Angelo.
I won't let what happened
to my father happen to me.
God forgive me,
but you may be a stronger man
than your dad was.
The fundamental question is,
will I be as effective
as a boss like my dad was?
And I will be.
Even more so, but until I am,
it's gonna be hard to verify
that I think I'll be
more effective.
I just talked to my parents.
They offered me
a JetBlue ticket home.
No economic relief.
What did the lady at student
placement say?
I never went down there.
Why didn't you?
This economy? Hello?
I mean, even the crappiest
McJobs aren't there.
Besides, I wouldn't want
to take away a job
a minority could have.
Just... It doesn't cool
anything anyway.
Leave it.
Don't open the window.
The garbage reeks.
Why do we want to be
in New York anyway?
It was supposed to be fun,
remember?
Summer before the big push
of grad school?
You could go out to Jersey,
sleep in comfort.
Is that what you want?
No.
All I know is, I cannot go home
and live with my parents.
I graduated.
I mean, maybe I should
go back out.
I can work as a PA
for Josh's dad.
At least I'd earn some cash.
You could come out for a week.
Wait, wait, wait. What?
He's a photographer. I told you.
He does major magazine ads.
BMW. It's pretty cool stuff.
- Is that what you want?
- No.
But at least I'd have money.
Your thing with models.
- There's no models.
- What?
It's interesting work.
As a career, actually, I mean...
Josh's dad saw my shots that won
the prize in high school.
Said they were
"solidly unsentimental."
What are you talking about?
Just blow off dental school?
You haven't taken
one photograph in a year.
You bitch every time
we're at a party
I ask you to take a snap
of me and my friends.
Look, I'm just saying...
I gave up junior year abroad
- so we could be together.
- I know.
And I wanna stay here.
I could come out west with you.
But I have to blow off
the law center.
- Is that what you want to do?
- I don't know.
Do you want me to come out?
If you want to.
No, you need to say.
Maybe we should stay out there.
You could transfer to UCLA.
Fuck it.
It's roasting in here.
It's 10:30.
We can still get into a movie.
What do you want to see?
I don't know. You say.
No, you.
Hello?
Mrs. Soprano.
Lee Nieman returning.
Oh, hi, great, thank you.
The reason I called, I gave your
secretary the broad strokes.
You're in the middle
of a separation,
your original attorney retired.
Right. Bob Greenberg.
At any rate, I'm thinking
it's time I move forward
with the divorce proceedings. Uh...
Mrs. Soprano, I'm afraid
I'm gonna have to cut you short.
As far as handling it,
I'm afraid I have to
recuse myself.
What do you mean? Why?
Actually, your husband
had been in to see me
for a consultation last year.
- My husband hired you?
- No.
But based on a prior meeting,
the code of professional
responsibility
precludes me
from representing you
because of that consultation.
But he met with Greenberg too,
and he was willing
to represent me.
Well, Mr. Greenberg
would've found himself
in a bit of ethical soup
had he actually moved forward.
See, I don't understand this.
Why is my husband so picky?
He talked to seven or eight
of the top divorce attorneys
in New Jersey.
Well, you can probably
figure that maneuver out
for yourself.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
I understand your frustration.
If you like, I can
recommend a colleague.
Someone your husband
hasn't contaminated.
Well, okay.
According to Johnny Sack,
the kid's brains
were splattered over the seat.
Joe Peeps?
Couldn't have been
too much to clean up.
I heard the hooker
he was with got it in the chest.
Must have been silicone
everywheres too.
Why you always try and top me?
You took the air right out of my
whole fucking punch line, asshole.
Anyway,
Joey Peeps' mom's a widow,
she's in a wheelchair.
Johnny's taking care of the interment.
That shit there.
So I'm thinking we should
pick up the headstone.
Jason, get into it.
I'll call the marble guy.
- What's up, guys?
- Frank.
Frankie.
Talk to you outside?
Give me two.
What's up?
Turns out somebody got a look
at the guy that did Joe Peeps.
All they got so far
is he's got a bad limp.
Huh. Long John Silver, maybe.
Where the fuck
do you get the balls?
I am bending over backwards
trying to stay neutral,
paying for fucking car seats.
And you're out there acting
like a fucking free agent.
And don't look at me
like I'm a fucking jerkoff.
Because I'm sick of you
leaning on this cousin thing
and that bad hijack,
like you can
do whatever the fuck it is
you want to do,
'cause you went away that
night and I didn't!
You're the one
keeps bringing that up.
I'm fine with it.
First of all, for the record,
I had nothing to do with this.
- Don't fucking lie to me!
- Even if I was,
would you really wanna know?
That'd just be another problem
for you with Johnny, right?
Look, I know you're not
earning what you expected.
And you got the twins,
and Nancy.
You're a capable guy.
Your mother let it slip
one time.
You got an IQ of 158.
- She told you that?
- The week you got tested.
All the fucking nuns
were raving about it.
Lot of good it did me.
I had high hopes
when you got out.
Yeah?
Look, a guy like you...
brains, balls...
if you'd fucking
be straight with me,
I could use all that.
Put me in, coach.
All right, we got the casino
on Bloomfield Avenue
above the hardware store.
Carlo's guy was running it,
but he just got diagnosed
with the Hodgkin's.
- That's mine?
- Yeah.
A lot of fucking money there.
And I'll see what I can do
about getting you
straightened out,
opening up the books for you.
It's long overdue.
Huh?
So I solved a major
problem business-wise.
Put a very good piece
of manpower to work.
My cousin Tony.
You mentioned how close
you two are.
You know, when we were kids, they
used to call me Tony Uncle Johnny,
and they'd call him
Tony Uncle Al.
Right, yes.
You told me all that.
Anyway, he's a very smart guy.
He's got an IQ of 158.
Do you put a lot of stock
into that number?
Why, are you gonna tell me it's bullshit?
'Cause I took that test,
and somebody gets a 158,
well, they know a few things.
So we can assume you think
he's smarter than you.
Honestly, I think
he's smarter than you,
the way you keep shitting
on the test.
But I'm no gabadotz myself.
This was a good move.
Carmela and I slept together.
What was that like?
It was nice.
It was very...
erotic.
She was wearing that perfume
that she wears.
Poor thing was starved for it,
honestly.
I'm the only man
she's ever been with.
Did you discuss it?
Nah, I left before she woke up.
How come?
'Cause if she woke up
and I was there,
it would send mixed signals,
you know.
I'm not sure that's the best...
Yeah.
No. Tell him I got fax machines
coming out of my ass.
And would you characterize
the separation thus far
as amicable?
It's barely civil.
Yeah, there are moments
when old habits kick in.
And, you know, feelings.
But he is definitely
not the person
I want to spend the rest
of my life with.
Fair enough.
As for the assets.
You've given me your tax returns
and investments here?
The house is in my name.
Not the boat.
That's the Stugots, is it?
Yes.
I'm a little concerned
that the returns
don't really reflect everything.
There is other income.
There's a lot more.
Unreported income?
Yes.
And this other income,
is it from an illegal stream?
No, of course not.
But he does deal in cash,
my husband.
The carting business.
I see.
- Is that a problem?
- I handled a case once
where the husband owned
vending machines.
I used a forensic accountant
to reconstruct his finances.
In less than a week,
he outlined 11 years of income.
And we're talking coins.
Hey, you. Busy day?
I dropped off an application
at the Cineplex on Broadway.
Stopped by my dad's.
Looks like he got you a job
working construction.
Construction?
That's awesome.
It's in Jersey, though,
so you'll have to take
the PATH train.
Fine, no problem.
But the most I ever did, though,
is, like, help my dad paint.
He said you don't
need experience.
You'll be a laborer
or something.
Pays like 20 bucks an hour.
Holy shit.
How is that even possible?
You believe these fucking
Blue Jays?
Last inning, I screamed so loud
my wife thought
I was having a heart attack.
Why, what happened?
Burrell got shelled.
It was beautiful.
- What are you, a Met fan?
- Padres, actually.
- Padres?
- I'm from California.
I gotta go make my collections.
Stick with the Angels.
The Pads haven't had
a team in 20 years.
What are you talking about?
They were in the Series in '98.
Yanks in four. I was there.
Hey, Shaggy,
grab a bucket and some Lysol.
Scrub off my tires.
There's fucking dog shit
all over by the entrance.
I'm supposed to be
picking up scrap.
You'll be picking up your teeth
in another second.
Hey, DeTrolio,
you need something to do?
Get fucking lost!
Come on, guys.
Go!
Before it sets in the treads!
Oh, my checks come in yet?
I don't know.
I didn't see the girl.
If she ain't got them,
send the kid, Meadow's friend,
when he's done with your car.
Who Meadow?
What are you talking about?
Meadow Soprano.
That's her boyfriend.
There he is!
I can't find any Lysol.
Don't worry about it.
Why didn't you tell me
you were dating my niece?
Here.
You take her someplace nice.
Make sure you tell her
it's from Uncle Paulie.
Thank you, I...
That's really nice.
Here. Give me that shit.
Paulie!
Come here.
Get the hose.
Sorry I'm late.
You been waitin' long?
Not really.
Yeah.
So to what do I owe
this pleasure?
Well, I don't know
if you're gonna see it that way.
I have asked you to lunch
to tell you that I'm filing
for divorce.
I hope you brought
your appetite.
Why don't you give us a minute.
Oh, that's nice.
Invite me to a public place
so you could ambush me.
What, you think
I won't make a scene?
Spare me your outrage, Tony.
Accept the fact that I am
moving on with my life.
Moving on?
That's what you were doing
after the party last week?
I think you and I both know
that didn't change anything.
First of all, we're Italian.
We don't believe in divorce.
We believe in
the nuclear family.
Will you listen to yourself?
And despite your best efforts...
I have an attorney
who is going to aggressively
pursue my custody of A.J.,
and also an equitable
distribution
of our assets.
Our assets?
I am through trying to get you
to provide beyond the minimum
I need to live.
Oh, so it's fucking money.
That's all this is to you?
After all we've been through,
is it so hard to own up
to anything
beyond that bullshit tax return?
Go stand over there.
I'll call you when I'm ready.
You want money?
How about my 40 grand you stole
out of the bird feeder?
That should be plenty,
you're such
an investment genius.
You want this to get ugly, Tony?
Because these guys
live for that.
Oh, you think I don't?
The only reason
you have anything
is 'cause of my fucking sweat.
And you knew every step
of the way
exactly how it works.
But you walk around
that fucking mansion
in your $500 shoes
and your diamond rings,
and you act like butter
wouldn't melt in your mouth.
And you don't want it
to get ugly?
Too late.
I want what I am entitled to.
You're entitled to shit.
She's ready to order.
I guess we get along.
We're just different, you know.
She zigs, I zag.
That kind of thing.
What's her dad like?
He's always flirting.
He's okay.
A little intense sometimes.
The main thing's
that he's a good person.
So, you guys gonna
get married or what?
Living together's
the same thing.
Uh-uh. I lived with a guy once,
and trust me,
it's not even close
to being the same thing.
What do you mean? Why?
Because.
You could just pack up and leave
whenever the shit hits the fan.
Talk to married people.
That ring, believe it or not,
it's got this kind of,
like, weird power.
So, what happened
with you and this guy?
Phineas, my boy!
Hey.
It's actually just Finn.
So, the Cubbies gave your boys
a shellacking last night.
It's still early.
That's true.
You know who he looks like?
That guy from Aerosmith,
Joe Perry.
- Your boss inside?
- Yeah.
All right.
I'll see youse around.
He seems like a nice guy.
Yeah. They all are, pretty much.
So, you dating anybody now?
It's cute.
It's a lot of money
for not much shirt.
Relax, I'll put it
on my own card.
You're damn right you will.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Ask your father.
He stopped paying my
credit card bills.
Daddy?
You guys looked pretty chummy
in the pool that night.
He went home with Artie.
They helped me clean up.
I have decided to move ahead
with the divorce.
What are you gonna do?
- About what?
- Life.
- I don't know.
- What can I do?
Haven't you ever thought beyond
being dependent on some man?
It's so simple for you, isn't it?
It's simple for everybody who
isn't expecting things
to be handed to them.
Even Finn got a job
working construction.
Good for Finn, then.
There are options in life.
Isn't that what
you always told me?
You have options.
I have a lawyer.
Oh, Phineas!
He was just asking.
How come a dentist?
What's wrong with being
a regular doctor?
I saw this thing on
shark teeth when I was little.
Hey, Phil.
Glad to see you're not exerting
yourself in this heat.
Of course. Now he comes.
Soon as the Jersey tomatoes
are in season,
you can't keep these
New York guys away.
Fuck the tomatoes.
I'll take the 'scarole.
You know my brother Billy?
- Yeah. What do you say, Bill?
- How you doing?
Hey, Felicia? What?
Those cases of toner
come in yet?
Yeah, it's in the trailer.
I'm gonna gas up.
I'll be right back.
Toner cartridges now?
They're not skimming enough
from this job?
Fucking brother sells them
out of his trunk.
- Jesus.
- So, Patsy, the necklace.
How'd it go over
with the goomah?
Beautiful.
With the little emeralds?
She fucking loved it.
First he gave her the emeralds,
then he gave her the pearls.
I got Ebel watches, too.
Earrings, whatever you need.
My girl's birthday's coming up.
Some rack on that girl.
Yeah, if you can get past
the sideburns.
You should talk.
That skank I saw you with?
This girl's fucking moustache,
it must've been like
kissing a fireman.
Well, you ought to know,
sweetie.
Ooh.
What'd you say?
Nothing, what?
We're just breaking balls.
Finn, what time's
that game tonight?
8:00, I think.
I'm gonna take a piss.
Do me a favor, huh?
Hold this.
Oh!
I knew that was coming!
- My eye!
- Your eye?
I'm sorry. I meant to hit you
in the fucking mouth!
Hey, oh.
Gene, Gene, relax.
You okay? All right. Come on.
You made your point.
Felicia, call an ambulance.
Use your own phone. I'm busy.
You been sick all day.
Why don't you take the day off.
What about him? One of these
civilians calls the cops?
What? I think I seen a couple
of niggers running that way.
Oh, yeah. Those two guys.
Need to rest?
You want some water?
You sure?
Eugene Pontecorvo?
He's so sweet.
Sweet? He was like an animal.
Are you gonna eat?
I'm not hungry.
It's too hot anyway.
I told you I was making
dinner tonight.
It's really good chili.
You should've seen these guys.
They were laughing.
It was fucking sick.
I mean, is this what
you grew up with?
What are you talking about?
These people,
your dad's friends.
I never saw one bit
of violence growing up.
What about your dad's road rage?
And didn't you tell me
you had a boyfriend once
who was killed,
shot to death or something?
First of all,
he was killed by drug dealers.
African-Americans, if that
makes you feel any better.
You know, you talk
about these guys
like it's an anthropology class.
But the truth is,
they bring certain modes
of conflict resolution
from all the way back
in the old country.
From the poverty
of the Mezzogiorno,
where all higher authority
was corrupt.
...for the Lord Jesus Christ
will change our mortal bodies
to be like His in glory,
for He is risen,
the firstborn from the dead.
In sure and certain hope
of the resurrection
unto eternal life
through our Lord Jesus Christ,
we commend to Almighty God
our brother Joseph,
and we commit his body
to its resting place.
"Peeps"?
It's a fucking nickname.
Family name is Peparelli.
They're gonna redo it.
Fucking Jason.
He's dyslexic.
What's that got to do with it?
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust,
the Lord bless him and keep him.
The Lord make His face
to shine upon him.
The Lord lift up
His countenance upon him
and give him peace.
In the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit.
- Amen.
Amen.
John. John. John.
Hey. I'm sorry about the stone.
It was a mistake. We'll fix it.
You remember Micky Farrell?
Dock worker,
used to run Port Newark?
Guess who he saw on the
Upper West Side the other night.
- Your fucking cousin Tony.
- So what does that mean?
The same night Joey bought it?
What, did you flip your
Maserati, hit your fuckin' head?
- You two-faced fuck!
- Oh, take it easy.
You wanna yell at somebody,
the man you should be
talking to is right over there.
Fucking cocksucker.
I should fucking kill him
and his fucking wife,
- and your cousin next.
- Yeah, alright.
Come on, let's take a walk.
Calm down, come on.
The fucking gall on that man!
His father must be spinning.
You want my advice?
You go out there,
you shake his hand,
and you put this
fucking shit to bed.
Shake his hand?
Then he kisses the kid's mother?
That's the way it works, John.
You know that.
Sure, that's why
your cousin's here!
You are sincerely mistaken
if you think me or my cousin
had anything to do
with any of this shit.
He was spotted
three blocks away.
By Micky Farrell.
You're gonna believe some
drunken Irish fucking prick
over me?
Have a drink.
- I don't want a fucking drink.
- Have one anyway.
So how's your daughter doing?
She's good.
All right, maybe I'm wrong.
But you haven't been yourself
since the old man died.
Lorraine Calluzzo.
Then you sink this idiot's boat.
That's not
the Johnny Sack I know.
I'm waiting for
your explanation, Tony.
My cousin could not have been
in the city that night
'cause he was with me.
We were looking
for his daughter, John,
'cause she fucking disappeared.
We were upstate, Monticello.
We'd heard Kelly had been living
with some fucking crackhead
up there.
Matter of fact,
we were gonna reach out to you.
See if you could get
some of your people on it.
I swear on my mother, Tony,
if I find out you're lying...
I'm sitting here humbling myself
out of friendship to you, John.
Oh! There he is!
"Three out of four
dentists surveyed."
Hey, how you doing?
Where are you going? Come here.
Okay, settle this.
If they fought today,
both in their prime...
Ali or Tyson?
If you were laying a bet.
Jeez, uh...
I... I really don't know.
He don't know.
It's an opinion.
To tell you the truth,
after the other day,
I really don't want
to say the wrong thing.
You see? This kid's all right.
I should get back.
Ramos'll be on my ass.
Would you forget about Ramos,
for Christ's sakes?
I talked to him.
Sit.
We got the good doughnuts today.
I'm fucking exhausted. I
hardly slept at all last night.
So take a nap.
What are you worried about?
You got any idea the money
in that casino?
And to give it to Tony B?
Guy's back on the street
two minutes,
gets a fuckin' promotion.
Did you even
go to the fucking store?
They're in the freezer
like you like.
Now he's talking about
getting a maid, Tony B.
- Really?
- Guy gets out of jail,
suddenly I'm dog shit
in Tony's eye.
- Chrissy...
- It's true!
Ever since I cleaned up,
no matter what he says,
Tony don't believe
a person can change.
And this asshole
went to a shrink.
Maybe he thinks
you're working too hard.
North Carolina,
plus all that other stuff.
I can multi-task, Adriana.
I'm not a fucking retard.
It's always some shit with him.
Side deals, secret promises.
He's always got an agenda.
What happened to not sweating
the small stuff, huh?
All's I know is,
I used to be number one cousin.
Now I'm being eased aside.
Your whole attitude in general.
And while we're at it,
kindly remember what we said
about interrupting
to ask for things
while I'm on the telephone.
Okay, Mom.
Hello?
It's me.
Hi, what's up?
Dale just told us he figured out
the rest of his life.
You still thinking CIA?
Yeah, fight terror.
Nah, I'm gonna
go to film school.
Me too.
I got to motor.
You don't have to work
for, like, three hours.
He has to sleep a little.
I'll get a ride with Alex.
At this point it doesn't
even pay to go home.
Maybe I'll just crash at work.
Felicia told me where she keeps
a key to the trailer.
Felicia told him.
Uh-oh.
Be careful driving.
All right. I'll see you tonight.
Later.
Bye.
Marone. You sound like
a racehorse pissing in there.
Hey, how's it going?
You know, I never asked you
what your last name is.
It's DeTrolio.
Finn DeTrolio. My arch-nemesis.
You enjoying yourself here?
It's all right.
I keep telling you,
you shouldn't work so hard.
Long hours. This fucking heat.
Plus you came in so early today.
I just do what the job is.
Good.
You're strong.
That helps.
You know you can call me Vito?
Yeah, I-I know.
So say it.
Let me hear you say,
"What's up, Vito?"
What's up, Vito?
Not much, Finn.
Except I got a little
surprise for you.
Two tickets to see your Padres
take a beating
from the Yanks tonight.
Oh! Shit.
Third baseline.
Plus, it's bat night.
That's really nice,
Vito, but I...
I'm... don't know if I can--
Don't pull that "aw shucks"
shit with me.
You're fucking going.
I'll see you under
the bat tonight.
Seven sharp.
And I don't like to miss
the national anthem.
So you're just not
gonna show up?
You love baseball.
What is wrong with you?
I don't like the guy, all right?
Right.
I get it.
Dr. DeTrolio can't hang
with the common folk.
He came on to me, all right?
Either that,
or he wants to kill me.
What?
I saw him blowing
some security guard
in the parking lot.
When?
What are you talking about?
This morning I showed up early.
I didn't wanna
say anything, but...
I'm really afraid of this guy.
Vito Spatafore
is a married man, Finn.
I seriously doubt
he wants to kill you.
Well, maybe he wants
to fuck me and then kill me.
Wait a minute.
Is that why you got out
the suitcase?
I am not going back to the site.
Do you have any idea
the strings my father pulled
to get you that job?
And you just fucking quit?
I'm gonna hear so much bullshit!
So it's all about you, right?
Is that all you can say
whenever it's anything to do
with my feelings?
So you're going back
to Mission Viejo?
I didn't say that.
Why don't you just admit it?
This whole thing...
the fight, the stuff with Vito,
it's really about you
not wanting to commit.
I'm right here.
We fucking live together.
But you got out a suitcase!
It's my process, okay?
Look, you never can tell.
Your process?
About anything, the future.
I was thinking out loud.
Well, not out loud,
but in the action
of getting out the suitcase,
I was thinking.
Thinking of leaving!
No.
Well, yes.
But... I'm still here.
I didn't go.
Fuck you!
Right, great. Fuck me.
There was no abundant
intentionality
in me getting out the suitcase.
I can leave too, you know.
My friend Hunter's in Montreal.
Do I know?
With the French roommate guy
who was all over your ass
the time that we visited.
You don't think you keep
mentioning him
every 24 hours at a minimum?
Because he's thinking
of becoming an oral surgeon.
And you might have had
a new friend
if you hadn't been
so obnoxious to him at the club!
Can we just stop fighting?
You got out a suitcase!
I'll put it back, okay?
Now batting for the Padres...
So it's not about us,
but suddenly you're
talking about options.
Don't paraphrase what I said.
I said this point in our lives
is a transition period
forced on us by external events.
School is over for me.
And next year for you.
These are difficult choices.
What, you'd rather not
have choices?
Thank God for choices.
Stop your bullshit!
It's really simple.
Are we going
to stay together or not?
- If you want.
- That's not what I asked!
- I said I did.
- And then you said,
"How are we going
to keep it together
through four years
of dental school for you
and probably med school for me?"
Well, it's a good question.
But why ask it now?
Tonight of all times?
Are you asleep?
- No.
- You were!
And now you were gonna lie,
like you did about the suitcase.
I did not lie
about the suitcase.
Then what do you call it?
I don't know. I explained it.
Jesus, you should quit
the law center.
You're like a prosecutor
at 4:00 in the morning.
I can't think.
How can you sleep when
we're in the middle of this?
In the middle of what?
All I said was I didn't want
to go back to the job site
and maybe I should go home
until this thing with Vito
blows over.
But you didn't ask me to come!
You went right to the closet
and got out your suitcase!
Jesus Christ!
Look, just stop crying, okay?
Why don't we just get married?
Married?
Let's get engaged.
Really?
Why are you saying that now?
I can't think. It's too late.
It's just something
I feel very strongly.
I was wondering
when I was gonna hear from you.
I never got your statement.
Well, actually,
that's why I called.
We hit a bit of a snag.
What kind of snag?
Well, I put a call in
to Phil Canter a few days ago,
the forensic accountant.
The one with
the vending machines.
Then I didn't hear back
from him.
Suddenly he called
and said he wasn't interested.
So I called another accountant.
And?
Frankly, when he heard
your husband was the defendant,
he demurred as well.
So, what does this mean?
You don't want the case?
Well, as my partners
reminded me,
I do have a full
caseload already.
I probably should have
mentioned--
And you were feeling
so positive.
I woke up this morning,
the depression
just washed over me.
You are dissolving
a 20-year marriage.
It's not my fucking
goddamn marriage, okay?
I had another panic attack.
And I thought
I had this shit beat!
What happened?
Playing golf
with a friend of mine,
and he was...
talking about this young guy
he knew who passed away, and...
I guess I became
overcome with emotion,
'cause they had to help me
off the tee.
It's not the first time
it's happened recently.
I wish you had told me.
Yeah, well,
I wish you'd cured it.
When the attacks
first reappeared,
what was going on in your life?
You had just rebuffed
my affections.
When you actually passed out,
were you thinking about me, or--?
I walked into my house,
and the cleaning girl was
crying on the phone about her cousin
who went off the road in a
Mexican bus wreck or something.
And I remember
just feeling inside
like I wanted
to fucking choke her
'cause it was always
something with her.
Next thing I know, boom!
When did it next happen?
My cousin Tony
was up at the house.
He wanted to borrow some tools,
and they weren't there.
I was inside talking to Carmela
and started to feel that...
...you know.
And it passed.
Your cousin was at your house?
Yeah.
Tony Uncle whatever.
Uncle Al.
And your maid was crying
about her cousin.
And the other day
at the golf course...
my cousin entered
into that, too.
- In what way?
- He hurt his foot.
You were so concerned
about your cousin's foot
you collapsed
on the golf course?
I worry about him.
He's a grown man, isn't he?
Is he in danger
of losing the foot, or--?
Fuck his foot!
It's not his foot!
Forget the foot!
I worry about him. He-he's...
right out of fucking jail, okay?
All right, look...
The reason he went to prison
is he got pinched hijacking
a truckload of Betamaxes in '86.
And they hooked him up on
a RICO, and he got 17 years.
And I was supposed to be there
the night of the jacking.
- I see.
- Oh, you see.
Why didn't you go?
I was jumped by a bunch
of moolinyans.
They were trying
to take my shoes.
I fought 'em off, but they
cut my fuckin' head open,
the fuckin' jigaboo
cocksuckin' motherfuckers.
Okay, forget that.
Your cousin went to prison.
That's tremendous guilt
to carry.
He went to Nam, I was 4F.
And that's the way
our friends look at it.
And that's why you favor
Tony Uncle Al...
In those 17 years,
I did so good.
He lost his wife, his daughter.
No wonder you're having
anxiety attacks.
Yeah.
Maybe if you came clean
with him?
Yeah, well... yeah.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Go on--go on--go on
with what you were saying.
Are you having an attack now?
No. No. I had a huge lunch,
that's all.
It's gas.
What is it, Anthony?
Anthony?
All right,
the night he got pinched
I had a fucking panic attack,
all right?
From my mother, goddamn it!
I didn't even know
what it was then!
All right, just relax.
Focus on your breathing.
Slowly.
It's not that, I just...
I just need some fuckin'
Beano or something.
No, just please, focus.
I've got my medical bag in case.
Black guys.
My ass.
I had a fight with my mother,
and I had a fucking
panic attack!
Okay, forget that for now.
Carmela was supposed to come
over with some fucking yarn
for some bootees
my mother was making Meadow.
She was late.
Oh, what the fuck.
Why go into it?
Close your eyes.
Focus on your breathing.
You want some water?
She was carrying on.
I said to her, I said,
"Carmela loves you.
You know, you gotta understand it,
she's got a three-month-old."
But she kept fucking...
she kept going,
and I started screaming at her.
So I left.
I walked out the door.
I went over to the car,
I opened the door, boom!
Cut my fucking head open.
And your cousin
doesn't know this?
No! I lied!
What am I gonna tell him?
What am I gonna tell
all of them?
I had a fight with my mother,
and I fainted?
That's why I missed the job.
Jesus fucking Christ!
That's a lot
to get off your chest.
I thought I was smart,
and that's why I bumped him up
and protect him.
Turns out I'm just
a fucking robot
to my own pussy-ass weakness.
He's also a capable person.
You okay?
You know, sometimes what happens
in here is like taking a shit.
Yes, okay.
Although I prefer to think of it
more like childbirth.
Trust me.
It's like taking a shit.
Hello?
Mom? I'm engaged.
- What?
- Finn proposed.
- We're getting married.
- Are you sure?
I mean, that's wonderful, honey.
I'm just so surprised!
I...
He's gonna finish dental school,
though, right?
We're both finishing school.
We're not getting married
till we have our degrees.
This is so exciting.
I can't wait for you to
meet his parents.
Well, we'll have to
have a party.
He's using his graduation present
to buy me a ring.
That is so sweet.
I told him he shouldn't.
Oh, my God, I'm gonna cry.
Yeah.
♪ If I were a carpenter ♪
♪ And you were a lady ♪
♪ Would you marry me anyway? ♪
♪ Would you have my baby? ♪
♪ If a tinker were my trade ♪
♪ Would you still find me ♪
♪ Carrying the pots I made ♪
♪ Following behind me? ♪
♪ Save my love
Through loneliness ♪
♪ Save my love for sorrow ♪
♪ I'm given you My onliness ♪
♪ Come and give your tomorrow ♪
♪ If I worked my hands In wood ♪
♪ Would you still love me? ♪
♪ Answer me, babe ♪
♪ Yes, I would ♪
♪ I'll put you above me ♪
♪ If I were a miller ♪
♪ At a mill wheel grinding ♪
♪ Would you miss
Your color box ♪
♪ Your soft shoe shining? ♪
♪ If I were a carpenter ♪
♪ And you were a lady ♪
♪ Would you marry me anyway? ♪
♪ Would you have my baby? ♪