♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned
Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Every night it's the same ♪
♪ I hear your heart
turn cold as rain ♪
♪ I know that
you'll be gone again ♪
♪ I hear the front door close ♪
♪ You say you got
to go downtown ♪
♪ I guess there's
someone else you found ♪
♪ So why you're
still comin' round ♪
♪ Heaven only knows ♪
♪ Heaven only knows just why ♪
♪ Lovin' you
should make me cry ♪
♪ Make me feel
like I could die ♪
♪ That's the way it goes ♪
♪ Heaven only ever sees ♪
♪ How love's made a fool of me ♪
♪ I guess that's
how it's meant to be ♪
♪ But heaven only knows ♪
A.J.!
Jesus, Meadow, chill out!
Inevitably, Sukanya,
what goes in must come out.
And these people now
being released from prison
are the same ones who were jailed during
the big Mafia crackdowns of the 1980s?
Seems like yesterday,
doesn't it?
For years we heard
how law enforcement
broke the back of the mob.
Well, they've served their time.
"It's the old never-ending battle
against crime and corruption,"
Sukanya, to quote Superman.
So what do you
think is gonna happen
with this infusion of new blood?
We could be looking at a period
of potentially violent power struggle.
They gotta paint everything
the worst, these TV newspeople.
- How long till dinner?
- Any familiar names?
In New York, the only old-style boss
still in place is Carmine Lupertazzi.
He'll soon be rejoined
by Angelo Garepe,
his former consigliere.
Also Philip Leotardo,
long-time Lupertazzi captain.
Can you help me here?
Crush some ice?
I'll be right there.
New Jersey's a better case
in point, Sukanya.
You've got Michele "Feech" La
Manna, released just this week,
a man greatly feared
and respected in the '70s.
Amen to that.
Similar situation with
Anthony Blundetto in that
same Jersey crime family,
the Sopranos.
Let me see how he looks.
Once known as Tony B.,
still is, as far as I know.
Twenty-eight years old when
he went away. A rising star.
Thought to be the central
suspect in the car bomb killing
of Thomas Gilardi
and his driver.
That's the best picture
they could find?
- He was a fox.
- Will you pipe down?
- We're tryin' to watch here.
- It's my house, Tony.
What are you watching?
Go call your brother for dinner.
- Bobby!
- Be nice to have him back, huh?
- Your cousin?
- Missed the shit out of him.
...the older you are,
the more you're entitled
to eat, as they would say.
Hi, sorry.
Where the hell you been?
- Your mother didn't send anything?
- She wasn't even home.
Her and Aunt Ro went
out to dinner, I think.
Everybody sit!
Now, please.
This is great of you, Aunt Jan,
keeping the Sunday
dinner tradition going.
Can you get the roast
out of the oven?
- Canned clam chowder?
- Go sit, goddamn it.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
My wedding ring.
- Go strap on the bag, Ton'?
- Yeah.
So, would you say this is
an interesting point
in the history of the Mafia?
I'd say we're looking
at a great year
for crime reporters, Sukanya.
- Anthony!
- What?
I wanna say hello.
Wait, can you stop a minute?
- How was dinner?
- Fine.
- What'd you have?
- Roast beef.
Did your father pick up his mail
when he dropped you off?
No, he didn't come in.
He was tired.
He said he just wanted to go to
bed. Listen, I'm trying to practice.
I see you didn't bring the power vac
in from the pool house like I asked.
And why does that even
have to be done?
I mean, Grandpa's still gonna
have to lift it into his truck.
I don't want him to have to
drag it from all the way out back.
♪ It's so nice to have
a man around the house ♪
You should've thought
about that before.
What did you say?
Go out and get that vacuum, now!
What did I just say?! Go!
Ah! Mommy!
Oh, my God!
Mommy, help! Mommy!
Mom.
Mommy.
A.J., be quiet, don't move.
Mommy?
Mommy!
Get Dad's gun!
It's all the way
in the dining room!
Hey, go away! Go!
Hey!
Get outta here!
Go!
It's kind of hard when
you're here only for a short time...
- How's the olive loaf?
- You know what I like?
- I like the Gulden's Brown Mustard.
- Are you leaving?
Yeah, I got a overseas call
comin' at home.
Finish your sandwich,
at least, first.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, no.
- Sheesh.
Could be the same one
from Willow Drive.
God. The most densely
populated state in the country,
- and still this.
- Gone.
He went through your neighbor's
garbage, though, the Kalchiems?
It's been goin' on all over.
If my son had been alone...
You're not gonna want
to put your trash cans out
until as close
to pick-up time as possible.
You hear that?
Also, put ammonia
or bleach in the container
and on the lid.
I posted a notice
for your neighbors.
If this had been a category two,
injury or serious
property damage,
we could set traps,
but not for this.
- God.
- You should've busted a cap in his ass
- with Dad's rifle.
- It's illegal to discharge
firearms within
the borough limits, son.
- You're gonna call Dad, aren't you?
- No.
The great percentage
of them don't come back.
If he does, call us.
Oh, do you have
bird feed back there?
Ah, duck food.
Yes, my husband's.
It's probably
what attracted the animal.
See, the corn's gotten damp
and aromatic.
You're gonna wanna tell
your husband to put it inside.
Right.
Setting up the equipment
is a complicated affair.
Video cameras
with built-in recorders...
Than the car that he qualifi...
- Hello.
- Mmm.
I'm Dr. Lowenstein.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Go back.
What?
- Come on.
- You're kidding.
No, go back, please!
Why don't you come in?
- I like Nolte.
- Why didn't you tell me last night?
I'm sorry. That's a long
story. Let's just skip it.
And I'll try to think
of a better one.
- What's bothering you?
- Global warming. Acid rain.
The national debt. Never
even know what's goin' on.
Look at her nails, totally real.
Let's face it, Lowenstein, women
are more devious than men.
One of my therapists
was a woman.
Too bad you didn't get
all your talkin' done with her.
You expect a man
to be a tower of strength.
Then when it turns out
he's got a few weaknesses
and some insecurities,
what do you do?
You turn around and,
goddamn it, you betray him!
So you feel that
your mother betrayed you?
Oh, God, I hate
this Freudian crap.
And it's not your job to listen
to my problems anyway!
And if you don't mind,
I'd like to go.
You're free to leave
anytime you want.
Good!
Goddamn shrink.
- Who was I kiddin'?
- What are you smiling at?
- I was a champion.
- Nothin'. I don't know.
You have this goofy
little look on your face.
- Come on.
- ...until Susan Lowenstein came along.
Her questions makin' me
as dizzy as her perfume.
- Jennifer Melfi?
- Yes?
So we open the fuckin' trunk,
this suffocatin' Russian
cocksucker pops up!
He's still alive!
We lead him through the snow.
This asshole's shiverin'.
I mean, he's wearin' fuckin' pajamas
and slippers in like eight-degree weather.
Hey!
- Ho! Here he is.
- How you doin'?
- Fellas?
- The B?
- Hey, Ton'.
- Radio on the way in.
Another fuckin' incident
at the airport.
Fuckin' assholes.
I gotta make a couple calls.
Anyway, he starts runnin',
the Russian. Boom!
I'm tellin' you, the top of his head
came off like a fuckin' bad rug.
What a beating we had
to give this prick.
- Oh, Marone.
- Where's he now, you think?
Who the fuck cares.
Right, Chrissy?
- Who the fuck knows?
- Poor bastard.
Never would've happened if
Paulie hadn't initially overreacted,
but it's one for the books.
What do you mean overreacted?
You choked him
with the lamp, Paulie,
or we could've got Silvio's
'scarole without havin'
to spend the night
in the fucking open.
You let him jab you with
that shovel was the problem.
Lets his guard down.
We would've caught up
to the prick
if you didn't lose
your fuckin' shoe!
Wait, you lost your shoe?
You didn't tell us about that.
"Chrissy, please,
don't leave me out here."
You little cocksucker!
I covered your ass with Tony
about that whole thing,
and never a word
of fuckin' thanks, ever!
Always playin' that
blood-relation card.
- Tony's little favorite.
- Fuck you!
- What?
- Come on!
Come on!
What the fuck?
That was a good story, damn it.
Tellin' you right now,
it's finished with us.
- Goodbye, Dr. Melfi.
- See you next week.
- Hello?
- Like the flowers?
And, yeah, before you ask,
I am takin' the medication.
How are you, Anthony?
It's been a long time.
I'm great, actually. You?
Thank you for
that beautiful arrangement.
I see you haven't lost
your sense of humor.
Ah, you gotta have a sense
of humor in life, right?
- You taught me that.
- And how is life?
Good, good. Well...
I'm separated, me and Carmela.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Don't be.
Well, I always thought
I saw some good things there.
Two healthy kids.
Other than that...
Look, the reason I called,
I'd like you to
have dinner with me.
Since we're not
in therapy no more,
and I'm a bachelor again...
That's very thoughtful of you.
Unfortunately, because of
our prior clinical relationship,
- I just can't do it.
- What, eat?
- You must be a toothpick.
- You know what I mean.
See, I knew you were gonna
say somethin' like that.
I can't, Anthony, I'm sorry.
You know, I waited
a respectable period or whatever
before makin' this call.
Well, then you realize yourself
there's something not
quite right about us dating.
No, I'm not undeterred by this.
We will talk again.
- Thank you for the flowers.
- And the detergent.
And the detergent.
Of course, what's wrong with me?
I don't know,
but we'll find out.
Leave it to Dr. Tony.
- What's the matter?
- The bear! Stay there!
Oh, right, lock the door.
What do you think,
he's gonna wipe his feet too?
He'll smash through the glass.
Now, where is that guy's card?
I don't know.
You have reached Fish and Game.
If you know the extension,
press it now.
Unbelievable.
Hello?
For hunting and
fishing licenses, press two.
You get a letter
from my cousin in the can?
Yes, Officer Zmuida, hi.
Yes, Mrs. Soprano
from North Caldwell?
We had the bear
in our yard the other night.
- What the fuck?
- You're the guys with the pool, right?
- Yes, it came back.
- Was anybody hurt?
- No, thank God.
- Property damage?
No. No, property damage
either I could see,
but I didn't really
wanna go out there.
Oh, one of those
eastern black bears?
We should be up
in about an hour.
Yes, that'd be great.
Okay, we'll be here.
All right, see you then.
Jesus Christ,
when did this happen?
The first time Sunday night,
and I saw it again just now.
A.J. didn't even mention it to you when
you two went to the game yesterday?
No!
I have to warn the Cusamanos.
They keep Esterhaz chained up
along the side there.
That bear will rip him
to pieces.
Cusamanos weren't home.
Got the machine.
Well, I don't see Esterhaz.
Why didn't you call me
when this first happened?
I called the cops.
They called Fish and Game.
What, are you tryin'
to prove you're independent?
This isn't Little House
on the fucking Prairie.
- Those things are dangerous.
- The ranger, whatever...
said it was your duck food
out there that attracted it.
I never heard
of that happening before.
Trapper Joe over here.
- We didn't find a spoor.
- I was just tellin' the gentleman
the animal still doesn't meet
the parameters for removal.
- Oh, jeez.
- So, when somebody's leg is gone...
Problem is, it hasn't
really threatened anybody.
Sorry.
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, hold on a minute.
You and your pal buy some new
lanyards for your whistles.
Oh, we can't accept that.
And we don't have whistles.
Thanks, though.
Ranger Rick's a little light
in the Timberlands, huh?
Everybody's always gay with you.
He's a good-looking guy,
that's all.
I already put the ammonia
on the cans, I told you.
Look, I came here to give you
your money, but...
this bear thing, though,
I'm... I'm worried.
- You and A.J. here by yourselves.
- What can we do?
You want coffee?
Last time it had a weird taste.
The coffeemaker is shot.
The heating element
is corroded, I told you.
That's not the problem. You
don't need another one of those.
Last month, it was
the upstairs toilet. Basta.
He goes down the street
to Willow Drive too.
Maybe he'll stay down there.
All right, look, you and A.J.,
you check yourself into a hotel
till this thing blows over.
Here's $1,200 extra
on top of our agreement.
- I'm not going to a hotel.
- Why not?
- I don't wanna break Anthony's routines.
- He'll get a kick out of it.
It's an adventure. And God
knows he loves room service.
Yeah, I'll give him room service.
The end of my foot.
What's with the attitude?
Well, he's an asshole,
that's what.
- So what? It's his age.
- Yeah, thank you, I know.
But you buy him too much stuff,
I think because you feel
guilty about the separation.
Excuse me. It wasn't my idea.
There is more than one way
to ask for something.
Could we please not?
Spend $5,000 on a set of drums.
But SAT tutor, coffeemaker,
I gotta fight you
tooth and nail.
All I said was I wanna see
statements from the tutor,
or he doesn't get paid!
He's a college kid, Tony,
he's not set up for that.
You worried he's gonna
soak you for an extra pencil?
Oh, rimshot!
What I think, Tony, is you're
trying to make my life now
as hard on me financially
as possible.
- Oh, it should be easy.
- Unbelievable.
What do you think, you're the
only Catholic here, Carmela?
I'm old school.
I don't believe in this
separation shit and divorce,
even if my wife was going after
some fuckin' immigrant!
Yet you are modern enough
to use a cell phone to call Italy
and every other fucking
place to threaten the guy's life.
Oh, that's right.
Certain people
see him, he's a dead man.
He had coffee here, Tony,
that's all.
And now the coffeemaker sucks.
How you like them apples?
You don't wanna stay at
a hotel, you suit yourself.
This is Anthony.
Could you call me
at 973-555-1299?
I'm thinking maybe I gotta come
back, you know, for therapy.
- Smells good, Feech.
- Yeah?
- You want a taste?
- Nah, I'll wait.
No offense, kid, but don't look
to me like you do a lot of waiting.
Just like his old man, huh?
Lot of changes
since you went away, huh?
Twenty years. Marone.
You know what the biggest
change for me is?
Broads shaving their bushes.
I went over to Silvio's, it's
like the Girl Scouts over there.
I think I'll
let this simmer a bit.
Must be different in the can
now, not like the old days.
Fuckin' animals.
It's all about
setting a precedent.
First day there,
I walk in the mess,
I'm wearin' a puss,
a fuckin' scowl.
I look around...
My nephew.
Right in the middle of my story!
There he is!
The man, the legend,
Feech La Manna.
Hey, my God, look at you!
You big galoot!
What'd you, go straight
from the joint to Earl Scheib?
Look at this fucking tan.
You close the cellar door
when you came up?
It's like the Bowery Boys in
here with this house arrest here.
Code words and secret passages.
- He's in the middle of a story.
- When isn't he?
Hey.
It's day one, I'm in the mess,
I look around
and I spot the biggest,
blackest motherfucker
that I can find.
Everybody's looking at me, and
I walk right up to him and I say,
"What the fuck are you
looking at?"
He says, "What?"
I said,
"You heard me, motherfucker.
What the fuck
are you looking at?!"
With that, I hit him! Bam!
Right across
the fucking coconut!
He goes down, I'm on top
of him. Everybody around!
He gets some shots in!
Everybody's going fuckin' crazy!
The screws, these guys,
everybody!
"Motherfucker!"
From that time on...
Nobody so much as looks
at me cross-eyed!
Well, welcome home, huh?
- Welcome home.
Reason I wanted to see you,
Junior, Tony too,
now that I'm out, I'd like
to get back in the game.
What'd you have in mind?
You know me,
I'm an entrepreneur.
Get my shy going, sports book,
whatever you say.
As long as you don't step
on anybody's toes.
Me? I'm Fred Astaire.
What's this Feech tells me, you
got a bear up there at the house?
What's it, on fucking CNN?
No, it's just
that your wife's up there,
and the kids,
your ex-wife, whatever.
It's just that wild animals,
they're dangerous.
- People talk.
- What people?
- Who?
- I don't know.
What am I supposed to do,
go up there personally
and set fucking bear traps?
We're separated, for chrissake.
So where's the dinner at?
Oh, I forget the name.
It's in the car.
Who's gonna be there?
What are you,
on the school paper?
Guys. Business.
- You got any cash?
- Some.
Hand me my bag.
- That's all you got?
- It's like $400.
I'm low man tonight,
I gotta pay for everybody.
You know, this is fucking
ridiculous, Christopher.
Why should you get stuck all the
time? You should make Paulie pay.
What, I make the rules now?
Guy's a captain.
I know,
but when he was in jail...
All's I'm saying is if you
get the extra responsibilities,
you should get the benefits too.
You're right.
I'll say hello
to the guys from you.
Benny, hi! Come on in.
Tony sent me.
He says he wants somebody
stationed in the yard.
He's worried the bear
might come back.
What? No, I don't want this.
Well, we'll switch off,
me and Paulie Germani.
This is silly.
I'm gonna call him.
Actually,
it's not that silly, Mrs. S.
If it was my family, I'd wanna know
there was a male at the house too.
What can you do about it
if it does come back?
Tony said you
should unlock the closet
and give me the "shkoopet,"
he called it.
- Oh, for God's sake.
- We'll call the Fish and Game too.
It's just I'll have
the weapon in case.
He's just worried about you,
that's all. And Anthony.
Well, okay. I don't know. I...
You're very nice to do this.
Nice got nothing to do with it.
Stay inside. You don't have to sit
out there like A Fistful of Dollars.
Tony said not in the house.
I got my little Sony in the car.
You want something to eat?
We were just about to sit down.
Nah, I'm good.
I just stopped at Tio Pepe's.
This freaking olive oil.
The food's drenched.
That's the reason it happened.
As far as fucking bears
are concerned,
I say get rid of them all.
They had their turn,
and now we got ours.
That's why dinosaurs
don't exist no more.
- Wasn't it a meteor?
- They're all meat eaters.
- Meteor, meteor.
- Take it easy.
Gentlemen,
whenever you're ready.
- All right, are we set?
- Yeah, sure.
What are you doing, you ready?
I gotta make a pit stop.
Eh, you forgetting something?
You get it. I got the last one.
Here, baby,
have some more cheesecake.
The other thing with bears is,
if you're ever chased by one,
run downhill.
Some reason, they can't do that.
It's the moss.
They attack when you're
having your period too.
No, no, that's jungle cats.
- So can we go?
- Hold your horses.
- What's goin' on, we ready or what?
- Yeah.
- Fine, I'll get it.
- Gimme the fucking thing.
- I said I'll get it.
- Enough. It's done.
- $860.
- What?
You heard me. That's what
you owe from last night.
You said you got it.
I only got, like,
a hundred bucks on me, anyways.
Then get the rest by tonight
or you start paying points.
I'm thinking of going
for the acupuncture.
What, your shoulder again?
Those long drives.
It's already tender.
Next time, we get you
out there, Angelo.
After 18 years in the can,
I'm just happy to be outside.
What, they don't have
a golf course at Leavenworth?
Still a smart ass, this one.
Carmine, you all right? You
barely touched your egg salad.
Too much gherkins.
- You smell that?
- What?
Burning hair.
I smell cut grass.
Any word on your cousin
getting out?
- Who's your cousin again?
- Tony Blundetto.
Oh, yeah, good guy.
Right, right.
He was my best buddy inside.
So you gonna give him a party?
When he gets home, get him laid.
What's the matter, Carmine?
- Carmine?
- Jesus Christ!
- Carmine!
- Call an ambulance.
- Yes, sir.
- Is he breathing?
Get that egg salad
out of his mouth.
Hurry up!
Lupertazzi residence.
Carmine, it's John.
Hey, John boy,
how's the weather?
Look, I got some bad news.
Your dad's had a stroke.
- Oh, my God, how bad?
- There's some paralysis.
It's too early to tell yet.
They're doing everything they can.
- Is my mom there?
- I just called her, she's on her way.
We're over at St. Vincent's.
Anything, John, anything he
needs. I'm on the next plane.
Sad, this shit, huh?
I wonder if I can smoke in here.
You know, I haven't forgotten
our arrangement last year,
you leaving me
in the lurch like that.
It was the right thing
to do, John.
Taking out a boss? Come on.
- Even still.
- What do you want, an apology?
Fucking Whitman Sampler, what?
Boy, imagine if his
fucking speech is affected.
Poor bastard.
So when you're up at the house,
who comes to visit? Anybody?
Mostly Rosalie Aprile,
Sil's wife.
Who calls on the phone?
Most of the calls
seem to be for Anthony.
So...?
Look, the real reason I'm here
is to confront you
in a positive way
about taking our relationship
in that other direction.
Why did you have
to be underhanded?
I don't find
that appealing, frankly.
I was gonna ask you out
for coffee or something,
but I didn't think you'd go.
I'll pay for the hour,
that goes without saying.
Forget that.
I was listening
to that guy on TV, Dr. Phil?
And he was talking
about a similar situation,
and he said that you could
if you wanted to.
There's no set rules. It's
basically about malpractice,
and you probably
couldn't get sued.
That's not the point.
Look, I was thinking
about all kinds of moves.
Buy her a piece of jewelry.
Pay the guy to close down
the restaurant
where she eats lunch
and hire a mandolin player.
This is the place
where we've been
most honest with each other.
And that's the way
I always liked it.
So that being said,
if you don't like me personally,
or the cut of my jib,
or my face, or whatever,
then the matter will end here,
and I will never ask you again.
You can be honest.
I like you, Anthony.
And, no,
you have a very nice face.
Working on the weight,
too, by the way.
Good.
Explain to me, okay,
why this is a matter
of such importance to you.
There must be plenty
of women out there.
You're different
from what's out there,
not to mention being
drop-dead beautiful.
My training teaches me to go
fairly quickly
to the idea that
what you really want
is to come back to therapy.
Jesus Christ Almighty,
come on, will ya!
Your marriage of 20-something
years has collapsed.
No doubt there are issues
with your children.
Why can't I do something
that's just for me for a change?
It would be for you.
All right, well, I want you.
And not just for
the smart things you say.
I want... I want your skin.
I want your mouth.
I want your eyes.
You project all these
qualities onto me.
You don't know me.
This is what happens
between doctor and patient.
Don't do that.
Out of respect for this office.
You know, forget about the way that
Tony Soprano makes his way in the world.
That's just
to feed his children.
There's two Tony Sopranos.
You've never seen the other one.
That's the one
I wanna show to you.
- Hi.
- Hi. I, uh...
I wonder
if I could use the W.C.?
- Of course, come on in.
- Yeah, okay.
- Is it cold out?
- Yeah, a little, but I got a fleece, so...
I know him. He'll just keep
coming back and coming back.
How to let him down easy, I...
You think it's worth
telling the police?
What? Jesus, Elliot.
I don't want to paint
in somber tones here,
but the man is a sociopath,
unpracticed in not
getting what he wants.
And now, since
the therapy is kaput,
what use are you
to him except for sex?
Thank you, Elliot.
Your depth of feeling is
really quite extraordinary here.
All you could come up with
was this weak borscht
about professional ethics,
because you are worried
about how this thug
will handle rejection.
You know, at first I
did find him a little sexy,
dangerous alpha male.
But as year followed year,
the ugliness I saw, I heard...
You kept him
a long time, though.
There's a mutual sympathy
there of some kind, I guess.
Maybe it's just
the Italian thing.
Sil said you
were looking for me?
Sit down.
This about the Easter baskets?
I don't even know what that is,
and, to tell you the truth,
I don't wanna know.
Now what's this shit
between you and Paulie?
You chiseled him
out of a dinner?
I chiseled him? He said that?
I asked you a question.
Can I say something
in my own defense?
It's not right that
I have to pay all the time.
I've been paying
for fucking years.
You done?
Good.
You pay till I tell you
you don't have to pay no more.
And don't give me that face.
You know how many tabs, how many
dinners I picked up over the years?
I got Richie Aprile,
fat fucking Gerry Anastasia.
Those guys killed me
at Benihana's.
And forget it-- they want a steak,
I put a new wing on Peter Luger's.
Brandy, cigars, champagne.
Could've bought a fucking plane.
I hear you, Ton', but that was
- before inflation.
- Whatever.
I-It's tradition.
It's like in ancient times,
the samurais,
they had these pages, young
boys that did their errands,
washed their clothes,
shit like that.
It's a sign of respect.
Why don't you cheer up?
One day, some kid'll
be paying for your dinners.
Atlantic City loves it's oldies
on Oldies 98.3.
♪ Now that you're gone ♪
So the Pope says,
"Just-a one-a more thing.
She gotta have-a big-a tits."
Oh, man!
- Ah!
- That was good!
You okay, Ton'? You're
being like a little quiet.
Yeah, yeah. I'm just,
I'm full, that's all.
Calm before the storm.
Get him near those
crap tables and look out.
Jesus, I'm stuffed.
I can't remember
the last time I ate this much.
- Sure youse don't want no dessert?
- Not for me.
Nah, I'm good.
Thank you. Thanks.
Enjoy it, girls.
I been enjoying looking
at youse the whole night.
Get some fuckin' glasses.
We gotta go.
All right, I'll see you
over at the $100 table.
Ton', you sure you're all right?
You got a big moose on.
It's a fucking broad,
believe that?
Really? You mean...?
- It's the real deal, I think.
- No shit, huh?
See, the thing is,
we got this
platonic thing going.
We have had for many years.
She thinks that's
what it is, but it's not,
and no amount of convincing
will change her mind.
- So she was a friend.
- Yeah.
They're wrapping up a lobster
roll for me to take to Ginny.
- We'll see youse over there.
- Yeah.
- Anything else, gentlemen?
- We're good.
My friend here'll
take the check, though.
Have a wonderful evening.
Eleven eighty-four. Oh, babe!
I gotta play that number.
Hmm... I'm gonna go wash up.
♪ We're all sensitive people ♪
♪ With so much love to give ♪
I'll tell you,
after a meal like that,
what I could use
is a nice piece of ass.
Who knows, maybe I'll call down,
have them send one up to the room.
Why don't you just fuck
yourself? Save a little money.
- What's your problem?!
- Stop trying to bait me, Paulie!
- You know what my fucking problem is!
- No, why don't you tell me?
You want me to tell you? Fine!
Steaks, three-pound lobsters,
the shrimp fucking cocktails
you made everybody get!
Then on top of everything else, you
send those skanks a bottle of Cristal?
I was being a gentleman,
Chrissy. You oughta try it some time.
Not to mention the Lyonnaise
fuckin' potatoes you didn't even touch!
- What?! I lost my appetite.
- Fuck you!
- Excuse me?
- You fuckin' heard me!
I'm telling you, Chrissy, I don't give
a fuck anymore who you're related to.
Go ahead, Paulie! Go for it.
Your big fuckin' moment!
- You little fuck!
- Excuse me, gentlemen.
Was there a problem
with the service?
- What are you talking about?
- You left me $16, sir.
- Perhaps you miscounted.
- There's 1,200 bucks in there.
That's correct,
and the bill was $1,184.
Assuming you don't tip on
tax or alcohol, 15 percent--
I'm tapped out.
You think this job is easy?
I have kids.
Then go back inside
before you get hurt.
I have a goddamn family
to support.
- Fuck off!
- Yeah, right.
Go piss it away at blackjack,
fucking assholes!
Oh!
What do you gotta say now?
Chrissy, he's fucked up.
Don't they have medicine they're
supposed to take, these assholes?
I don't know.
He'll say we hit him
with a brick.
He's still going, this asshole.
That's my money, Paulie!
How's he doing?
I love him so much,
and I can't do shit.
We're all praying for him.
You know, you were
another son to him.
- Yeah?
- You get some sleep?
- A little, you know.
- Fucked up, huh?
What are you gonna do?
I'm not too worried
about the cops.
Nobody knows us down there.
The reason I called.
Let's bury the hatchet,
you and me.
All this bullshit with us.
- I know, I know, it's stupid.
- Life's too short, Chrissy.
You can't waste it
fighting with your friends.
Look what could've
happened last night.
One of us could've got hurt,
or even killed, for chrissake.
- I know.
- You're special to me, you know.
Always have been.
You, too, Paulie, to me.
We'll split the tab.
- I'm sorry, Paulie.
- I apologize too, kid.
I'll talk to you later.
When you say that, you
make me feel... less than.
Next week, everyone.
Good luck.
I'm going outta town next week.
Okay.
Good night.
Anthony.
- Hello.
- Hey.
A friend of mine had these.
I'll see you next week.
Like I was saying, a friend of
mine had these and couldn't use 'em.
I figured, well, maybe we could.
Tickets. Bermuda.
Lodging at
the Elbow Beach Hotel.
I turned down
a wonderful dinner invitation,
and you think
I'll go away with you?
Well, the guy couldn't use 'em
and, you know, he gave 'em to me.
What do you want me to do,
throw 'em away?
Come on, I'm breaking out
the big guns here.
You're turning me
into half a stalker.
Listen, Anthony, I'm...
I'm not going to go out
with you, okay?
And it's not
because you're unattractive,
or I don't think
I would have a good time.
It's just something
I'm not going to do.
And I would like you
to respect my decision
and just try to feel that
I know what's right for me.
Okay?
But it's not just the
psychiatric ethics stuff, is it?
I wanna preserve
the option for you
that you could always come
back to our work, if you wish,
and that we could pick up
where we've left off.
I don't think you get this.
I want you!
And that's very
flattering to me.
I'm not interested
in flattering you.
I know you're not.
All right, then what is it?
Okay, what is it?
Just help me
understand it, okay?
You know, Anthony,
during therapy I...
I never judged you
or your behavior.
It's not the place
of a therapist to do so.
All right, I get all this.
Go, go.
In a personal relationship,
I don't think
I could sit silent.
About what?
Our values are...
just very different.
- You don't like my values?
- Honestly?
Yeah.
No.
Okay. Like what?
- It's getting late, I...
- No, no, no.
Come on. It's okay, it's okay.
Well, you're not
a truthful person.
You're not respectful of women.
You're not really
respectful of people.
- I don't love people?
- Maybe you love them, I don't know.
You take what you want from
them by force or the threat of force.
I couldn't live like that.
I couldn't bear witness
to violence...
Fuck you!
You're a fucking cunt!
Oh.
How come Benny's not outside?
He just got here,
he's going out.
Where is he?
He's in your office on the
phone with his girlfriend.
Hey, Ton', how's it going?
You can take the night off.
I'll spell you.
No, no, no, Ton', that's
all right, it's okay, really.
I'll take over, okay,
for tonight.
Okay, well... 'night, Mrs. S.
Good night, Benny, thank you.
- You want coffee?
- No.
♪ I'm gonna turn and walk away ♪
♪ There's nothing left
for me to say ♪
♪ It wouldn't
change things anyway ♪
♪ Oh, I suppose ♪
♪ The love I gave
was always true ♪
♪ Well, I don't know
what else to do ♪
♪ And how I'll ever
get over you ♪
♪ Heaven only knows ♪
♪ Heaven only knows just why ♪
♪ Loving you
should make me cry ♪
♪ Make me feel
like I could die ♪
♪ That's the way it goes ♪
♪ Heaven only ever sees ♪
♪ How love's made a fool of me ♪
♪ I guess that's
how it's meant to be ♪
♪ But heaven only knows ♪
♪ Heaven only knows just why ♪
♪ Loving you should
make me cry ♪
♪ Make me feel
like I could die ♪
♪ But that's the way it goes ♪
♪ Heaven only ever sees ♪
♪ How love's made a fool of me ♪
♪ I guess that's
how it's meant to be ♪
♪ But heaven only knows ♪