♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
"♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon In your eyes ♪
- Yeah ♪
- Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- Yeah ♪
- Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- Got yourself a gun ♪
Fuck this. I'm calling Carlo.
Yeah, they didn't show.
The Vespa scooters.
We gotta wait.
Carlo was furious.
His guys waited by
the Hackensack River
all fucking night.
Fucking Vespas
never got in my hands.
This is Port Newark.
Where the fuck
were your longshoremen?
Heightened security at ports,
al Qaeda.
Done, Johnny.
I gotta go.
Nice job, Billy boy.
Carlo was told it was a go.
If it didn't happen,
how come nobody called?
A lot of things didn't happen
that seem like they happen.
Your cousin didn't whack Joey.
The Vespas never got
into my hands.
- Come on! Go, Soph!
- On the ball, Keaton!
Hustle! Hey, Soph is open!
She's open! Come on!
She's gotta be at least 11.
Don't put up with that, Lissie!
Careful with those elbows,
number seven!
Hey, out of bounds!
Out of bounds!
Go, Lissie, go!
They're just a bunch of losers!
Hey, no negatives, you!
Come on, putz, charge the ball!
Charge it!
Foul!
That kid tripped my kid!
That's legal.
She was going for the ball.
- She was not.
- Score!
Score! Come on!
Your kid is out of control.
She's been tripping
and pushing all summer.
Oh, shut up and get out of here.
Don't tell me to shut up!
What, are you crazy?
Oh!
Please. Come on!
- Somebody!
- How do you like it now, bitch?
Her kid kicked my kid. Get off!
- Cost you 100.
- Call.
Sit down. Sit down. Sit down.
I talked to John.
The Vespa scooters came in,
but there was no opportunity
to grab them
because of increased security
at the ports.
Jesus Christ!
The young crowd is crazy
for these scooters.
He owes me half
that fucking load.
- You're not buying it?
- I don't know what to think.
He's getting awfully
fucking cute with his remarks.
All I know is his behavior
at that kid's funeral
was a disgrace.
It's a big part
of my livelihood, that port.
I will say,
very interesting timing, T.
You and John had that
chat at the funeral,
whatever that was.
Suddenly, no Vespas.
All right, I gotta take this.
Whoa, whoa.
Take one of Carlo's guys,
start hanging around
down Port Newark.
Find out what the fuck
is going on.
The property taxes, I know.
Hello to you too.
I thought you should know,
your sister Janice got arrested.
- What?
- In Essex County this afternoon,
an incident of sports rage
among soccer moms
led to the arrest
of a Verona woman
with ties to the Mafia.
Our Gillian Glessner
was on the scene.
What about it, Gillian?
Think that other mother
better go
into the soccer mom
protection program?
Maybe she should, Carl.
It started here
at Summit Avenue Park
during a 9
and 10 year old girls'
club soccer match,
an altercation
between soccer moms
that sent one mother to the
hospital, and one to jail.
Denise McCarthy, a parent,
witnessed the violence.
I just feel so bad for the kids.
Parents taping the match
captured the mêlée.
Somebody!
How do you like it now, bitch?
Her kid kicked my kid!
Charges are still pending,
but we know that
the woman shown here
being taken into custody
is Janice Baccalieri,
sister of reputed New Jersey
mob boss Anthony Soprano.
Guess you could call it
a Mafia-related hit.
Ha ha. We spoke with
psychologist Bela Kakuk.
It's a growing problem
in our society.
Psychologists are finding
that certain individuals
are particularly prone to rage.
Almost any frustration,
inconvenience
or perceived inconsideration
will set them off.
Motherfucker!
Janice, open the door!
- Where is she?
- It wasn't my fault!
My name was all over the
fucking TV because of your bullshit!
It's not that simple, Tony.
Apparently the woman's kid
was picking on Sophia.
Why didn't they
collar her, then?
I am suing the township
for wrongful arrest...
- No, you're not!
- ...and the YSO.
No. No, you're not!
What you're gonna do
is you're gonna call Neil Mink,
you're gonna play it down,
you're gonna pay the fine
and not turn this into
one of your causes célèbres.
Anybody's side but mine.
That bitch is lucky
I didn't kill her.
Well, we know that.
What?
You and your fucking temper,
Janice.
Get out!
This is the end of it.
Tony.
I know this looks bad.
But on the other hand,
she called Sophia her daughter.
I don't give a fuck.
All right, I do give a fuck.
But how many times
I gotta tell you?
Get control of your wife!
Sophia.
Phia?
I'm so embarrassed.
I don't wanna see
any of my friends again.
Well, when you're a parent,
you'll see.
You'll defend your children
like a lion with her cubs.
- You're not my parent.
- What did you say?
I'm here.
And I try to care very much.
Now get to sleep.
You gonna punch me?
Jan, can I talk to you?
Sophia, go to sleep.
We'll talk tomorrow.
I'm exhausted.
No. Now.
What, I don't have
a say in things?
Janice, I think you need
professional help.
I'll be having an extra session
with Sandy, believe me.
Sandy, Sandy. What does she do?
She tells you you were
picked on by your father
and asks you to read
her screenplays.
I think there's
anger specialists.
And I think you should see
a weight-loss specialist.
You don't see it in yourself.
I heard you with Sophia.
Youse were getting along
so much better.
She says one little thing,
and you get nasty.
I'm so sore.
This is not
an isolated incident.
They won't let you shop
up at the corner anymore.
Those coffee beans
were burnt, Bobby.
You tasted them.
Janice, I like a spitfire type,
I told you.
But we can't live like this,
me and the kids.
Like what?
This was a nice house.
Peaceful. I don't know.
There wasn't all this
yelling and tension.
How could you understand?
Your dad was a sweetheart,
even when he had emphysema.
My house, it was dog-eat-dog.
Well, be that as it may,
the past and all,
if you don't go
to these anger classes
they have or whatever,
this with us
ain't gonna work out.
Look out, ladies and gentlemen.
He's rolling. It's nine.
Place nine.
What do you think
he clears here?
Two crap tables,
blackjack, roulette.
You gotta figure
he's grabbing anywhere
from 2,500 to five G's
a night for himself.
It used to be you, didn't it?
Teacher's pet?
Stop making meatballs, Paulie.
I'm just saying.
Now you know
what I went through.
It's the same Gina
had at her wedding.
We should see how it looks
on your face.
Chrissy.
The fuck?
- What's up?
- Hey there, cuz.
- Guess who called me this morning.
- How'd you find me?
- Oh, you're not gonna guess?
- Okay, who?
Our friend with the orchard.
No shit. He okay?
Yeah. Sold the place.
Moving to Florida.
He should.
He's getting on in years.
Oh, shit.
You still got your canned
peaches up there.
I just had the car serviced.
Watch what you say.
I gotta move that shit? Again?
That developer's going up there.
Now, obviously it wouldn't
be good for you or our friend
if somebody opened
the canned fruit.
So you and your cousin here,
you're gonna go there
and take care of it.
I'll do it.
I'm worried about the old guy.
- I told you, I'll do it.
- The thing is,
my old man's got a few jars
up there also.
Could make problems
for my uncle.
It's gonna be a lot of work,
which with Louise around,
can only be done at night.
That's true.
This thing's gotta
be done in two weeks,
the latest.
Bulldozers are coming.
So, what, are you
picking out wedding cakes?
Yeah.
Hope you have better luck than I did.
Why? You didn't like your cake?
I think your luck's
been fucking great,
and listen to you
cursing it out.
What, you got something
you wanna say?
- All right.
- So call me.
Who is this Uncle Pat anyway?
He was a knock-around guy
like Tony's dad,
but they let him retire
to this farm upstate New York.
It sounds funny, but it wasn't.
He had the hiccups
for, like, a year.
Jeez.
Great guy. He had a daughter,
but she lived with her mom.
Us boys each got sent up there
summers when we hit up 12 or 13.
He'd school us.
Did he have the hiccups?
No, I told you, that went away.
What, you think
it's fucking funny?
He almost committed suicide
because of it.
How would you like it?
Where's my Barney's underpants
with the ventilated cotton?
Still in the dryer.
Tell you one thing,
I need fucking Tony B. up there
like I need a third nut.
All this resentment.
He is your cousin.
Yeah? Should've seen him
when I was little.
Him and Tony both.
How they broke my balls,
teased me.
One time, I was spending the
summer up at Uncle Pat's farm,
just like they used to.
I was 11.
They came up, they were
like 19, to shoot guns.
They didn't take me with them.
And when I tramped through
the stickers and found them,
they said I had to be initiated
into a special club
by being tied to a tree
alone in the orchard
for an hour.
I was on that tree till
3:00 in the fucking morning.
Aw.
I worshipped these two guys.
Tony Soprano especially.
When he was by himself,
he used to push me
on my Big Wheels,
he'd teach me curse words.
When he was by himself.
Where's the Tinactin?
Right on the night table.
And here we are again.
Tony B. goes wrong,
and Tony lays a 200K-a-year
cash cow on him.
Christopher,
don't get mad, okay?
I know we kind of touched on it
a couple times,
but you're so unhappy.
What if we left here,
went far away,
and you went
into something else?
- Like what?
- I don't know, like...
Pick up your writing, maybe?
Male modeling.
I'll get back
to the writing someday.
But from a position
of great wealth.
As far as male modeling,
I'd probably be a success,
but I wouldn't want to be
around those fucking people.
I'm a soldier, Adriana.
When are you gonna
understand that?
What the fuck?
- Carmela.
- What?
There's no water in the pool.
Yeah, I had it drained.
The electricity costs a fortune.
I can't afford that.
You're the only one who uses it.
I thought we were getting
along better lately.
So you polluted all the decent
lawyers in New Jersey
so they can't represent me?
You couldn't even play fair.
I'm not the one that wanted it!
Okay, so let's
just pretend that you
weren't begging for it in a
million different ways, okay,
because I am worn out here.
Motherfucker.
He's a nice kid, Finn.
Right?
Right.
We gonna throw them
an engagement party or what?
Well, if we can be civil.
She's so young.
Same age we were.
It wasn't all bad.
Last time, I asked you to
jot down one or two situations
or people that trigger
your anger,
so much so that when
you think about it,
you get angry all over again.
Anybody got...?
Let's give Bradley
a chance this time.
My partner parked me in again.
I couldn't find the keys.
I had to wake him up,
and he starts yelling at me.
Describe the feelings.
I think--
My stepkids do that
all the time.
They leave their bikes
in the middle of the garage,
and if I wanna pull in,
I gotta get out
and move the bikes
with a car full of groceries.
Doris, can't you keep Billy's
bike out of the driveway?
It was a famous commercial
from the '60s.
Bufferin.
Guy has a headache,
and he takes it out on his wife.
Back to Bradley.
I'm trying to get into his
physical sensations of anger.
He saw red. Who wouldn't?
She's right.
I mean, why is he in here?
Why isn't his roommate in
therapy for selfishness issues?
There are always things
out there that are irritating
and annoying
and out of our control.
What we can control
is our response to those triggers.
So people just get a free pass.
The whole world?
I told you about my supervisor,
checking my work
and nobody else's?
I wonder why.
Because you're a minority.
Exactly. That's why I'm in here.
Uh-huh.
You seem angry
about Evelyn's problem.
It makes me mad.
"It" doesn't make you mad.
"You" make you mad.
I come from a biased family,
but I was different.
I put all my faith and my hopes
into the civil rights movement.
I left home and I marched.
And for what?
So they could ride around
in their SUVs
blasting that rap shit,
and you can't say anything
because they might have guns?
Wait a fucking minute.
Who's "they"?
If the shoe fits.
This is fucking priceless.
Okay, let's not
time-travel here.
Let's try to stay
in the present.
Janice, you're angry.
Let's stay with that.
What are your actual
physical feelings right now?
I'd like to punch you
in the face.
Your hands are clenched.
Did you realize that?
You're provoking me
to make a point.
And maybe that's your job,
but I don't like it.
Look at you.
You're not even listening.
- Hello? He's talking to me.
- No.
You and me, we do most
of the talking in here.
The man is trying to say
that those people outside,
they do the thing.
But we're the ones that get
all upset and start carrying on.
That's all he's saying.
The Hudson Valley.
That Legend of Sleepy Hollow
cartoon
scared the piss out of me
when I was a kid.
Would you mind
watching your shoe?
Oh, sure.
It's a $50,000 vehicle.
I don't want it scuffed up.
Uncle Pat's farm?
When you're 12, 13, man,
it's like fucking heaven, right?
Running around in the woods,
driving that tractor.
He made me clear
the brush by the fence
with a fucking scythe, though.
Yeah. I had to do that.
Tony too.
And water his fucking tomatoes
and his basinigol.
Changed, though,
you know, Pat's,
after Louise came
back there to live.
It wasn't just you and Pat
and his great stories.
They used to call me
Ichabod Crane.
Who?
Some very sorry people,
that's who.
The Carmela front?
Did you two ever discuss
that evening you made love?
It was a one-time deal.
I've moved on.
What about the depression?
Your revelation
about your cousin?
His prison sentence?
You were very upset.
Tell you the truth, I haven't had
a lot of time to think about that.
My sister...
She attacked some woman
at her stepkid's soccer game.
You've mentioned
her temper before.
She got charged with aggravated
assault and resisting arrest.
Excellent.
- Let's talk about that.
- What?
- Rage.
- Why?
Depression is rage
turned inward.
Tell me about
the Soprano temper.
Well, the thing is,
it's bad for business.
Clouds your judgment.
John, he always had
a terrible temper.
- John?
- Gotti.
And in the end,
I think it hurt him.
See, we forget
that in the old days,
the ones that came over,
that started this thing,
they didn't get mad.
They just smiled and nodded
and made sure you got it later.
That's the whole
beautiful point.
You know what they say.
Revenge is like
serving cold cuts.
I think it's, "Revenge is a dish
best served cold."
- So, what'd I say?
- But why revenge all the time?
Where does it come from,
this insatiable anger
you and your sister share?
I was wondering how long it was
gonna take for her to come up.
Your mother?
What about your father?
You never saw her
chop off someone's finger.
Told you about that, didn't I?
Yes.
- Oh, Jesus, I wish I hadn't.
- Why?
I mean, I dress up nice
and everything when I come here.
Okay, let's stick
to the subject.
- Which is what?
- Your own intolerance for frustration.
"Thank you for holding.
Your call is important to us."
If it's so important to you,
answer the fucking phone!
- Stay with that.
- It's just a level of bullshit!
Bullshit! Bullshit!
Every fucking new idea
they come up with
that's supposed to make things
better makes things worse.
Okay, right, I agree.
"The center cannot hold.
The falcon cannot
hear the falconer."
What the fuck
are you talking about?
We live in a time
of technological
and spiritual crisis.
But you feel you're above
all of it.
Certainly above any
inconvenience or annoyance.
And if things don't go your way,
instead of being
merely disappointed
or inconvenienced, you blow.
My sister's...
She's taking
anger-management classes.
You know, maybe she's on
the right track.
Is this something
you'd consider?
No.
Well, but I-I-I'll admit
it's not good for me,
all this fucking agitation.
Wears me out.
I'm fucking exhausted
all the time.
Where did we start off?
I don't know.
Depression is rage
turned inward.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh!
This is nice.
For inner-city kids like me,
this was important.
Inner city? You lived next to
the largest shopping mall in New Jersey.
It's over now. She's sticking me
in that home in Florida,
and that's the last
I'll ever see of her.
I'll be right down
the road, Pop.
I got a beautiful condo.
Thinks she's gonna meet
some old, lonely widower.
Louise, it's time for dessert.
I'm getting it.
And do me a favor.
Be as polite as you are
when it's just the two of us.
We know where Chrissy
buried the guy.
But with Uncle Johnny's,
you gotta help us out.
Well...
I'm not exactly sure,
but there was two of them.
The Johnson brothers.
You don't remember where?
It was a long time ago.
We can't excavate
the whole fucking place.
Because you know
what Tony's gonna say?
Let him come up here
and dig then.
Please.
He's a heart attack
waiting to happen.
That's no joke.
Our bodies are 86% water.
His last blood test,
he was 65% zeppole.
When he first heard
the term "pie in the sky,"
he volunteered
for the 82nd Airborne.
That's pretty good.
I learned in recovery
that he's just tamping down
his feelings, T, by eating.
I should talk to him.
It's a shame, you know?
Because he used to be
the funnest guy in the world.
When was that?
He's got the world by the balls,
and he acts like everything's
a big fucking imposition.
Being at the top,
he's isolated himself.
Yeah, it's just him
and his money.
Hello.
Who is this guy, anyway?
My first.
Czechoslovakian guy.
This is the second time
I'm moving him.
Ah!
Come here, you little fuck.
Guys, wait.
It wasn't me...
Help! Please, don't kill me.
What the fuck
are you running for?
The night of the 12th,
there was a ship from Italy
with these containers
of Vespa motor scooters.
I don't know anything
about any fucking Vespas!
We know they got here.
What happened to them?
I don't know. I wasn't here!
Well, apparently he says
he wasn't here.
Who picked up our motherfucking,
cocksucking Vespas?
In two seconds,
this is going up your ass.
It was the guys from New York.
Phil Leotardo and them.
Listen...
Thanks for doing this.
You didn't have to.
Fuck that.
You're my little cousin.
I think I can imagine what you
may be hearing about me,
and what happened in New York.
All I can say is,
there's no truth to it.
I didn't think nothing.
As far as Tony putting me
in at the casino,
I knew people
were gonna resent that.
But I went away for a long time,
stood up for this family.
And you, or anybody,
can think what they like,
but I feel I had
a little coming to me.
Hey, absolutely. I was telling
Benny that the other day.
He was complaining.
And what I said
about Tony before?
You know I love him
like a brother.
I love him too.
We saw the guy down the pier.
John has the Vespas.
To think of how supportive
you were of him.
That whole Little Carmine
fiasco.
It's fucking payback.
Johnny's got it in his head that
somehow my cousin had
something to do with Joey Peeps.
Johnny should be looking
for the real killers
instead of spending all his time
on that golf course.
Whole fucking shipment
of cheese coming in next month.
The imported provolone.
I guess we can kiss
that goodbye too now, right?
Motherfucker!
Carmela.
Hi. What are you doing here?
My son is a senior here now,
isn't he?
We were electing party chairs
for Senior Night.
Oh. Right.
So how are you?
- Fine.
- Because you were pretty upset
when you left,
and I wanted to call.
I began to really
rue what happened.
- I was probably over the top.
- I'm going back with my husband.
Oh. That's good.
All the best.
You don't drink no more?
Clean and sober, 14 months.
Yeah, your mother
has that problem.
Good for you.
That's right.
- What?
- The Johnson brothers' bodies.
I know where they are.
Over by the fence
in the northwest corner,
because that night
I noticed one of my pickers
had stuck a Swiss Colony bottle
upside down
on one of the fenceposts.
And I was plenty goddamn mad
they were drinking on the job,
I'll tell you.
It's still there,
the glass bottle.
- Are you fucking sure?
- Lunch!
Look what I got for you,
Chrissy.
Thank you.
Sandwich?
Oh, you're the best.
- Here, Pop.
- Thank you.
Beautiful.
This is mail from
three fucking weeks ago.
The girl didn't even
show up today.
Why don't you call the service
and get somebody new?
Two classes, she's telling
people how to run their life.
Don't let me stop you from
taking your kids to the rink.
You have every right to be mad
at me, and I apologize.
I know it's bad for the family.
For business.
But I'm working on it.
Yeah, I know. Bobby told me.
So how's that going?
Anger management?
It's the best thing that ever
happened to me.
And it's such a relief
to let go of all that shit.
I never realized
what an angry person I was
and how it fed itself.
So they got you
on tranquillizers?
No.
Basically, it's taking
responsibility for your anger,
and learning to recognize
your feelings of anger,
and that they're just feelings.
You don't have to act on them.
That's just what people want
so they can walk all over you.
A lot of anger
is self-importance.
Self-importance?
Problems with authority.
Dr. Seepman locks the door
promptly at 7:00.
People wig out if they don't
get in, start banging on the door.
It's a big lesson.
I was making everybody
in my life miserable.
Yelling and screaming,
or pouting
and feeling victimized.
But I feel so much better now
about everything.
It's like this great sadness
is beginning to lift.
Sadness?
Yeah.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you.
I am.
Your bid, Chrissy.
You expecting someone?
Ho! There he is!
My God, I don't believe it.
Who's that? Anthony?
What's the matter?
You all right?
God, you're big. Oh!
Look at those shoulders.
Jan sends her love.
And Barb too.
Did you eat?
Louise, don't ask him.
He's a guest.
Just go get him a plate.
Sit down.
You look good.
Feel good.
So how we doing?
Took care of mine last night.
The Johnson brothers
we'll get tonight.
Uncle Pat was like
Johnny Mnemonic.
- Right, Uncle Pat?
- Huh?
We're playing pinochle.
Take a hand.
This is the life, huh?
I'm with you.
Yeah, we were just saying that.
Two... three!
Here's to a job well done.
Salute.
Ah.
This place hasn't
changed much, huh?
Met some pretty nice college
girls the other night, huh, Ton'?
She liked you. Miss Raven-Hair?
Pat seems good, huh?
Louise seems fat.
The human body is 86% water.
But Louise's last blood test,
she was 65% zeppole.
That's a good one.
I knew a guy, when he was gonna
eat Philly cheese steak,
the mayor of Philly would have
to call out the National Guard.
What the fuck's
so funny about that?
Doesn't even make sense.
Well, he's drunk.
Him? No way.
He's in recovery.
Oh.
Well, if you recover
your fucking balls,
give us a call.
We might like to hang out.
No, seriously, it's not funny.
He's a 12-stepper, right?
Yeah. You know that.
That's right.
Maybe he can take another
couple of steps out the fucking door
so we could have some fun?
Come on, don't get pissy now.
He's just having a joke,
that's all.
Sobriety's hard enough without
having to get mocked for it.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Why don't you have
a fucking drink, will you?
'Cause you're driving
everybody crazy with this shit.
The fucking
higher power yammering,
and the sweets,
and the Key lime pie and the...
Jesus.
Order a fucking bullshot,
will you?
Do me a favor.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
I was being a jerkoff like that.
- No, no, look, it's just...
- No, no, no, no.
You know, come on.
Hey, you're doing
the right thing.
You're doing the right thing.
So how do you like his car?
Schwarzenegger's.
Pretty fucking great, huh?
Oh, yeah. The Humvee.
Yeah, yeah, it's nice.
Kind of steep, though.
Come on, you told me
you didn't pay for it.
- You gave the guy a hum-job.
- For the Humvee.
Maybe he'd like to hum me.
Who, a friend of Bill over here?
Fucking wits over here.
Bill? I'll say.
That? That's not a bill,
that's a beak.
You know...
that was you he made
that joke about,
the zeppole content.
On the way home,
we can drop him off
at Beakskill.
Well, if beaks could kill,
that one certainly would.
You know, I could've called you
Ichabod Crane, but I didn't.
What the fuck's he talking
about? Ichabod Crane?
Nothing.
Well, here's
to the Johnson brothers,
whoever the fuck they were.
- Johnson brothers.
Back pain? Is your pain...?
...case, and are
ergonomically des...
Port Newark in New Jersey...
...but one example.
Six million containers
enter U.S. ports every year,
yet fewer than 2% of them
are opened and inspected
by U.S. Customs.
It is physically impossible
to check every container
without essentially
stopping global commerce.
But what keeps officials
from sleeping at night,
they say,
is that terrorists
could use shipping containers
to smuggle in a weapon
of mass destruction.
It is within the capabilities
of Islamic fundamentalists
to track a container
with a Global Positioning System
and detonate a nuclear
or biological weapon
- hidden inside.
- Son of a bitch.
In fact, a terrorist could
even use a shipping container
to smuggle himself
into the country.
There he is.
What I saw on TV last night.
The ports are wide open.
Government's not doing shit.
Louise, where's
my butter substitute?
Right in front of you.
Didn't you hear what I said?
I knew it was bad,
but you realize there's,
like, seven million containers.
The news team put radioactive
shit in one of them.
- It wasn't even detected.
- Please, my ears.
Sit down. Sit.
Come on.
I made eggs.
Could've been a goddamn A-bomb.
- You want coffee?
- Yeah.
Fucking terrible nightmares.
Yeah, it knocked the edge right
the hell off your appetite.
What's the matter with you?
No, it is some scary shit.
Not my problem much longer.
Speaking of scary shit,
was that you
- in the bathroom this morning?
- Oh, yeah.
I thought they already
dropped a biological weapon.
All right, I gotta go.
What you talkin' about? I thought
we were gonna go do a little hunting.
- You hear the turkeys this morning?
- No, I gotta take off.
Uncle Pat.
Take care of yourself.
Be careful of
the alligators down there.
All right, tough guy.
♪ Don't tell me to stop ♪
♪ Tell the rain not to drop ♪
♪ Tell the wind not to blow ♪
♪ 'Cause you said so ♪
Hey, Ton'!
What'd you do,
knock over a roadside stand?
My uncle's farm.
Less than a hundred miles
from here.
It's like a whole
different world.
The bullshit really
falls away up there.
Hear about that shit with
the ports now?
I know customs agents
are bad for us,
but antiterrorism-wise,
they're doing nothing.
What's it gonna take,
a fucking nuclear bomb?
They caught one of these
al Qaeda cocksuckers
in one of these containers,
trying to sneak in there.
Thank God they caught him.
There's enough they don't catch.
You gotta realize,
the administration's
busy, though, too,
handing out noncompetitive
building contracts
to their friends.
Hell, we can all
understand that.
- Mm-hm.
- We're fuckin' sitting ducks here.
The only thing between
our homes and Port Newark
is a chain-link fence.
They get a nuclear bomb
in a container,
we're fucking dead.
That's why you gotta
live for today.
- What'd you say?
- I said,
that's why you gotta
live for today.
Talking about annihilation,
you stupid fuck.
Your kids, my kids,
burning into cinders.
I can't even think about it.
You stupid...
You can't even fucking
think about it?
Think about it now?
How about now?
Take it easy. Take a walk.
Get some air.
Take a walk.
Take a walk outside.
- Take it easy.
- Sorry, everybody.
Come on. Take it easy.
- I wake you up?
- Yeah.
I just come from the hospital.
They said you wanted to know.
Oh, how's he doing?
Hey.
Sorry. It's all right.
Doctor has a peel at 1:00.
- Hi.
- How you doing, hon?
- Call me?
- Yeah.
Bye.
See you later.
That the dermatology nurse?
- Yeah.
- Nice-looking.
Well, they get all the best
skin treatments half-price.
So, what'd they say?
He's gonna be okay, the kid?
He's big, strapping.
He'll be all right.
But he's got some
hearing loss, one ear.
Looks like
it could be permanent.
Skip, the poor fuck knows
he should keep his mouth shut.
Go over there.
You make sure he gets the best.
Thing is, Ton',
he's quitting the Bing.
And he told Sil, he goes,
"And I'd appreciate
if Tony don't come visit me."
He don't wanna see you.
I told him watch his mouth.
These things happen, T.
That's why I don't like
to talk politics.
You did?
Please, I couldn't
believe it myself.
Well, are you going
back with Tony?
No.
Then why'd you say it?
I don't know. It just came out.
Asshole. He was gonna
call me. Did he?
Jerk.
Come in!
Hey.
Uncle Pat.
Oh.
Where's A.J.?
He's not coming.
You lose them to their friends
for a little bit,
but he'll be back.
Hi, Uncle Ton'!
- Hey.
Soph?
- Before dinner?
- Half?
Thank you.
Mahatma Gandhi over here.
Nice.
Hey, Tony.
- Hey.
- I thought I heard your voice.
- Hello?
- Good game on later.
I think we're
on the do-not-call list.
Oh, no, we're happy
with our service.
Are those telemarketers?
Just hang up, hang up!
We're just sitting down
to dinner.
Okay, please don't call again.
Thank you. Thank you.
Bobby! Soph! Come on!
It's a G5.
It's got a 64-bit architecture.
They speak a different language
now with these computers.
I saw a show on computers,
how the prices
have dropped so low
that you can buy one
for $500 at Costco
that's more powerful
than the one
that they used to put
the astronauts on the moon.
Good eggplant, Jan.
Yeah, delicious.
Mm.
I wonder where Harpo's
eating his Sunday dinner.
What?
Just wondering
what Harpo's up to.
- Who's Harpo?
- That's Hal, Janice's son.
- You have a son?
- You didn't tell us that.
You know that song
"Harpo's Song," by Phoebe Snow?
'Cause that's the song
you named Harpo after, right?
He's half
French-Canadian, Harpo.
All right, Tony, make fun
of a boy because of his name.
I wonder what's
French-Canadian for,
"I grew up without a mother."
"Sacré bleu!
Where is me mama?"
You son of a fucking bitch!
- You son of a bitch!
- Come on!
Daddy!
Easy, easy, easy!
- You miserable fuck!
- I don't got a right to ask?
- I'm the boy's uncle!
- Easy, easy.
Easy. Easy.
I hate him, I hate him.
♪ I won't take all
That they hand me down ♪
♪ And make out a smile
Though I wear a frown ♪
♪ And I'm not gonna
Take it all lying down ♪
♪ 'Cause once I get started
I go to town ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm not like
Everybody else ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ I'm not like everybody else ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ And I don't want
To live my life ♪
♪ Like everybody else ♪
♪ And I don't want
To be destroyed ♪
♪ Like everybody else ♪
♪ And I don't want
To get a job ♪
♪ Like everybody else ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm not like
Everybody else ♪
♪ So, what are you? ♪
♪ I'm not like everybody else ♪
♪ You say, darling
You know that I love you true ♪
♪ And I'll do anything
That you want me to ♪
♪ I'll even confess
All my sins ♪
♪ Like you want me to ♪
♪ But there's one thing
That I can't do for you ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm not
Like everybody else ♪
♪ What can I say? ♪
♪ I'm not like everybody else ♪
♪ What you say? ♪
♪ One more time ♪
♪ I'm not like everybody else ♪
♪ Like everybody else ♪
♪ And I don't want
To live my life ♪
♪ Like everybody else ♪
♪ And I don't want
To be destroyed ♪
♪ Like everybody else ♪
♪ And I don't want
To get a job ♪
♪ Like everybody else ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm not like
Everybody else ♪
♪ What did I say? ♪
♪ I'm not like everybody else ♪
♪ Like everybody else ♪
- Everybody else ♪
♪ Everybody else ♪