♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon In your eyes ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ I was all right ♪
♪ For a while ♪
♪ I could smile ♪
There he is.
Black Jack Massarone.
I saw this,
and I thought of you.
- Ho! Look at that.
- Guy's local.
He makes them as part
of a program for disabled vets.
A little gift to show my
gratitude for all our work together.
Thanks.
- Look at those guys, huh?
- Mmm.
They had some times, huh?
You know, we're finally gonna cut
the ribbon for the museum on the 22nd.
They're gonna ask me
to make a little speech
on the challenges of
contemporary urban development.
Thank you.
Somethin' for you?
Oh, I'll have what he's having.
Listen, my buddy
in city plan check says they
just pulled a permit to turn the
old bus station into a mixed use.
The thing is, Zellman still
hasn't given me a number.
Has he said anything
to you about another bid?
Oh, we don't talk much.
Take your hat off. Relax.
Yeah, I just started
on the Rogaine.
Listen, you think
maybe you could ask Ron
if this falls
under the same arrangement?
Kinda soggy,
you wanna know the truth.
Tony, this
is federal redevelopment.
I'll look into it.
- So, a speech, huh?
- Yeah.
At the Museum of
Science and Truckin'.
I just wish my mother
could've seen it.
Well, wherever she is,
I'm sure she's proud.
Actually, I think I know
exactly where she is,
and it's pretty fuckin' hot.
You had one of those, too, huh?
Gentlemen.
Is everything okay here?
Yeah, sure. Just talkin'.
Okay, then.
Have a good night.
So they go through labor.
Big deal. Try a prostate exam.
This is great.
And I-I usually
don't like modern art.
The Rat Pack.
Do you know
a Joseph "Joey" Cogo?
Not much. I mean, I met him...
last week.
Me and Chrissy were havin' dinner
with Tony and his friend Valentina.
Joey Cogo sent over
a bottle of Veuve.
Wanna show her those?
Oh, my God.
Was this man with him?
Yeah. I saw him.
- You're sure?
- Tuesday night.
Jesus, 'cause of what I said?
You're supposed to be earners.
That's wh...
the top tier positions.
So each one of you go out
to your people on the street,
crack some fuckin'...
Create some fuckin'
earners out there!
- So, what's he sayin'?
- The way I remember he said,
"That's why you got
the top tier positions."
This other inaudible is
"Crack fuckin' heads," not legs.
I need a signature.
Now, that's it.
That's all I gotta say.
Frankly, I'm depressed and...
- Depressed and what?
- "Depressed and ashamed."
So what about my Alan Stewart
shirt from that meeting?
Ralph Cifaretto spilt
my coffee and ruined it.
I can petty cash it.
Resubmit, okay?
This Crazy Horse pole
camera's working out really good.
Paulie Gualtieri's car again.
She's still lying.
Listen, any chance
you could ask Ron
if this falls under
the same arrangement?
It's kinda soggy,
you wanna know the truth.
Pie. He was eating.
Tony, this is
federal redevelopment.
I'll look into it.
- So, a speech, huh?
- The sound quality is amazing.
New hats.
Mic's right in the button.
...Museum of
Science and Truckin'.
I just wish my
mother could've seen it.
Give it to Angela
and shut the door.
Wherever she is,
I'm sure she's proud.
What happened to the jury tampering
investigation on Junior Soprano's trial?
- Actually, I...
- You guys just drop the ball on that?
Massarone's a huge
asset. Couple him with...
What?
Three-year-old airline tickets?
Some ties
to the Bevelaqua murder?
Even if Massarone and a
thousand other snitches pan out,
we've still gotta
put Tony on trial.
That's useless
until we find out how they
penetrated
the anonymous jury system.
And what? Jury duty's
not tough enough?
You know we don't like
to dig into some citizen.
Tough shit. One of those
citizens is a felon. Get on it.
You know what's
goin' on here, right?
He fucked up his six-figure
future with O'Melveny and Meyers
when he blew
the Junior Soprano trial.
Of course he'll keep tryin' him
until he fixes that.
- Hey!
- Hey.
There he is, John Barrymore.
- How are ya?
- All right.
I thought nobody ever
comes to see you.
I was droppin' off
some dandelions.
Saw a beautiful patch in a
vacant lot over by 15th Street.
- Nice salad.
- Any word about Tony B?
Yeah, yeah,
should be any day now.
Aunt Quintina's gonna call
the moment she hears.
He's a good kid,
your cousin, huh? Smart.
Fuckin' weirdo, you ask me.
All right, the vacant lot
over on 15th Street?
That's where all the
neighborhood dogs go to piss.
You goddamn clown.
You got anything
lined up for the kid?
Yeah, yeah, air bags.
We pull 'em from boosted cars.
People buy 'em like you
wouldn't fuckin' believe.
Hey, legit dealers, body shops,
they reinstall
undeployed bags as new.
- Top dollar.
- Brave new world. Jesus Christ,
they didn't even have
shoulder belts when I went away.
So you'll let me know
when the kid gets out, huh?
Yeah, we'll have
a party for him.
- All right.
- I love you, okay.
Come on, eat.
Don't be so sensitive.
I was bein' polite. It's like...
It's like eatin' red fescue.
I'll take an egg.
You want an egg?
Bobby, make my nephew an egg.
I don't want an egg.
Tony B.
Like a welcome home present.
- What's that, a Motorola?
- Yeah.
Supposed to be the best.
You know,
I figured he could use one.
Call me when he needs me.
All the fellas are
gettin' out, huh?
The class of 2004.
Old rats on a new ship.
I think I'll take an egg.
Make us a couple eggs.
I'm doin' it. You told me.
He don't want one.
You and Tony Egg again.
Tony Egg? Tony B.
Like the time you two, you took
that camera in the bathroom...
...at your sister
Barbara's confirmation.
Hello?
Oh, that's terrible.
Where's he gonna be laid out?
Who now, goddamn it!
Well, let us know.
Carmine Lupertazzi.
He passed during the night.
What a fuckin' blow.
He was a great man.
My cousin told me it was Carmine
who invented point shaving.
CCNY versus Kentucky, 1951.
Nobody beat the spread.
I bought a black Fleetwood.
Anthony.
Anthony, did I ever tell you
I want to be cremated?
About four times.
And don't throw my ashes
in somebody's yard
or off some fuckin' bridge.
I wanna be on the mantelpiece
surrounded by family.
Yeah, under
the moose head, I know.
Keep jokin'.
Let me tell ya somethin'.
It's like that game
we used to play as kids,
crack the whip.
You run around like an idiot
holdin' hands as tight as you can,
and then the line snaps,
somebody lets go...
and you're next.
Your father meant
a lot to all of us.
And not just financially either.
How are ya?
What's up, buddy?
Nicole,
you remember Mr. Petrille?
What, honey?
He meant a lot to us.
- Ginny.
- Phil, how ya doin'?
- Hey, kid. I'm heartbroken.
- Angelo.
Nicole, you remember Mr. Garepe.
Of course.
That was my aunt.
- My cousin's out.
- Aw, that's great news.
Start him off small, T.
You hear that?
Your cousin's out.
- Oh, look who's comin'.
- What?
- Hey there, handsome.
- Hey, baby.
- How are ya?
- Good.
Lorraine, you're lookin' good.
Yeah, keepin' it together
with Pilates and gin.
Sil, Paulie, how's it hangin'?
Still got the nice manners, huh?
Ah, this is my
nephew Christopher.
Lady Shylock,
you got some reputation.
Yeah, my mother
said that might happen.
I'd like to introduce you
to the love of my life.
This is my partner,
Jason Evanina.
- Honor to meet ya.
- Hey, how are ya?
So Jesus leans off the cross
and whispers to Peter,
"I can see your house
from here."
I'm so sorry.
This was such a shock.
This is a very hard day.
I just saw Ginny.
The flowers are beautiful.
- John, got a minute?
- Yeah.
Nicole, I'm sorry.
What's goin' on here?
- What are you talkin' about?
- My father.
- Look at his hands.
- He looks peaceful.
I'm talkin' about his rosary.
The medal?
You think I don't
know what that is?
It's for Opus Dei.
The fuck is that about?
In his later years,
your father was very sensitive
- about what's been goin' on in the church.
- Bullshit!
Your wife is into Opus Dei.
You told Colombino
to put it there.
- You sure about that?
- Yes, John, I'm sure.
Body's not even cold.
No respect for anything anymore.
And New Jersey housewife
fundamentalist shit?
- I doubt it, John.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You yourself said
I was like another son to him.
I was bein'
polite. It was his deathbed.
I should've
written those words down.
Maybe you should have, John,
'cause they don't mean
anything anymore.
You understand what I'm sayin'?
I saw a huge
mushroom cloud from the shell.
Jim Campbell might
be alive today
if he hadn't said to me,
"Heffron, you stay
here with your gun.
I'm going up."
All your life,
you gotta remember
what one guy did
because he thought it
was his job to do,
and he took a shot for you.
This shit's not supposed to run,
and here I look like a raccoon.
You are irresistible
and you know it.
- Danny said I was clingy.
- Fuck him.
He's the one with
the self-esteem issues.
You don't know what
it's like out there, Ade.
You're marrying Christopher.
He's handsome, makes money,
he's got great hair.
Oh...
Okay.
You know I love animals,
but this thing is so gorgeous.
Isn't it?
My dad almost had a stroke.
But I told him, "Hey, asshole,
I'm the one taking all
the fucking risk here.
I have to fake the invoices."
Sometimes you gotta just take
care of yourself, you know?
Sure you do, honey.
Come here.
- Mmm.
- Oh!
Come on. Let's don't
keep your date waiting.
He likes you, I can tell.
We got a white wine for Ade.
- That's another apple martini for you.
- Thank you, my dear.
My Seven-and-7,
and nothing-and-nothing.
Don't listen to him, Chrissy.
I think what
you're doing's brave.
It's not for everybody.
Things are different when you
don't have that crutch, you know?
We make up for it other ways.
My God, it's hot in here.
What do you expect?
You're dancing in a mink coat.
- It's fox.
- She's my fox in a box.
Let's see her box,
or maybe her socks.
Stupid.
Well, I have to wear fur
on the outside
on account of being
bare everywhere else.
- You believe this one?
- No shit.
Every place I go, I got substances
I can't enjoy shoved in my face.
But I guess asking you for a little
support system in my own home
is way the fuck outta line.
You gotta have some more wine.
Seemed to have
a good time tonight.
The fuck you talking about?
What, Tina?
Come on, that cunt's too
full of herself, anyway.
Cunt? She's my maid of honor,
Christopher.
She's no fucking maid,
let me tell you.
Great, now I'm upset.
See what I'm talking about?
But I guess it's all my problem.
I'm sorry, baby. Okay?
Please, stop.
All right, all right.
My handsome nephew.
Auntie Quin, look at you
all dolled up, huh?
Ah! I never thought I'd
live to see this day.
Well, here ya are, still here.
Where's Tony?
Downstairs getting
into one of his old suits.
- I'll buy him some new suits.
- He's fine.
I only wish he had more
to come back to.
That ex-wife of his,
she uses her answering machine
to ignore me,
so forget about
his seeing the twins.
How's Kelly? How's she doing?
She's lost to us, Anthony.
But Tony says
he's gonna hire a detective.
Look at this.
The two of you were so cute.
Even then,
my cannoli was bigger than his.
Ooh, stop.
Aw, man. There he is.
Ah.
Oh! God, Ton'.
Look at us, 15 fuckin' years.
- The language.
- Go ahead, say it.
I haven't changed a bit, right?
You look good, you look good.
Oh!
Say "provolone."
Surprise!
Shit. Very nice,
you give me a heart attack.
Ma, it's enough, all right?
Stop crying.
I'm embarrassed enough.
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything. Just eat.
Oh, hey!
Ha! I got peppers been
marinating for 15 years!
Hey.
- What?
- Where's Tubs?
Artie? What happened here?
Still a ball-breaker, huh?
Boop!
The fuck's with him?
Ask him.
You guys have a beef?
I loaned the guy some money,
then he tried to kill himself.
And guess who got the blame?
Oh, my God, Tony.! Oh!
My God, we have
all missed you so much.
I swear, you...
you look exactly the same.
Oh, you're still
full of shit, huh?
Is Nancy here yet? The twins?
No, Nancy couldn't make it.
Her aunt in Bayonne,
the sciatica.
- What are you gonna do?
- Cousin!
Jan! Oh!
Come, come, I want you
to meet my family.
I'm talking to him right now.
- Tony, you remember Bobby.
- Oh, yeah.
Now my husband.
And guys, this is
your Uncle Tony Blundetto.
Hey, there.
How come we
never met you before?
I've been away on business.
I've never even heard of you.
Stop playing with your ice,
come on.
They let that kid say anything.
- Welcome home, Uncle Tony.
- Oh, Jesus.
This is Meadow.
God, you turned out
beautiful, honey.
And this strapping young man
is Anthony Jr.
How's Kelly?
Our regular dinner,
out by you Thursday, right?
Yes, Daddy.
See, with my family now,
you know, the separation,
you gotta make an appointment
to see each other.
- I should go see Uncle Zio.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Show him the phone!
Yeah.
Tony.
I'll make this fast
'cause I know you're all hungry.
I remember growing up,
I was always asking why
I just used to have sisters.
I said to my mother, I said, "Can't you save
up something and then get me a baby brother?"
And my mother said,
"What's wrong
with your cousin Tony?"
And she was right,
'cause we were brothers.
Except, you know,
we had the same name.
There was, like, 50 Tonys
in the family.
Some of you remember this.
My dad's name was Johnny,
and his dad's name was Alfred.
And so whenever we were out
running around and we'd hear,
"Tony Uncle Johnny,"
that was for me.
And "Tony Uncle Al,"
that was for him.
And there was "Tony
Uncle Philly!" Remember?
- Right, yeah, yeah.
- But he passed away.
Buon anima.
And Uncle Phil, Uncle Phil,
he passed away
a long time ago too.
So, anyway...
Tony's being away,
it's been hard.
But he's back now, for good.
- So welcome home.
- Welcome home.
- Thank you.
- Salute.
Come on, let me hear it.
Welcome home!
Hey, Ton', Meadow is incredible.
She's a fucking Ivy Leaguer.
You and Carm hit a home run.
Yeah.
I'm sure Kelly's all right,
wherever she is.
Hey, her old man was in prison.
We tried to do everything
we could.
I know. I mean, I wasn't
around. What could I expect?
I mean, if things had gone
different way back when, who knows?
- What do you want from me?
- Nothing!
I'm just saying it's good
it wasn't both of us.
Ah, well, these things
happen, right?
You're gonna like
this place. This is nice.
This is the kind of place we
always talked about having.
Fucking weird.
My cousin in the old man's seat.
It's like Sun Ti-zu says:
"A good commander is benevolent
and unconcerned with fame."
- What?
- Sun Ti-zu.
The Chinese Prince Matchabelli.
Tony turned me on to him.
"Zoo"! "Zoo"!
Sun Tzu, you fucking ass-kiss.
- Hey.
- Feech!
You know, I missed you
by two weeks at Allenwood.
This'll help you get started.
Jesus, you're
on your feet already?
You hit the ground running,
and you don't look back, huh?
Thank you.
Come on.
So you in
on the bus station project?
Massarone's waiting on a number.
- How's he doing?
- Good.
We had coffee.
He used to bore me, Jack.
But he ain't a bad guy,
once you get to know him.
I always liked him.
I was very touched
by that funeral the other day.
- Real heart-grabber.
- That fucking little Carmine.
And after what?
Five years in Florida
fixing wet t-shirt contests.
M'boy are you fat.
What did you say?
Reginald Van Gleason III.
"M'boy are you fat."
That's good, yeah.
Oh!
So I got some ideas,
you know, for you.
Get you on your feet.
Unless, of course, you already
know what you wanna do.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Well, yeah. I kinda got an idea.
Yeah?
Like four years in,
I got moved to Springfield.
You know, where they got
the big prison hospital.
It's mostly stab wounds, detox.
Anyway, this guy
I knew from Elkton,
he was telling me how I
could be an orderly, you know?
And how it's
like easy time and all.
Well, you know, so then you're
the guy that hooks everybody up.
That's smart.
Yeah, but it
wasn't business for me.
I mean, I really got
into this shit.
Rehab block had guys
with broken limbs,
muscle diseases,
and we'd help 'em back.
So I think this might
be a thing I can do.
I got my associate's degree
already. Took me five years.
And now it's only like six months
more for my massage license.
So you wanna run
a massage parlor?
No.
I'm gonna be
a licensed massage therapist.
Look, I've been away
from all this a long time.
I mean, if I got a shot at staying
out and putting shit together,
- I should take it.
- Oh.
'Cause I was thinking, you know,
I got this air bag thing going...
Oh, Ton', thanks, but...
I mean,
it's a really nice offer,
but I need regular work
until I'm certified.
Just regular work.
Well, I guess
I know this guy looking
for a delivery man
for his linen fleet.
- Bobby Gociletto?
- No, no, no, Koreans.
You know, I don't
got my driver's license.
So you'll go to my guy
at the DMV.
As far as the union shit,
I can take care of that.
Wow, Ton'. Thanks. Thank you.
Come here.
- You're the best, you know that?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Out.
- Why?
Because we are watching a
movie and you are studying.
And why must we keep
having that conversation?
Here it is.
Number one on the
American Film Institute's
Greatest American Movies list.
Citizen Kane.
- Jesus, it's black and white.
- Oh, come on.
That is what film club is
all about, trying new things.
Now, to give us some background,
let's see what Leonard Maltin has to say.
"A film that broke all the rules
and invented some new ones.
The cinematography, music
and Oscar-winning screenplay
by Welles and Herman J...
something are all first rate."
- Wow.
- So it was a sled, huh?
He should've told somebody.
I think it's fascinating that
the man had all that stuff,
but he died, you know,
alone with nothing and nobody.
Good. Prick.
I hated it. "You supply the
war, I'll supply the headlines."
How conceited.
- There was the cinematography.
- Yeah, that was very good.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
I saw Laura Basi in the
dressing room at Loehmann's.
Definitely had some work.
D-cup at least, and a lift.
Well, she said she was remodeling
her upstairs, but I had no idea.
So, Carm, how you doing?
I'm okay.
My lawyer, he's a top guy,
Robert Greenberg.
He says that New Jersey has
this equitable distribution law.
So apparently 20 years entitles
me to at least half his money.
Well, it should. You made Tony
a home, you raised his children.
Does this guy know
how to get it?
Well, it's mostly cash,
obviously.
God, all those years,
and you could get nothing.
This other lawyer, Dan Minditch,
he says that we should play hardball.
You know,
go after the real assets.
Marriage is
beautiful in the beginning,
but two, three years later?
You'd think there'd
be some romance at least.
- Janice, you're a newlywed.
- I know.
Six months and Bobby still
hasn't found my rosebud.
Maybe he should hire a reporter.
So the movie's over
and they all start talking
about their marriages
and how miserable they are.
Bitterness.
So besides the movie night?
- You have kids?
- No.
So did you attend
Carmine Lupertazzi's funeral?
I didn't know him.
Movie night was fun, though.
Who was there at the
Tony Blundetto homecoming?
I told you, just family.
God, is that all you think
about, is your fucking work?
You don't care how
I feel about anything.
Okay.
I was married to an agent.
What happened?
Did he cheat on you?
While we were trying
to get pregnant,
he climbed right over me to
become an assistant supervisor
on the Milken task force.
Moved to Los Angeles and
jumped a pay grade without me.
My God, that-- that's terrible.
So, where were we?
What am I doing?
I can't talk to you.
I can't even talk to Christopher,
and he's my soul mate, for God's sake.
I can't talk to my friends.
I am being, like, ripped apart
here, just snitching on people.
For what?
What do I get out of it?
Maybe take some comfort
in the fact that you're trying
to do the right thing
by helping your government.
No, seriously.
For me, it was
when I was in college.
My sister's boyfriend, Kyle,
traded our TV for six handguns.
He sold five
to a high school kid,
then used the last one
to open a coconut.
The ricochet left
my sister a paraplegic.
I knew I had to do something
about guys like him.
And nowhere but the FBI
is the line clearer
between the good guys
and the bad guys.
And you're
with the good guys now.
Wow.
Jesus.
- Hey.
- T.B.!
I didn't call
for no linen delivery.
What do I find at the pork store?
A bunch of guys beating the meat.
- Wanna deal me in?
- Absolutely.
Stakes might be
a little high for you.
You know you can't
pay us in napkins.
You got to let that dry
before you put on a second coat?
Fuckin' Grandpa Munster
over here.
Oh!
You gonna deal those?
They're not candy bars.
You can let some of 'em go.
The fuck's that for?
Drying shirts?
It's a Tao master massage chair.
Oh, I had no idea
I was so tense.
It's like my back
is on vacation.
Well, it could
definitely use one.
The fuck is this?
Hey, T, you gotta try this.
He's really fucking good.
There's nothing like being
in the joint
to teach you how to ease
another man's tensions.
Jesus Christ,
I'm gone for one hour.
All of a sudden it turns
into a fucking slumber party.
Somebody woke up
on the wrong side of the bed.
Could I talk to you a minute?
None of your fucking business
which side of the bed I wake up on.
- Jesus, it's just an expression.
- Bullshit.
And don't tell me you don't
know what I'm talking about.
All that Reggie Van Gleason,
"M'boy are you fat."
Things have changed around here.
I'm the boss
of this fucking family.
You're crowding me.
You don't make fun of me.
Got it?
Got it.
And knock off the massage shit.
It's a place of business,
not a Jack LaLanne.
You gotta declare all that?
Most of it, anyway.
Well, if you had
a good bookkeeper...
Hey, you got change? Been
fuckin' slidin' this stupid bill
in and out of
the cigarette machine
for like an hour.
An hour? I bet you
can go longer than that.
Listen to you.
Why do you always
talk like a whore?
- Because men like it.
- Yeah?
I think you're right about that.
♪ I don't mind spending
every day ♪
♪ Out on your corner
in the pouring rain ♪
Tellin' you,
I'm having a fucking time.
Stay out late, come home
drunk, fuck anyone I want.
Yeah, so what's the difference?
I don't know. It's a mindset.
Jesus Christ.
Ton', I was hoping
you'd be here.
I gotta tell you,
you shouldn't go out and eat
up there in Fairfield no more.
The fuck you talkin' about?
I went to collect
from my cop up there,
and he gave me a heads-up.
His buddy on the force
saw some car
out by Napoleon's diner
a couple of weeks ago.
And I remembered how
your goomah lives up there.
- Yeah?
- Guy thought maybe they were fags,
but he ran the plate,
and it bounced back a no-hit.
Feds.
Cop said they were just
sitting there in the rain.
They always do that,
but I know it wasn't me
they tailed that night
'cause my whole life's
in the fucking rearview.
- Mine, too.
- Absolutely.
It's Massarone.
Aw, Jesus Christ.
He flipped, I'd be fucked.
We all would.
Well, he ain't been
to the grand jury,
because we would have heard
from our girl up there.
They could be just
following him at this point,
see if they could
get anything on him.
Yeah, and eventually they'll
bring him in. Jesus Christ.
They've turned a lot
fuckin' tougher guys
than Jack Massarone.
You want me to take care of it?
All right, we don't know
shit yet, right?
He did give me that
fuckin' painting, though.
There was that, Ton'.
Can't a guy be fuckin'
nice anymore? Friendly?
So what do you wanna do?
I wanna be
absolutely fuckin' sure.
That's what I wanna do.
All right, we arrange a meet.
I'll feel him out a little bit.
I gotta do it. I know the guy.
I know the way he thinks.
I know the way he acts.
My old man was very good
at vibing people out, too.
Massarone's up to
something, I'll pick it up.
You piece of shit.
I don't believe this.
Hold on.
- Yeah.
- I just wanted to thank you
for taking the components
out of the home theater.
Hey, I bought that for us to
watch movies as a family, okay?
Not to entertain
your girlfriends.
I talked to my lawyer about
filing a separation agreement.
I'm not paying a lawyer.
We should be able to settle
this thing like adults!
Then stop taking shit
out of the house!
- Hey, Tony, what's up?
- Let's take a walk.
- There he is, huh?
- Hey, how you doing?
- Good, good. How you doing?
- Okay.
- Everything all right?
- Yeah, watch the curb here.
Hey, wait a second.
Before you say anything,
- have you lost a little weight?
- You think, huh?
I don't know.
Listen, I talked to our friend.
You know, the one that
celebrates Hanukkah?
Uh-huh.
- It's in the works.
- Oh, great, it's good news.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. Yeah.
So I been meaning to ask you...
you noticed anything lately?
What are we talking about?
You weren't followed here,
were you?
No, I-I don't think so.
I-I'm pretty careful.
All right.
Everything else okay,
good EKG and shit, huh?
- Yeah, I guess.
- All right.
But I gotta tell you,
I don't like what I'm hearing.
Relax.
It's not worth
losing your hair over.
- Right?
- Okay.
All right.
I couldn't tell shit. What
the fuck am I, a mind reader?
So what's the next
step here, Ton'?
What?
Said I looked like
I lost some weight.
- Oh.
- Motherfucker.
Yeah?
Hey, whoa, whoa. Take it easy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, hold on.
That Korean Kim.
Something about your cousin,
I don't know.
Yeah?
It's your fucking linen truck. What
do you want me to do about it?
Yeah, yeah, it's okay.
Fire him. Go ahead.
Put him out in the fuckin'
street, for all I care!
Tony B wants
to pick up some scratch.
He could do this
Massarone thing, if it goes.
What the fuck is
wrong with you?!
The man is trying
to go straight!
Don't you give a fuck
about your cousin?
I'm sorry, T. You're right.
That was a great party
the other night.
Fuck him.
Guy is fucking useless to me.
Was that a yes on Massarone?
Tony's...
got his own process.
What's to process here?
Honestly, Carm,
this is a lot better
than watching Casablanca.
I didn't need to see
that movie again anyway.
Even if it kills Tony,
I will have that system
back for next time.
So what is next on that list?
Number three, The Godfather.
Look at us. We'll kill
ourselves for these cigarettes.
You know they
had a bear back here?
So how come Angie
Bonpensiero don't come?
Please. She's not welcome here.
I thought everybody liked her.
Don't you know about Pussy?
He went in the Program.
He turned on everybody, us,
the people he knew
his whole life.
Who knows why people
do what they do?
But what kind
of person does that?
I mean, it's like
Judas or something,
eating that last supper
with Jesus.
And the whole time he knows
they're gonna crucify Him.
I mean, at least Judas
didn't go into any
apostle protection program.
He hung himself.
He knew what he did.
Oh, look at you.
You're shivering.
I didn't know it
was that cold, sweetie.
I'll tell you, I don't
know how I'd be holding up.
It's just...
I guess you all
are really important to me.
Aw, Carm, you'd do the same.
We love you so much.
Ade, you okay?
What's the matter?
I'm-I'm not what you think.
I don't know what to do.
I need...
I wanna tell you all something.
It's driving me crazy.
You know you can
tell us anything.
Oh, God.
She's been drinking like crazy.
- Where are you going?
- Oh!
Oh, my God!
Honey!
I'm fine, okay?
Just leave me alone.
No, you're bleeding.
Let me drive you.
Ton'? It's like 3:00
in the morning.
Yeah, yeah. Well, I couldn't sleep,
so I wanted to see if the phone worked.
Well, yeah, it works great.
I'm in my mother's basement,
and I can really hear you.
Listen, you should know
that that boss there, Kim,
he's after your ass.
I rub him the wrong way.
Maybe you shouldn't be
a masseuse then.
Oh.
Look, Tony, the reason I called,
you know, about the other day, uh...
Look, you can kid around
with me, okay?
But not when
the other guys are there.
I gotta maintain respect.
No, I know. You're the boss.
Jesus.
See, you gotta be careful
what you say on this phone.
It doesn't affect you,
but it affects me.
Right. I'm sorry.
Is everything good over there?
You know, my mom's on my case.
Who'd have thought
we'd both be on our own again?
Well, you can get back
together with Carm if you want.
'Course she thinks it's up to her,
and she goes from zero to bitch
every time I try to show
any warmth, you know?
That's gotta be tough.
Listen, Ton',
I gotta be up in two hours.
So go to sleep.
But you're my cousin
and my best friend.
You gotta know
we could always talk.
Yeah, well, I'll buy
a fucking lunch box.
All right, go to sleep,
go to sleep.
We gotta talk about
my compensation overall.
Interferon for my son's MS?
That's 20 a year now.
Right. You said you were
gonna get us a making ceremony,
which you didn't do.
And here you are
asking for a raise.
Can't you talk
to the higher-ups?
Okay, we made Vito Spatafore
as running Ralph Cifaretto's
construction business.
Has Chris ever confirmed that?
- You wanna know something?
- What?
This girl, she's totally
ripping off her employer.
Probably over a hundred grand.
What do you mean?
Tina Francesco's her name.
She's a bookkeeper
for this furniture wholesaler.
So she makes up vendors,
but she writes them real checks.
Then her father cashes them.
Is that like a federal crime?
How many checks?
I mean, how much?
Like I said,
probably over a hundred grand.
Tina...?
Francesco.
The father's name's Victor.
It's Brettler and Sons Imports.
♪ Hear the screams
of Center 42 ♪
♪ Loud enough
to bust your brains out ♪
♪ The opposition's tongue
is cut in two ♪
♪ Keep off the street
'cause you're in danger ♪
♪ 100,000 disparus ♪
♪ Lost in the jails
in South America ♪
♪ Cuddle up, baby
Cuddle up tight ♪
Keep it all out of sight ♪
♪ Undercover
♪ Undercover of the night ♪
♪ The sex police are out there
on the streets ♪
♪ Make sure the past laws
are not broken ♪
♪ The race militia
has got itchy fingers ♪
♪ All the way from New York
back to Africa ♪
♪ Cuddle up, baby
Keep it all out of sight ♪
♪ Cuddle up, baby ♪
♪ Sleep with it all
out of sight ♪
♪ Cuddle up, baby
Keep it all out of sight ♪