♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon In your eyes ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
You must be hungry.
You're not gonna cook, are you?
Just saying,
don't trouble yourself.
How about some Egg Beaters
and Tabasco?
That's fine.
Didn't I tell you I hate this
shouting-between-rooms shit?
So you even gonna
look at the brochure?
What is it,
Sneakers or something?
Sandals.
It's the jewel of Antigua.
Three sun-filled days
on white sand.
I got A.J. on weekends.
So we'll go on Monday.
Get a great rate
on an ocean view.
The air is the same
temperature as your body,
so you don't even
need to wear clothes.
I gotta watch my skin
in the sun.
You know, you're
getting a divorce,
and I see you less than before.
I didn't say no.
I want your
undivided attention, for once.
Is it so much to fucking ask
for a little bit of atten...
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, shit!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
I got you. All right, okay.
All right. I got it.
It's out! It's out!
I got it.
You're okay. You're okay.
There he is.
Hey, kid, it's good to see you.
So you finally made
the trip out here, huh?
Tony, this is my oldest,
Charlie.
Nice to meet you.
Walk with me.
Well?
You in that suit.
Long way, huh?
He lucked out.
Got his mother's looks.
Takes after her too.
He's in architectural salvage.
Old fixtures, windows, toilets.
Like Sanford and Son?
Didn't I tell you he's quick?
- Good for you, Charlie. Salute.
- Salute.
Oh.
And this is some more,
for the Joey Peeps thing.
Not all of it.
Ah, he's okay.
Jesus, I did a clean job.
Fuck it, it's embarrassing.
But that's the way
Little Carmine and Rusty
are doing things over there now.
I'm sorry, but Rusty, I think he
bangs his wife in installments.
This guy was my old man,
my rabbi and my priest
rolled into one.
And even though I don't miss
a fucking day of it,
the parts with this fireplug
were the best.
Get the fuck outta here.
Oh, I almost forgot.
It spoke to me on account
of your sense of humor and all.
I'm putting this
in a position of prominence.
Hey, how you doing?
Are you gonna operate on me?
No, it's-it's me, Tony.
They gotta fight infection.
My hair.
Well, the good news is
it'll grow back.
And the burns are second degree,
so you don't need a skin graft
or that hyperbolic chamber.
You're gonna look the same
as you always did.
Fuck you.
All right, one second.
All right.
- It hurts.
- Okay, sit tight, rest.
They gotta keep you
in here a couple days
so we don't get
no bacteria in there.
Are you gonna operate on me?
All right, look, I'm gonna
take care of everything.
The doctor bills, a wig.
Whatever.
And don't worry about nothing.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
I gotta go.
Oh.
Just put it in there.
I'm going to get some twine.
Forget it,
I'm not going that far.
- ♪ Peanuts ♪
♪ Oh-oh, oh-oh... ♪
I know. I know, you fuck.
Come on. Let's go. Move on.
♪ Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh ♪
- ♪ Peanuts ♪
Fucking great.
Listen, I don't know
what the fuck
you were looking at...
Fuck is this?
Ange, sorry about that.
We were on our way to your
place, and Billy sees you drive by.
I tried to get your attention
for a couple of blocks.
Why didn't you use
a fucking phone?
I'm an old man.
I don't see so good in the dark.
Jesus, relax.
Johnny wants to see you.
This late?
Tell him I'll see him tomorrow.
Apparently it's gotta be now.
You know,
he's in one of his moods.
Fine.
I'll follow you over.
Whatever, let's go.
Don't!
Hey! Jesus, don't!
Phil, please!
Philly! Philly, you know me.
You couldn't fucking retire?
Philly, for God's sake,
you know me!
Look at this shit.
You know the work I just had?
Give me the fucking keys.
Mirsa, you seen today's paper?
Everything in the kitchen,
Mr. Tony!
God-fucking-damn it.
You know this is today's paper?
Oh, no.
This is today's paper, Mirsa.
That's I'm thinking.
Why'd you throw it away?
Oh, no.
Jesus Christ, forget it.
I bake you some
enchiladas you like.
Thank you. That's nice of you.
These are for you. Enchiladas.
Okay.
I came for my money.
Don't worry, I'll talk
to Carlo and tell him why
you're kicking up
directly to me this week.
I gotta be careful
getting my cash,
on account of
the Carmela situation.
She's all over that.
- You buying that WaveRunner?
- Oh, I'm, uh, moving to the Plaza.
That fucking house
is falling down around my ears.
Well, we did good over
at the casino last night.
I seriously dread going home.
That fucking Guatemalan,
she forgets her English
whenever it suits her purposes,
and then she shows up
whenever she feels like
with the fucking enchiladas.
So fire her ass, get a new one.
This is the new one.
I been in the burn ward a
couple of nights with Valentina.
Poor thing caught
herself on fire.
No shit?
She's laying there
like a rag doll,
the poor kid.
That smell.
Fuck, that burning hair smell.
I can still smell it.
Jesus, you know,
that's the last thing
that Carmine said
before he had his stroke?
He smelled burning hair.
You got a Coke or something?
Ma, can you get Tony a Coke?
I'm upstairs!
Jason, Justin, get up here!
You all right?
I just got the kids up my ass,
that's all.
So you come
across any burn victims
at that hospital in the can?
Sure, Aryan guys are always
setting each other on fire.
So, what's she in for?
You know, the future, I mean.
They said she don't need
no skin grafts.
Seriously, what the fuck
is with you?
I just told you.
You know the tough part is,
this girl is a constant
pain in my ass.
I was gonna end it
right there, that night.
And now how the fuck
is it gonna look?
That is a tough one.
How the fuck does this shit
always happen to me?
You know what I been
thinking about lately?
Charmaine Bucco.
Nice set on her.
No, not like that.
Well, maybe like that.
But also,
she's a fantastic cook.
She's better than Artie
in some ways.
Plus, she's a licensed
notary public.
I mean, I'm thinking that this
is the kind of woman I need.
And it almost worked
between me and her, right?
Comic books, juice boxes,
robot crap all over the place.
Go get your uncle a Coke
and then your stuff.
I'm taking you back
to your mom's early.
I should take off.
Yeah, you know, I really gotta
run them over there now.
All right, yeah.
I'll see you later.
All right.
I'll come over to the hotel.
Yeah.
Lawrence wedding?
- No.
- Long-term or short-term?
Can't you just park it?
Here.
Keep it out of the horse shit
over there, will you?
Oh, yeah. Beautiful, ladies.
Here we go.
Although you'll be paying cash,
we'll need to see a credit card
to secure any incidental charges.
Minibar, parking, et cetera.
Right.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Oh, Jill, that's so funny.
Very good, Mr. Petraglia.
We have you in a deluxe suite
with a park view.
My name is Sharice.
And along with our 24-hour
concierge service,
I'm here to see that you enjoy
your stay with us.
Great.
The bellman will show you
to your room.
Enjoy your stay, Mr. Petraglia.
Anything else I can do,
press nine, ask for Jesus.
For you.
Thank you, sir. Enjoy your stay.
Thanks.
Hello?
Whoever you are,
I'd like you to stop this.
Of course, whether
it's the Vanderbilt Suite
or an elegant deluxe
standard room,
the Plaza is equipped with a
state-of-the-art safety system
and a well-trained staff.
...the gentle pleasures
and mysterious ways
of the East, more than
the ladies of Jade Escorts.
New York's most exotic
and erotic girls
are waiting to please you.
Call 1-900-555-JADE.
And let them satisfy
your every need.
All major credit cards
are accepted.
What are you waiting for?
Been trying to reach you.
Angelo got it. Last night.
Probably Phil.
I'm not available right now, don't
leave messages on this phone.
Fuck!
Hello?
- Who's this?
- It's Dot. Who's this?
It's Tony, looking for Ton'.
Oh, he's not here.
He didn't come in
tonight at all.
He might be in later, though.
You wanna try
his portable phone?
I did.
You see him, you have him
call me, immediately.
Okay, will do.
Hello?
Yeah, Aunt Quin.
It's Tony, looking for Ton'.
Marone, I was hoping
he was with you.
You heard from him?
Not since he took the kids back
this morning.
Call me if you hear,
you understand?
- Yeah.
- You got my cell?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Yeah?
- You seen my cousin?
- No.
But I heard about
that thing last night.
The old-timer
was a stand-up guy.
Yeah, well,
that's the least of it.
Hold on. Hold on.
Hey, you call for a date?
Yeah. Yeah.
Got company?
Yeah.
- Hold on a second.
- Can I get a drink?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wanna know the minute
he surfaces.
You got it.
I saw him this morning, and he
must have known something,
because he was acting
all squirrelly.
He's got a right to be upset
after what him and Ange
been through together.
They were cell mates
at Allenwood.
I don't know, I got
a bad feeling about this.
Don't worry about it.
He ain't that stupid.
Yeah, you're probably right.
We'll let you know
if we see him.
You want me to suck
your dick now, baby?
Is that what you want, baby?
What the fuck?
Tony, I'm so lonely.
I miss my Violet.
What violin?
Violet, my wife.
She was everything to me.
I'm all alone on the other side.
It ain't right.
Answer the fucking thing.
If it's him,
tell him you ain't seen me.
Tell who?
The Man Upstairs.
Hello?
We need you to do somethin'.
Like what?
Our friend.
He's gotta go.
No problem.
Don't fuck it up.
It's important.
I know it's important.
He was staring straight at me.
And he didn't look dead.
Any deader than he ever did,
anyways.
And he says, uh,
"I miss my wife."
Then the phone rings, and...
there was this voice.
They wanted me to do something.
What?
They wanted me to kill a guy.
It was just a dream, all right?
He must be in heaven.
He said "the other side."
But he was so fucking sad.
Doesn't sound like heaven to me.
Well, you would know
more about it than I do.
What'd you see in me, anyways?
The object is to learn
what you saw in me,
not what I saw in you.
One of these days, Alice.
One of these days.
Pow! Right in the kisser?
"To the moon, Alice!"
I remember when you hit me.
It was like, "Pow! To the moon."
"Don't get me steamed, Alice!"
And then you choked
the shit out of me!
Yeah, but that's after you were
tryin' to put a fork in my eye.
No! That was your mother!
Sometimes what happens here
is like taking a shit.
I prefer to think of it
as more like childbirth.
Maybe it is more
like childbirth.
You tell me.
I don't have any children.
I died too young.
My cousin does a mean Gleason.
Are you ready for what
you have to do?
No sweat.
I did my homework.
You wanna ride up front?
No, Dad, I'm fine.
Kid gets sick in the back seat.
You know, douchebag, I
realize I'm dreaming.
I got no opinion,
one way or the other.
Anybody mind?
What?
Where we goin'?
Driving you to the job.
Oh, Jesus, you scared me.
And you're not even ready.
We gotta meet Finn's parents.
Why didn't you wake me up?
Is that how you're gonna dress?
Well, my stuff isn't here.
You left your brown suit.
I did?
And we're late.
I had the worst fucking dream.
Tony, we're late.
And we should take
separate cars.
Oh, yeah.
Howdy.
You, uh, were riding out here
the other day, weren't you?
You speak English?
¿Habla inglés?
Sí.
- Tony...
- What? Give me a minute.
Can you pull yourself away for once?
Your head is filled
with this stuff.
It's just that it's so much
more interesting.
Than what?
Than life.
What, are you kidding me?
It is your life.
Good morning, señor.
Tell me, what day is it?
What day?
Why, it's Christmas Day,
of course, sir.
Christmas Day! Christmas Day!
Christmas Day.
Then I haven't missed it.
The spirits must've done
everything in one night.
Will you please get dressed?
Of course they can.
God, look at you.
All right, let's go.
I'll wait in the car.
Now what's the matter?
Nothing.
Are you coming?
Yeah.
Hi.
How are you both?
There you are.
I was getting so nervous.
Hiya, babe.
We were about to start
calling the hospitals.
Somebody forgot.
I'd like you to meet
Finn's parents.
Mr. DeTrolio and Mrs. DeTrolio.
Oh, how do you do?
- Hi, how are you?
- Nice to meet you.
We've been enjoying getting to know
your daughter while we were waiting.
So how's the food here?
It's pretty goodl, uh,
we went to high school
with the owner and his wife.
Oh, you two were
high school sweethearts?
So how long can you stay?
Something I have
to take care of.
Oh.
Show them what you have
in your pocket.
With a husband in dental school,
he'll be able to fix
your mouth, honey.
Then for the capper...
Oh, son of a bitch.
We know all about you,
and I think it's great.
Well, that's a relief,
huh, Tony?
Speaking of dental school,
people always told us Finn would
never amount to much.
He won't.
I think the die is cast.
Yeah, if it wasn't for his Tooth
Fairy money, he'd have nothing.
Let's not get into it in front
of other people, okay?
Well, you're the one that said--
Never mind.
Please, just drop it.
So, Meadow,
do you play an instrument?
I was in chamber singers.
I used to sing
in the Navy Glee Club.
♪ Thanks for the times ♪
♪ That you've given me ♪
♪ The memories ♪
♪ Are all in my mind ♪
♪ And now that we've come ♪
♪ To the end of our rainbow ♪
♪ There's something
I must say out loud ♪
♪ You're once, twice ♪
♪ Three times a lady ♪
You're Annette Bening.
I thought so.
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Yes, you're once ♪
♪ Twice ♪
♪ Three times a lady ♪
♪ And I love you ♪
♪ When we're together ♪
♪ The moments I cherish ♪
♪ With every beat Of my heart ♪
♪ To hold you To touch you ♪
♪ To feel you To need you ♪
What?
♪ There's nothing ♪
♪ To keep us apart ♪
Something bad is gonna happen.
♪ Yes, you're once, twice ♪
♪ Three times a lady ♪
♪ And I love ♪
♪ You ♪
Well...
after I sing, I can usually
use a nice tinkle.
I'll go with you.
I don't want my husband
coming out of there
with just his cock in his hand.
Mine either. Believe me.
Oh, that feels good.
You don't do this no more, huh?
No.
Oh.
You got a good boy out there.
Are you gonna be able
to come through on the thing?
I did my homework.
Yeah?
Well, the piece wasn't
behind the toilet.
- Well, this is real life.
- No, it's not.
This is it.
Stop! Stop!
I knew this was gonna happen.
Why didn't you stop him?
Please.
You have any idea
what you just did?
Why don't you tell them
what happened 20 years ago.
I can't go into that right now.
What do I gotta count to
before I can get up?
Tony?
You're really dead.
But I got kids. They got kids.
Yo, wasn't that Tony there
the guy you were supposed to cap
to prevent this from happening?
I don't know.
I guess not.
I don't have a piece.
Annette Bening?
There's something "Bugsy"
about him.
Get him!
Over here!
I'm wiped out.
The fuck you doing
to yourself?
Huh?
What's that noise?
It's those micks
outside the hotel
with those carriage rides.
Tell them to go away.
Oh, God, Tony.
It's so much better
than when we were kids.
See? What'd I tell you?
The best, huh?
Oh, she likes it when
you rub her muzzle.
I think I wanna come home.
There are some
non-negotiable conditions.
Like what?
You can't have
your horse in here.
- Why not?
- Are you kidding me?
The smell, and shit
all over the place?
I'll clean up after her.
You always say that.
I'll have to think about it.
You're the one brought it up.
I should go.
You didn't take care of that?
But...
check this out.
Be careful.
I know you're there, Soprano.
Well, come on.
You're gonna do it, do it.
Well, look at you.
How you doing, Coach Molinaro?
Me? I'm fine.
What's that you got there?
A bigger dingus
than the one God gave you?
Dumbass.
You know, you ought to show
some respect.
Why?
'Cause I'm not some kid anymore.
No?
What did I tell you?
Cleave yourself away from
them bums you hang with, I said.
Well, I'm in therapy now.
That's a damn shame.
You all listened to that
pismire, Arthur Bucco.
He was the worst of the bunch.
I told you that.
Artie owns a restaurant.
He's doing great.
- Bucco?
- Yeah.
So what? The exception
that proves the rule.
Oh, you know everything,
don't you?
I suppose you blame it
on your father
when you're crying
to that shrink of yours.
No, more my mother.
Of course, even better.
Well, my family was different
than other kids' families.
You know, I bet you got
that psychologist
wrapped around your finger.
Well, that's what you always
told me I was good at, right?
I also told you, most likely,
you'd take the easy way out.
It hasn't been easy!
I see you on TV.
Oh, yeah?
Some show you put on.
The Five O'Clock News.
Then you realize I got nothing
to apologize to you for.
I am a leader.
Got a house worth a million-two.
Two kids. Wife.
Do you?
- Do I what?
- Have a wife?
Yeah. She's got the big house
'cause I'm successful.
You and I know
your little secret.
You know, I only told you
I wanted to be a coach
'cause I liked playing ball,
but I was shining you on,
'cause that's
what I do with people.
I told you many times, Anthony,
you were special.
You had smarts, personality,
leadership potential,
all the "perquisites"
to lead young men
onto the field of sport.
And now look at the stress
you live with.
You're not prepared!
You'll never shut me up!
Yeah?
We're sorry to disturb you at
this hour, Mr. Petraglia,
but there's a
Mr. Montevani to see you.
He says it's urgent.
Send him up.
Hey.
Sorry to get you up,
but I knew you'd
wanna know right away.
Know what?
Tony B. took out Billy Leotardo.
Yeah.
Wait a minute, you mean Philly?
Billy. Phil got winged.
- He's in the hospital.
- Ah.
TB went ape over Angelo.
Phil, he's holding
his little brother
as the kid's dying in his arms.
There's blood all over Phil.
Jesus.
So he knew.
Goddamn him.
He knew what he was gonna do
when he sat there
right in his mother's house
and pretended.
Lied right to my face.
I don't know what to say.
Guess TB's fucked, poor guy.
Poor guy?
We're all fucked.
I'm here for you, whatever.
I know that.
It's a nice suite, T.
Anyway, thought you
needed to know right away.
You gonna eat that?
No, take it.
Thanks.
All right.
See you later.
Hello?
Yeah, don't get alarmed.
I'm sorry to call you
so early, but, uh,
I gotta cancel
the fishing trip.
Tell A.J.
You all right?
Yeah, yeah.
I had one of my
Coach Molinaro dreams.
Oh, yeah?
Were you unprepared, as usual?
Yeah.
As usual.
Yeah, Mr. Mol.
I wonder where he is now.
He wasn't such a bad guy.
A bad guy, no.
He actually took
an interest in you.
A lot of that was bullshit.
It was just his way of keeping
me from causing trouble.
Make his life easier.
I don't know about that.
I told him in the dream,
I am sort of a coach now.
That's a way of
looking at it, I guess.
Is it daylight where you are?
Nope. Where are you?
Looking out at Central Park.
All the lights are on.
You were in the dream too.
Oh, yeah?
I was on this horse.
Anyway, is-
is Artie all right?
'Cause in the dream,
he was the only alive guy
in this car full of dead guys.
I had dinner over there
last night.
Who'd you eat with?
Gab and Ro.
That's nice.
It was all right.
The veal was very dry.
Is that Esterhaz
next door barking?
Can you hear him?
Absolutely.
5:30 in the morning.
Someone ought to serve him
some veal... à la strychnine.
Stop it.
I'm serious.
Is it light where you are yet?
♪ Thanks for the times ♪
♪ That you've given me ♪
♪ The memories ♪
♪ Are all in mind ♪
♪ And now that we've come ♪
♪ To the end of our rainbow ♪
♪ There's something ♪
♪ I must say out loud ♪
♪ You're once, twice ♪
♪ Three times a lady ♪
♪ And I love you ♪
♪ Yes, you're once, twice ♪
♪ Three times a lady ♪
♪ And I love ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ I love ♪