♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon In your eyes ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
The fuck?
Oh!
Shit!
So, "Blundino,"
why you fuck me like this?
Fuck you talking about?
I got a whole leg
covered with Neosporin.
I just spent an hour
with the cops
explaining how it went down.
I no forget you
professional criminal.
Let me ask you something.
If I really wanted to rob you,
you think I'd have to put up
with this bullshit?
Well, just so you know.
I didn't take your truck.
I lost my study guide,
my fucking flash cards.
I'm sick of this fucking
prejudice against ex-cons.
I never hire you if I no need
Tony Soprano for union.
Not for him,
I show you the fucking window.
Great.
Hey, I thought you
liked the other one,
the Corn Pops.
Here, take it.
What, no juice either?
I told you, write it down,
I'll have the girl pick up
whatever you want.
She doesn't know the difference
between Fruit Roll-Ups
and Pop-Tarts.
I know, everybody's
an idiot to you.
You know they got these places
called supermarkets
where you go and you buy
the things that you like.
I'll reimburse you.
And when am I supposed
to do that?
Well, as far as I can tell,
you spend most of your time
on the phone,
or on the couch perfecting
that pissy look on your face.
Add coming home drunk,
sounds like you.
What the fuck did you say to me?
- Let the fuck go of me.
- Or what? Or what?
One of these days, you wait,
I'm gonna kick your fucking ass.
What's wrong with right now,
then, huh?
What's wrong with right now?
Come on!
Blah.
Now you got nothing.
- Thank you, Mary.
- You're welcome.
I hated to call you in,
but I got this midterm report
from Mr. Fiske,
Anthony's English teacher.
And, well, it doesn't hit
the mail for a few days,
and I thought maybe
we could get a jump on it
and avert any real crisis.
Wonderful, another crisis.
He's still well below
the "C" average he needs
for the colleges we discussed.
There is also an issue
with his five-paragraph essay.
Animal Farm?
Anthony submitted his
one-line topic late.
Then two drafts.
The first was apparently
sketchy.
The second, Fiske said,
was, uh, suspiciously cogent.
Plagiarism.
He thinks my son cheated?
He spent an entire Saturday
afternoon at the library.
I think it's obvious
what's going on here.
What do you mean?
Anyone else shows
sudden improvement,
he gets a gold star.
My son gets his act together
and suddenly he's a cheater?
I know what people think, Bob.
Italian-American, father
in the carting industry...
Are you suggesting
some sort of bias,
because that's a very
serious charge.
I have met this Mr. Fiske.
He is a cold fish.
Couldn't you or one of
the other teachers talk to him?
Tell him how hard A.J.'s trying?
Nothing will make
a better argument
than continued effort
on A.J.'s part.
But, hey, there's still a shot.
This semester's grade
is heavily weighted
on their term paper
on Lord of the Flies.
God, my stomach is in knots.
That's why I thought
it important that you come in.
Though it, uh...
did take me about an hour
to decide what to wear.
Me too.
Does that mean you've thought
about my dinner offer?
I probably shouldn't say this,
but I have thought about
nothing else since you called.
Well, we can't do justice
to any discussion
of Madame Bovary over the phone.
That's the thing, though.
That book was way over my head.
Why would you even be
interested in someone like me?
Because of just that.
I mean, who admits this stuff?
Not only are you
very attractive,
you're unpretentious,
you say what's on your mind.
I'm a big mouth. I see how that
would attract a man like you.
So should we grab a meal or not?
Well, there are other things
to think about.
My husband, for one.
Well, your husband's gonna
have to get used to the idea
that your life is moving on.
I'm not worried about my life.
Oh, you know what?
Call me naive,
but in this day and age,
I don't really think
your husband, if he found out,
is going to break
his son's teacher's legs.
Not to mention
how that would play
in the admissions office
at Arizona State.
I don't get it.
What's so funny about that?
Honey? Aren't you gonna
eat something?
Janice made lasagna.
It's not so great, but you
need something on your stomach.
We're gonna go.
Gotta stop at my mother's.
Gwen just told us how you met.
They let you use
the Internet in the can?
They let you post an ad.
I gotta read some of that shit.
I bet it's hysterical.
He's trying to concentrate.
Vascular physiology.
Neurotomy.
Shit.
T. made it out like
it was a big gym test.
Some people don't realize
what massage involves.
I'm practically doing two years
of medical school on my own.
One thing I learned in recovery,
other people's
definitions of you?
Sometimes they're more about
making themselves feel better.
You gotta define yourself.
Keep your eye on the tiger, man.
- See you, Ton'.
- Bye.
I suppose I could speak
with Monsignor Bava,
have him call his nephew
at K-Mart.
That'll fix us in
the Huggies department.
Well, the diaper drive
covers Clothe the Naked.
What do you say we work
on feed the hungry?
Ah, this looks delicious.
Thanks for inviting me, Carm.
Pleasant surprise, indeed.
So how goes life these days?
Actually, I think
I met somebody.
Really?
Just kind of happened.
We had been working
on this project together,
and suddenly we both realized
that there were
certain feelings.
And I like him as a person, too,
of course.
Don't get me wrong.
The funny thing is,
I was sure he was gay.
He sort of reminded me of you.
You know, he's an intellectual.
You know what I mean.
Anyway, we had been friends,
I guess,
and then he called
to ask me out,
and suddenly all
the formality dropped away.
When I saw him the other day,
he looked at me
with this intensity.
Now, I know it's wrong,
but the truth is,
I feel it, too.
You know, if you really want
to discuss this,
I think we should include Tony
in the conversation as well.
Why--why are you sounding,
I don't know, kind of hostile?
I'm not.
Perhaps that's your sin talking.
This is none of Tony's business.
Who knows what he's been up to,
and not just during
the separation either.
That doesn't change the fact
you made a commitment
to each other before God.
Maybe you should send the papal
nuncio to Tony and remind him of that.
Why am I the only one
held to any kind of standards?
And for that matter,
if this is wrong,
why did God put this man
in my life?
Is it God that put him there,
or is there a particular
need you have right now?
See, I never understand this.
Didn't he put the need there?
Say when, signor.
You! Office!
5:15. I haven't punched in yet.
This is still my time.
Yeah?
I give you a hard time
about my truck the other day.
Cops find two kids.
Feel free to apologize any time.
Anyway, they investigate.
Could be joyride.
But I think maybe behind it
is my cousin at Northside.
- Do you know if they found my books?
- Who knows.
You study hard
for massage, yeah?
The licensing test
is pretty hard.
Huge failure rate.
If you pass,
then what you do with this?
Be a professional masseur.
You no think
of "massagie ghageh"?
You know, small sauna.
Yeah, I could see it.
Four or five tables,
soothing atmosphere.
Pipe in a little Keith Jarrett.
First thing I get
stuck with you I think,
oh, shit goddamn it.
He lazy American and criminal.
No good for Kim.
But you work for Kim and future.
Like Korean people.
I wouldn't say that.
I come from Korea.
Only new shoes
and Uncle's address.
Worse than prison.
But I become
"jah-soo-suhng-gah."
The boss.
That's why I try to help you.
Help me how?
What are you talking about?
I stake you the money
in the storefront.
I got a travel agency
in mini mall
over at West Caldwell.
Shitty business with a fucking
three-year lease.
You know, my daughter,
very interest, in massage.
Physical therapy.
Top of two-thirds class.
Good for her.
It's a tough nut to crack.
She no like physical
therapy no more.
Cripple people make her sad.
Now, she watch TV,
live at home, do nothing.
You pass test then you,
me, my daughter,
we make the big success journey.
Okay?
Jesus.
Yeah, all right.
I-I don't know what to say, Kim.
Thanks.
I laid it out for him.
He wants to move back here,
it's gotta be with
your full approval.
This was your idea?
It was mutual.
He's upset because he don't
get the kind of cereal he likes.
He threw it in the sink.
How am I supposed to focus
at school with no breakfast?
I got dizzy.
I'm sorry, I don't
see why the two of you
can't work this out
between yourselves.
Maybe I don't
wanna live in a place
where people use violence
against children.
Violence? You're lucky I didn't
put my shoe up your ass.
You see? Now that's abuse.
I know what my rights are.
I can call social services
and they'll send a case worker.
Go ahead!
He'll get the other shoe!
- This is demoralizing.
- Well, now maybe you see...
That a son of mine
would even consider
calling in the authorities.
- Go ahead, live where you want.
- Fine.
Family meeting?
Try to stay awake, A.J.
Keep walking.
I-I just want my old room back.
You wanted to live
with your father, A.J.
- Live with your decision.
- I don't like it there.
That's funny,
I thought I was the problem.
I make you miserable, remember?
- Well, I never said that.
- You did.
Absolutely.
For me to even consider
having you back,
we're gonna have to establish
some nonnegotiable ground rules.
- Like what kind?
- Let your mother talk.
First and foremost,
school comes first.
That means putting the brakes
on your social life:
parties, phone calls, Devin.
You are at a crisis point
grade-wise,
so you will make sure your work
is done on time and correctly.
All right.
I will not tolerate cursing.
After 16 years of uninterrupted
potty mouth from you people,
- I get slammed?
- This is my house.
You will treat me with respect.
Well, is that it?
I want you to involve me
in your life a little.
Fine.
All right.
Go get your stuff from the car.
We played that just right.
Think his time
over there with me
whipped him into shape a little.
Hmm.
Think you'll see a difference.
Which muscles attach
to the coracoid process?
Okay, I fucking know this.
It's on the tip of my tongue.
Oh, fucking study hall again.
Vito, where the fuck
is my Tupperware?
Keep your shirt on.
My wife's bringing it down
this afternoon.
Pectoralis minor and
the coracobrachialis, of course.
And...
Come on.
Even I know this.
- Fuck, fine, what is it?
- Biceps!
Fuck.
Oh, fuck, I knew that.
My mind's all over the place.
Fear knocked at the door.
Faith answered.
There was no one there.
Why do you wanna do this?
So you can touch
a bunch a strangers?
You really skeeve
the human body, don't you?
You like this so much,
let me ask you a question.
Why do pissing,
shitting and fucking
all happen within
a two-inch radius?
Everybody asks that, Paulie.
There's no answer for it.
They're all sources of pleasure,
though.
Get the fuck outta here!
I know this shit, then the next
minute it's gone.
I don't know
how you do it, working full time.
If your parole officer's
a problem,
give our guy Jimmy Curran
a call.
- He's a supervisor.
- It's not that.
It's just all this pressure
now that I got this opportunity.
Sungyon Kim, my boss,
he's gonna back me on a whole
storefront operation.
The Korean?
You're looking for money,
why not come to me?
Well, this is different.
This self-owned business shit's
like a religion to these people.
Plus, the guy sees
something in me.
You know, in some ways,
the whole prison thing
is not that different
from being an immigrant.
Word to the wise,
remember Pearl Harbor.
We really were
the last people in there.
At least they were
subtle about it.
Was it stacking of chairs
or the running the vacuum?
Relax.
Sorry.
Madame Bovary.
It's a first edition.
Well, Modern Library's
first edition.
Thank you, that is so sweet.
Honestly, though, I don't know.
The story's very slow.
Nothing really happens.
I think he could've said
what he has to say with
a lot less words.
Outside, nothing happens.
But inside,
she has these extremes
of boredom and exhilaration.
You should try it again.
And what a wonderful thing
to have in a den.
You know, you look really
beautiful in this light.
I don't do this a lot.
Do what?
Sitting in a car, with a man,
not really knowing what to do.
Or if I should at all.
And feeling like some teenager
which was, believe it or not...
I have to tell you...
I haven't been with anyone.
You're a virgin?
This is my lucky night.
Stop with the jokes.
I'm so glad you're here.
So, how was it?
Oh, cut it out.
So, what is Abelard and Heloise?
It looks religious.
I just like to read in there.
It's the classic story.
A 12th-century scholar
falls in love
with his underage student.
Gets her pregnant.
God, in the 12th century.
And they're found out.
And her uncle, the abbot,
has him castrated.
It's timeless, really.
Even though he becomes
a monk and she a nun,
their passion burns on
through these incredible letters
through the rest of their lives.
You, with these books.
Education should never stop.
It enriches all aspects of life.
I know.
I wish someone could
convince A.J. of that.
I keep thinking he could
start over in college,
but who knows if he's
even gonna get the chance?
He will.
All our students matriculate.
You gotta be fucking kidding.
No way.
Why do they take so long?
All they have to do
is spit out the results.
5-6-2-4-7-3-7-32-11.
That's me. Blundetto.
I'm only authorized
to inform you
that your score meets or exceeds
the required minimum
for licensure,
and you're now board-certified
in massage and bodywork
by the state of New Jersey.
Honey, you passed.
You passed.
Oh, Jesus.
I couldn't have done it alone.
Oh, my God, look at you.
You did it, baby. You did it.
Bless me, Father,
for I have sinned.
It's been a month
since my last confession.
Carmela?
I had sex with that man.
I know we talked
about commitment,
and the sacrament of marriage.
But...
I don't know.
You sound remorseful.
I am.
I'm also confused, though.
The truth is, I have been
walking around on a cloud,
like Maria in West Side Story.
It's not right.
Have you heard of
Abelard and Eloise?
I think it's "Heloise,"
and from what I remember
it ends badly.
I know, exactly.
But, something in me
has been reawakened.
And even if it never
happens again with this man,
just knowing that feeling
of passion again.
I don't know if it's ever
gonna go away.
I'll need it.
If it never happens again?
Carmela, I can't
absolve you of a sin
you're going to continue
to commit.
You need to show resolve,
a firm purpose to change.
Yeah, I know, I know.
So this man takes you
to restaurants,
fulfills certain
physical desires.
Tells jokes.
But will he be there
beyond the here and now?
When you're too old
to walk to the bathroom,
will he be there to help you?
What, and you think Tony will?
Carmela, you took a vow.
You both did.
For your penance, I want you
to do something kind for Tony.
I don't think I can, Father.
Then pray for him.
Not only that God
will touch his heart,
but that he'll touch
yours as well.
It's not much now, of course,
but it's a pretty
flexible space.
Plus you got the dog groomer
next door,
in case your Korean friend
wants some lunch.
You know they really do
eat dogs.
I mean, not all of them,
but I asked Kim.
Aw, Jesus Christ.
So I'm thinking of building
a row of rooms here
with different themes.
Asian for shiatsu,
a little Danish thing
for Rolfing,
even though technically
it's Swedish.
Well, sounds like
it's all coming together.
Look, Ton',
I know you're disappointed.
What the fuck you talking about?
The way things turned out
since I left the can.
Going civilian.
Over here I'm gonna put
an oasis with big plants,
like a waiting area
for the customers.
Could buy some $30 hand cream
while they look at one of those
fountains with the koi in it.
Oh, I can get you the koi.
Really? Giant carp?
How the fuck do you get that?
It's done.
Don't give it another thought.
Tony, you here?
- Yeah!
- Out front.
Hey. I came by to get the keys.
I would have gone
by the laundry,
but my dad's such
a hard-on at work.
Tell me about it.
Amanda, this is my cousin, Tony.
- Hey.
- Hey, how are you?
Hey, you believe there's
a dog groomer there?
In case somebody needs a snack?
Place is nice.
A little paint, maybe...
Amanda, this is
my cousin Christopher.
Hey.
So, I met this guy
at a club on Canal.
He says he can hook us up
with ginseng, fake rhino,
nerve tea, all that herbal shit.
We could keep it up front
with the koi thing,
- if we're still doing that.
- Koi's taken care of.
Well, I gotta book.
Nice meeting you guys.
What's she here for,
happy endings?
She's not gonna
do massage at all.
She's Kim's daughter.
She's trying to find herself.
She'll do the books and shit.
Oh. Nice ass.
The ceiling tiles
come right out,
so I can install
the sound system myself.
Think you could put in a word
with number one daughter there?
- For what?
- You know.
Get some of that
kung-pao coochie.
You fuckin' guys,
this is important to me.
Sex agrees with you.
You look great.
You're being discreet, right?
Well, sneaking around
is actually half the fun.
It's like you have
this secret, you know,
you wanna scream to the world...
Yeah, but do yourself
a favor, though, huh?
Yeah.
So how was it?
I will say that
he took his time.
Oh, you're not
getting off that easy.
Come on, details. Come on.
Hello there.
- Hey, A.J.
- Hey, Aunt Ro.
How was school?
It sucked.
Mr. Wegler pulled me
out of language lab
to go over my term paper notes.
I didn't have my stuff with me,
so he puts his faggy hand
on my shoulder and says,
"Do your best."
Well, that's his job,
to get you into college.
Or maybe he's just a big homo.
Could be.
I'm making ziti for dinner.
Go start your assignments.
I will call you.
Could I watch TV first?
Promise me
you're gonna work later.
- But you gotta help me.
- I will.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, my Jackie...
Oh, honey.
They never caught those
goddamn Chinks who killed him.
Oh, my God, it hurts.
So I'm finding the other copy
when Gene, the actuary,
completely unloads on me.
Jerk.
Like yelling's gonna
make me do anything
but screw up more.
You know, you have to remember
that when you're the boss.
The boss.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Jerks. Garbage pails
are right there.
Come on.
- Holy fuck.
- What?
Oh, my God, is it a fetus?
Oh my God!
Shh!
It's crack. Or crank, maybe.
- They were drug dealers?
- Yeah.
They were probably thinking
they were being tailed
by the cops.
Honey, your parole.
Happy? Come on.
I have never seen
that much money before.
There's gotta be 10, 12 grand.
Look at this.
You're doubly blessed.
You're right. Kim, and now this.
I am gonna buy you a ring.
You are the sweetest,
sweetest man.
But you should put it
into the business.
See, I gotta start
thinking like that.
It's a learning curve.
Well, it seems to say here
that this Piggy represents
intellectualism
over the physical.
So maybe the eyeglasses
are symbolic.
And that's a good topic
for section two in your outline.
A.J., wake up!
I'm not gonna do this by myself.
How are you gonna
finish this paper?
It's not gonna write itself.
So now this so-called bag.
You sure it wasn't
on some old lady's arm?
I can't believe
she thought it was a baby.
People do that shit.
Twelve grand?
Madonna mi.
How many guys you gotta jerk off
on a massage table to make that?
I don't know, what do you
charge without the table?
Cristal, gentlemen?
Keep it coming, honey.
From now on, anytime somebody
steps in a pile of shit,
it'll be known as a Blundetto.
To the Blundetto!
Oh...
I wasn't ready.
♪ Cross over the river ♪
♪ Beyond every cloud ♪
♪ She's passed the wind ♪
♪ Blowing loud ♪
♪ Over the mountain ♪
♪ A girl waits for me ♪
My God, you scared me.
What are you doing here?
Jesus. Nice greeting.
How are you? Everything okay?
A.J. left this in his room.
Thought he might
need it to turn in.
Did you even look at this?
Who the hell is Anne Dunham?
How the hell should I know?
Well, she's obviously
some girl who was an expert
on Lord of the Flies
three years ago.
This is an "A" -plus paper.
Since when do you eat duck?
I can't believe
he would do this.
Neither can I, considering
how tight he is with money.
That's not what I meant. What?
Oh, you think he bought this?
Goddamn it.
Hello?
Hi, I was just laying
here thinking about you.
What are you wearing?
Yes, hello, Mr. Wegler, hi.
I'm afraid now
is not a good time.
I'm serious. I wanna know.
Uh, well, yes, thank you very much.
I will make sure
that he brings it in.
Okay, goodbye, Mr. Wegler.
I made reservations at that
crab place down by the shore.
Dinner and a little
night swimming.
Right, okay, thank you.
What'd that fag want?
Jesus Christ, Tony,
everybody's a fag to you.
You know, maybe you're a fag.
You ever think about that?
Can I help it if I know one
when I see one?
Oh, really? What are the signs?
Education? Culture?
Sucking a guy's cock
usually tips me off.
How do you know
who sucks whose cock?
What, do you got
a little secret?
And what do you care anyway
if somebody's gay?
It must be some
big fear of yours,
or you wouldn't
talk about it so much.
I forget now. What part of hell
did you say they go to?
Are they with the abortion
doctors or the child molesters?
That was a long time ago.
Now you're all
open-minded that you got
a couple of friends
that are bologna smokers.
- Right?
- What the fuck are you doing?
Going for a swim.
What, you leave your goddamn
socks here? Your underpants?
♪ A girl waits for me ♪
Hey, that's some beautiful suit.
I had to get it.
It went with the shoes.
- Whose got those? Vito's guy?
- Vasily's, custom-made.
The only thing I ever found
in the street is my first wife.
Dealer has 20.
- Son of a bitch.
- Oh!
I just took a beating at craps.
How you guys doing?
Pocahontas here is scalping us.
What's the matter?
Oh, just nothing.
I don't know.
I just keep thinking about
A.J. and that girl's paper.
Oh, it's a pretty common thing,
Carm, really.
Honestly, you know,
the important thing
is you took a stand.
A lot of parents just take it
in stride or even condone it.
It's just the cheating,
you know.
It's just not like him.
He's always done his work.
Poorly, a lot of the time,
and late.
But he always did it.
He never cheated.
Well, wait.
Didn't I read
somewhere in his record
that he stole a test
at Verbum Dei?
Oh, please, no,
that was just acting out.
He was with a bad crowd.
They were there to vandalize
the science lab,
but it was locked,
so they stole some tests.
Well, I was a late bloomer too.
Union College
took a chance on me
because they saw
that I had potential,
but I wasn't that mature.
That's all this is.
A.J.'s just fighting
to keep pace
with the kids
who seem further ahead.
You know, you ask me,
I think he was driven
to cheating.
It's that Mr. Fiske.
He is ridiculous
with the pressure.
I mean, how hopeless
would you feel
if you really worked on
something and still got a "D"?
I have been there, Carm.
You're worrying for nothing,
I promise.
I have thought about this
all day.
You know, I almost called you
from the faculty parking lot.
- Oh, Bob.
- What?
Stop. Bob, I...
What's the matter?
I can't right now, I'm sorry.
I'm too upset.
Carmela, stay.
What are you doing?
What kind of mother am I?
I mean, look at us.
You realize under the laws of
the Church, I am still married?
The Church?
I can't do this tonight.
I'm sorry.
Jesus, Carmela, come on.
♪ Thrill me, thrill me ♪
♪ Walk me down the lane
Where shadows will be ♪
♪ Will be ♪
♪ Hiding lovers
Just the same... ♪
Okay, thanks.
It was a fucking blast.
You sure you don't wanna eat?
Steak and eggs up by Skyway's.
- Ah, I can't.
- Come on, shut the door.
I'm gonna mang', then hit
the sack for the next 14 hours.
Hey. I thought once
they move you upstairs
you get to leave early.
No such luck. Got a second?
The Soprano kid.
How's he doing?
Got his paper yet?
Well, the usual.
Solidly below average.
So, what, a "C"?
Well, no, that's a little
generous for 10% insight,
90% CliffNotes.
This is an important class, Tom.
Anything less than a "C"
is gonna blow that kid out
at Arizona State.
You think it's gonna make
that much of a difference?
As Dean of College Admissions
and head of your department,
I happen to know it's a fact.
He's doing his best.
Well, like my dad used to say,
the world needs
ditch diggers, too.
Let me ask you something.
How is floating
this kid a C-minus
gonna fuck things up here?
A.J. Soprano's
a spoiled lox, Bob.
He'd be lucky to go
to a trade school.
It's a D-plus.
Tom, cut him a break.
So, what does it mean to the kid
who really breaks his ass
in here
if Fredo Corleone can
get a "C" 'cuz you asked?
Is that what this is about?
His background?
Good night.
I'll be working
over at the place.
That's good dedication.
Way to go.
See, regular people
need a place to relax too.
They can't just hop on a plane
to the Bahamas, right?
Hey, guys, what do you
think of Daddy's business?
Jason, Justin,
I'm talking to you.
- I like it.
- Yeah, it's nice.
Well, maybe someday
when this thing takes off,
you guys can work here, like as
a summer job or something.
Would you like that?
Working with your old man?
Sure.
All right, put those away.
You gotta do your homework,
before I take you back,
or your mom's gonna kill me.
Mom says we need helmets
to ride the scooters you got us.
We'll stop at Sports Authority.
Come on, do your homework.
Where?
I don't know.
Here, on the floor over there.
Hold it like this. Ready?
That was fast.
I took a shortcut.
Did you ever think
of painting that ceiling?
Maybe.
How about a glow-in-the-dark
solar system
like I had in college?
I was thinking blue, maybe.
You know, like when you stick
your hand in the Caribbean.
Oh, yeah.
You think Union College
is a good place of A.J.?
I don't know. Could be.
You know,
maybe you could tell them
how he's a lot like you were
when you were his age.
That's a thought.
So, have you ever been
to the Caribbean?
Yeah, Barbados, once. Years ago.
Oh, it was beautiful.
Yeah, it is.
Maybe you could bring up
the fact that he has A.D.D.,
because it's not
the stigma it once was.
That's true.
It isn't.
Where you going?
Mmm.
Faculty lunch, right?
Patty D'Amico brought them.
What's the matter? You okay?
Maybe we should take a time-out.
What?
Really? Why?
Because every time I think about
putting the arm on Tom Fiske,
I wanna poke my eyes out
with a knitting needle.
What does that have
to do with us?
I just think we should, uh...
not do this.
Oh. Oh, no.
Here, tell me.
I don't know any
other way to put this.
I have been thinking, and...
I don't know, I...
I think you're a user, Carmela.
What?
Maybe you saw
an opportunity in me,
and you just took
what you needed.
Oh, that is not true.
I am here because
I enjoy being with you.
It was wonderful, in fact.
Yeah, it was.
I mean, it is, I know.
How could asking someone you're
with for help be using them?
That's what people do.
Bob, this hurts.
Oh, my.
Oh, my stomach. I feel sick.
You strong-armed me using
the only weapon you have:
your pussy.
How dare you
talk to me that way?
Okay, let's pretend you don't
know what I'm talking about.
I don't.
Of course, I don't have
a fucking master's degree.
Leaving me with a massive
hard-on the other night
and then practically
attacking me sexually
after you got what you wanted.
You know what, Bob?
You are fucked up.
You need help, you know that?
Fucking idiot I am.
Take it easy.
Believe it or not,
I thought you cared about me.
I just thought you
should know how I feel.
Fuck you!
You better watch your step.
Jesus Christ, it's 4:00 a.m.
Okay, boys, hands on the table.
Full boat.
Jesus Christ.
Three fucking jacks over here.
You just keep jacking,
my friend.
That's it for me, tapioca.
You blew the whole 12 grand?
What are you stupid?
I got 400 left.
Punch in in two hours.
There's no sense going home.
Fuck.
Hello?
Hey, hon,
I'm over at your mom's.
- Great.
- Roadway Xpress
delivered five massage tables.
There? They had that address
by mistake.
I told them to deliver here.
They're still in the boxes.
I looked inside, though.
They're pretty spiff.
That Salamanca fabric
was worth it.
It's like leather, almost.
Great.
What's the matter?
This shit gives me a headache.
Details and all that stuff.
Oh, you, it's no big,
for gosh sake,
- we'll get Rudy's truck.
- Maybe I have a brain tumor.
Honey, you don't.
This headache in my jaw.
I read it in Time magazine.
It's really not that likely, jeez.
I gotta get back
to the painting,
or I'll never get the fuck
out of here tonight.
I am so fucking sick and tired
of your gambling and complaining.
I've got a headache.
When I think of me
waiting outside that
prison for you to come out
sometimes I wanna vomit.
I am sick! I'm evil!
Hey, Henry Ford.
Big entrepreneur.
I like color.
My friend, Pak, come by?
Fix the toilet?
It's not fixed.
He's gotta come back
with a fucking part.
Oh. Pak, he good plumber.
Right over here,
"Wes-a Calwell".
"Wes Calwel, Wes Calwel."
West Caldwell.
So, partner,
we open in three day, huh?
Fucking stroll in.
I'm over here
busting my fucking ass!
You fucking crazy?
Work in your fucking laundry,
all fucking day!
Fucking scam artist.
Hyah!
Fuck.
Ah!
Fuck!
The pole is bent.
Somebody been
punching this door?
You had a man around,
you wouldn't need to call me.
Yeah, right.
You're still young, Mel.
A good-looking woman.
There's no reason you shouldn't
move on with your life,
if that's what you want.
Well, there actually
was somebody.
- And he seemed very nice.
- Oh, that's good.
He was a wolf
in sheep's clothing.
He made all these accusations
about my character.
Whatever I say, whatever I do,
because I was married
to a man like Tony,
my motives will always
be called into question.
Well...
Hey. Sit down.
You want something?
What'd you do?
Back. Fucking job.
A work-related injury.
So, here's the thing.
You mentioned you might
need someone
to run the swag airbags.
Bring me a vodka rocks,
and get me some kind
of a cushion, will you?
What happened with
the massage parlor?
It's hard doing business
with strangers.
♪ I got a heart
Full of trouble ♪
♪ A house full of sin ♪
♪ Things are bad
As they ever been ♪
♪ If trouble were money ♪
♪ I'd have more money
Than any man should ♪
♪ I'm open for business
In your neighborhood ♪
♪ The blues is my business ♪
♪ And business is good ♪
♪ If I had a dollar
For every broken heart ♪
♪ I'd be drinking fine wine
And eating caviar ♪
♪ If trouble were money ♪
♪ I'd have more money
Than any man should, yeah ♪
♪ I'm open for business
In your neighborhood ♪
♪ The blues is my business ♪
♪ And business is good, yeah ♪
♪ Business ♪
♪ And business is good ♪
♪ The blues is my business
And business is good ♪
♪ The blues is my business ♪
♪ I'm open for business
In your neighborhood ♪
♪ The blues is my business
♪ And business is good ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Oh, all right, yeah ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪