♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good,
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon In your eyes ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy, brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
Ah, that's so funny!
No, it isn't!
You just poked me in the eye!
Well, you poked me first.
I can't find the thing.
Here.
I don't know what the fuck
happened to the DeWalt.
Everything disappears
around here.
Especially now that I'm outta
the house, she lets everything go.
Aah!
Stop, stop, Uncle Tony!
It's freezing cold!
Uncle Tony, knock it off!
She wants to talk to me
about somethin'.
Thanks for havin' us
up here, Ton'.
Jason, don't put pine cones
in the filter!
Hell's the matter with you?
No, Dad, watch me!
He's hitting me!
Hey, what did I say?
They will probably
go through their entire lives
not knowing that
their father's sperm
was smuggled out of jail
to get Nancy pregnant.
It was the least I could do.
I just remembered what happened
to the power drill.
Pardon me?
I loaned it
to your cousin, Brian.
And he never gave it--
What's the matter?
I don't know.
Is this one of your attacks?
No, it...
I think it's just indigestion.
It's goin' away.
I had an attack... full blown.
- What did your therapist say?
- I don't see her no more.
- Why not?
- You think you're the only one
that has to cut back
on shit they need?
'Cause of the separation?
Now what's on your mind?
Mr. Wegler wants us
to come in and discuss
A.J.'s lousy
academic performance.
Is this the same Wegler?
From last year, the riccione
with the Billy Budds?
A.J. got him
as a college advisor.
I told this kid to start
crackin' the books.
Was he supposed to do that
after he got back
from the Nets game
you took him to
on a school night?
It's gotta be hard for him,
this situation with us.
Why don't you
cut him some slack?
No, that's your department.
I get to be
the prison warden over here
while you indulge him.
With the iPod, the drums.
Oh, again with the drums!
Encourage extracurricular
activity, you said.
Brand new drums, just like that?
Don't even look
in the classifieds.
Why don't you just tell me
when the school meetin' is.
'Cause I don't have to listen
to this shit anymore.
That's why we're separated!
Oh, are you kidding me, Tony?
That is not why!
Jase?
Were you knocking?
Hi, Lorraine. I'm Billy.
The fuck?!
Jason!
Ow! No!
Aah!
Oh, no!
You were warned, Lorraine.
The money goes up to John.
Fuck!
Lorraine Calluzio
and the kid, Jason.
Fuckin' Philly Leotardo!
She told me he warned her.
About givin' us
points of her take.
Phil's a pimple.
It's goddamn Johnny Sack.
It's his message
to the other captains,
that fuckin' animal.
Take it easy.
Fuck that.
Rusty?
Car's here.
I'm telling you, Carmine.
We go all out, we'll steamroll
right over John.
And I predict the guys on the
street in Brooklyn and Queens,
they'll welcome us
as fuckin' heroes.
It'll be easy.
It's a fuckin' declaration
of war by Johnny, if ya ask me.
- Hey!
- Ho...
There he is.
Let me kiss the ring.
How about the one
in the center of my ass?
- Hey!
- Feech.
- Good to see ya, baby.
- Good to see you.
Hello there, kid.
Good to see ya.
- Hey...
- Hey, how ya doin', Feech?
How are ya? How are ya?
Just, uh, talkin' about
that mess over in New York.
Sounds to me like
your friend John
wants to force
Little Carmine's hand.
In my day, the top spot
would've gone to Little Carmine,
unless he was actually retarded
or crippled or somethin'.
He's the son.
Come on, when was that?
Yeah?
- Vodka rocks.
- Thank you, dear.
Anybody else?
We need anything else, uh,
one of the kids'll come out.
Ton', you didn't have any lunch.
- You want a sandwich?
- No, I'm all right. Thanks.
Adriana, hold on a second.
Tommy Pinto's cumare, eh,
when I was comin' up
she had the long legs,
up to here, like that.
Famous beauty, smart as a whip.
My compliments.
Oh, that'd be beautiful.
- Thank you, baby.
- You drove Tommy Pinto?
I was at the Clam Broth House
that night he beat that longshoreman
to death over a corner table.
No shit.
Here we go. Memory lane.
It's important these young guys
know the history.
Tell 'em about the time, uh,
Tony and Jackie Aprile
knocked over your card game.
Oh, that he doesn't
like to talk about.
I heard this.
This is a great fuckin' story.
He should be dead by now.
They bust in,
couple of fuckin' punks.
Guns out. Bad guys.
This one is fuckin' scared!
First of all, it was my game.
Feech has forgiven,
even if he hasn't forgotten.
But it's a great yarn,
right, Feech?
Yeah.
Actually, it brings me
to my business.
Fellas, you wanna
give us a minute here?
Yeah.
So, what's up?
I came to ask for my game back.
It's my uncle's game now, Feech.
Yeah, right, your uncle's.
You'll still keep
the lion's share of the rake.
I'm in a way just askin'
if I can run it for ya.
Why would I need that?
Eleven years, I ran it.
No fights, no raids.
Not to mention that maybe
I got it comin'?
Considering how
it could've gone for you
after you took the game down,
if I had been a prick about it.
Or if his old man
didn't have so many friends.
I'll give you 20%, but you
gotta rent the house from me.
I could throw some
high rollers your way.
Friends of mine.
All right.
Let me get outta here
before I keep talkin'
and fuck this up. Jesus.
Thank you, Don Antonio.
He's a strunz.
He's a busybody, that's all.
He's an egomaniac, Ton'.
Always was, always will be.
Nothin's ever good enough--
praise, money.
Comes in this fuckin' office,
starts orderin' people around?
He's old.
How do ya think that feels?
Can I go to the Mudvayne
concert or not?
Well, I've been trying
to think of a reason
to let you stay overnight
in New York with your friends,
but I'm afraid
it's not gonna happen.
Todd's mother already
made the arrangements.
And she said it'd be
better than us driving home.
She's not your mother.
Yeah, I know. Believe me.
Isn't life unfair?
So, we're at
the Peppermint Lounge,
when in walks these two
stewardesses from Braniff.
Everybody's in? Aces high.
Your action, Mr. Taylor.
- Two hundred.
- Hesh?
They're sitting at the bar,
we send 'em over
a bottle of Dom.
Next thing you know,
we're in the hotel room.
Me, Frankie, and the two broads.
I see ya, raise ya three.
- Your mother.
- But this one,
this little pothead from Texas,
she fucked me dry.
But she still wanted more!
She's fuckin' nuts!
So I'm wearin'
these pointy featherweights,
and I stick the toe in,
and I'm fuckin' her with it.
I don't know where
this story's heading,
but I guess
we should all be grateful
he wasn't wearing white bucks.
The maid walks in,
She says, "What's going on?"
And I say--
Ante up, boys.
- Ho! Hey!
- Hello, girls!
- Hey.
- Hey, Ton'.
Sir Lawrence
from the Meadowlands.
Your Highness, how are you?
Tony, let me introduce
Bernie Brillstein.
Didja get my list of toys?
Hey, Ton'.
Oh, my cousin!
Kinda high-stakes for you, no?
Feech fronted my action.
And thank you for
not humiliating me.
Isn't there something
in your parole about
hanging out with
degenerates like this?
Aww...
- Come on, he gets away with anything.
Last time his parole officer
made the unannounced visit,
he gave him a massage!
So how's Lady Luck
treatin' you, huh?
Jesus fuckin' Christ, how many
times this guy gotta say hello?
What, did I interrupt
one of your impermeable stories?
Go ahead.
So, we have these girls
in the hotel room.
Long story short,
I got my shoe in her snatch.
Then it falls off and she
keels over. Che puzz'.
Fuck it. This hand's
from thalidomide.
Three ladies, gentlemen.
- Ahh.
- Take it. Thank you.
The rich get richer.
So, Doc,
how's the plans for the wedding?
Please. It's not
a wedding planner anymore.
It's an environment
and event coordinator.
What the hell.
She's my only daughter.
She and Iris
have their hearts set
on making the Vows column
of the Sunday New York Times.
Featured Couple of the Week.
Our publicist
is lookin' for a hook.
Turns out that Gillian's law
degree from Harvard means bupkis.
Everybody's got that or better.
If it was a black couple
or a gay couple,
- they'd be in.
- Hmm.
My wife calls
the Times wedding section
the "ladies sport page."
So Ira, who's the lucky guy?
Jeremy Silverman.
Puppeteer. Children's
Television Workshop.
Father's Asa Silverman,
head of commercial paper
at Goldman Sachs.
Upper East Side.
I didn't get my invitation.
Fuck you.
That was good.
You told me to be
sure to let you know
- when it was a quarter of.
- Thank you, Mary.
So with Wesleyan
as your fallback,
I think we're in
pretty good shape.
Straight A's at
Middlebury's Language Camp,
can't sneeze at that.
And your blues folkloric studies
in Mississippi last summer
have an almost community service
spin to them.
I just wish he had the
minority thing going for him.
If we can just nudge
Lem's verbals past 760
on the next round, he can
basically write his own ticket.
I'm stoked.
Appreciate your help.
Folks?
So lemme guess.
He called the English teacher
Daddy-O.
Oh.
Thing is...
we are rapidly approaching
crisis mode here
with these grades.
And time is of the essence.
Could I ask a question?
I handed in
my final list of colleges.
- Did you get that?
- Yes. We talked about this.
So... Ramapo and Trenton State.
And our reach schools, University
of Arizona and Arizona State.
I'm gonna take him out there after I
drive him around to the ones in New Jersey.
If either of the Arizonas is
what he's got his heart set on,
he's not gonna get in
with these grades.
And I know about football,
Anthony,
That's our ace in the hole.
- He says he's tryin' his best.
- SAT-wise, 505 and 430,
uh, I think we can
edge up the math
into the fives the next round,
providing Anthony feels
he can bear down and focus.
He's had trouble
with that before.
Remember, Carm, when
they thought he had ADD?
- You didn't tell me that.
- Anthony, what do you say
you head on back to class,
let us talk?
But if I'm learning disabled,
I get unlimited time on my SATS.
Is that true?
Let's talk about that later.
So, you had time to talk
directly to Dr. Rapke
about last week's
testing results?
Yes. She said Anthony has
good interpersonal skills,
she said his affect was--
where is it?--
"constricted," she called it,
but that was normal
for a teenager.
And all in all he seemed
to be handling the split well.
This is not to say I don't get a
ration of shit in every conversation.
Pardon my French.
Well, still, uh,
there's this thing
with his grades.
Do you think it would be
of benefit to him
to see a psychologist
on a regular basis?
You don't approve
of therapy, Mr. Soprano?
People use it as a crutch.
And I always wonder
what happened to Gary Cooper,
the strong, silent type.
Well, Gary Cooper wasn't
a 16-year-old boy.
He was at one time.
I'm gonna have to agree with my
husband here, Mr. Wegler.
We sent our daughter to an
adolescent developmentalist,
and it was a disaster.
I know my son. He's just lazy.
We're gonna get him
a different SAT tutor,
and I'm gonna stay on him
and he's gonna work harder.
And that's that.
They said I might be
learning disabled.
Hey, didn't he tell you
to go to class?
What's going on, Mary?
Domenica Paolini
and Sasha Caputo,
they were on their way to school
this morning and they hit a tree.
Nick is dead. Sasha's in a coma.
What's that?
It was here when I got here.
Okay, if a million zeroes
can be written
on the front and back
of a sheet of paper,
how many sheets of paper
do you need
for a googol of zeroes?
Whoa!
Oh man, oh baby, an Xterra SE!
It's loaded.
3.3 liter supercharged.
- What, this is mine?
- Yeah.
- You are unbelievable.
- Sticker's still on it.
He doesn't have
enough distractions?
After what happened
to those kids at his school?
Thing's got sensors
in the seatbelts.
It's part of Nissan's
triple safety philosophy.
- Nice ride.
- Are you leaving?
- Hour's up.
- You're not gettin' in?
This is so deck.
What is this, Bose?
Yeah, six-CD changer.
It's got surround sound.
I feel safer already.
Carmela, this car is a tank.
What's the matter?
SUVs eat up more of the ozone.
So you wanna be the sucker in a
regular car that gets decapitated?
I'm gonna catch some shit
at school for this.
So what do you wanna do?
Screw it. Can we take it out?
Yeah, we can take it out. Once.
Then this baby sits
in the garage
till you pull your grades
up to a "C."
- What?
- You heard your father.
I was talkin' to him, not you.
I gotta put dinner on.
Tony, I have bills for you.
You better be nice
to your mother.
She's got the keys
till your grades are up.
I'll be right back.
The car is a motivational tool.
The carrot and the stick--
you gotta do both!
I could strangle him sometimes.
He can be so hateful.
The smart mouth is not good.
That's minor, believe me.
God, what happened to him?
He was always the sweet one.
He had the concept of sharing
before any of
the other toddlers...
Well, Meadow was always sharper,
but I remember
the same thing with her.
It's like watchin'
an angel fall.
What are you, cryin'?
Here's the tutor, in
writing like you had to have.
I had to call RotoRooter. That's a
cheap sound system for the media room.
- Why should I pay for that?
- Because you took the last one.
Your little movie connoisseur
friends, they're still meetin'?
- At least I have friends.
- The fuck's that supposed to mean?
C'mon, Tony, you just have
a bunch of flunkies.
What do you know about it?
They compliment you
on your new shoes,
they tell you that
you're not going bald.
You think they really care?
You're the boss.
They're scared of you.
They have to kiss your ass.
- Laugh at your stupid jokes.
- Well what about Artie, then?
- You're turning into a friggin' cynic.
- Yeah, whatever.
What do I give a shit
if they're scared or whatever?
I'm runnin' a fuckin' business,
not a popularity contest.
"I've been thinking,
and I apologize
for my use of fowl language"--
"fowl" with a "w"--
"--in regards to yourself."
You said some
very hurtful things to me
in regards to myself.
but it is still no excuse to
use the vile word that I used,
of which I am sure you know...
"that I'm talking about."
"Cunt," right?
Yes, Elliot.
"You don't wish us
to be social friends,
"and so that is that.
"I still have great 'rigard'
for you
"even though you said
some horrible things.
P.S. I'm doing fine. Anthony."
It came with a bathrobe
and a basketful of
Dr. Hauschka bath products.
Ablution.
The desire to cleanse himself
of the deed.
Notice he still
fundamentally blames me.
- Hello?
- Mrs. Soprano?
Robert Wegler.
Oh, hi! Hello, how are you?
Uh, after our meeting
the other day,
I had some ideas about some
further strategies for Anthony.
I thought maybe we could meet,
have lunch, a cup of coffee,
I could share them with you.
Next week, perhaps?
Really? Uh...
well, yeah, I guess
that would be okay.
"Happy Birthday" by the Beatles.
You know, I heard it
the other day in the car.
There's such a good drum solo
in the middle there.
Drum solo?
It's the basic 4/4.
You know, Ringo was not their
original drummer. That was Pete Best.
And they fired him.
He put out his own album,
"Best of the Beatles." Sad.
So is this what they call
common ground?
Just trying to have
a civilized conversation.
Can I go to my room? I'm full.
Am I so horrible?
You are not horrible.
Get over yourself.
Over myself?
What is that supposed to mean?
Just go. Do me a big favor.
If you're gonna be a martyr,
obviously I'll sit here.
No. Go.
Put your plate in the sink.
Two hundred.
Two to go.
See, and raise four.
- Call.
- So, Tony,
you're likin' the Escalade?
I can't keep 'em on the lot.
I love it. After I pulled out
that Global Positioning shit.
Oh, right.
Always got his eye
on the big picture.
Up to you.
I think you got that ace,
and I'm not payin' you for it.
- Aces over.
- Three treys, my man.
Paulie wins. Cards, please.
You fuck, you. Ahh.
Used to be a great tax
loophole, those SUVs.
Told all my clients,
"Write it off on your business."
Accountant dies, goes to heaven,
same time as the Pope.
Saint Peter says, "Come on in!"
Then he shows the Pope to this
shithouse, that's where he's gonna live,
and he gives him
a crust of bread.
Then he shows the CPA
where he's gonna live.
It's a fuckin' mansion--
servants, broads.
Pope says, "He gets a mansion
and I get a hovel?!"
Saint Peter says,
"Your Holiness,
we got hundreds
of popes up here.
This is the first
Jewish accountant!"
I used to be able
to write off condoms.
What do you get when you cross an
accountant with a giant jet airplane?
A Boring 747.
All right, all right. Bet two.
Algebra, huh?
Listen...
I have been doing some thinking.
I've decided to let you stay
in the city after the concert.
How come?
On one condition, though.
No Hudson Suites.
I talked to Mead. She said that
you can sleep over at her apartment.
I will give you cab fare. When the
concert's over, you go straight up there.
Sunday morning I want you home
ten-thirty sharp.
Thanks.
Don't stay up too late.
Come on, go! Go! Go! Hurry!
So, you guys like your job?
Beemer, space 43!
Whooooa!
♪ Siman tov and mazel tov
and mazel tov and siman tov ♪
♪ Yehe lanu ♪
- ♪ Yehe lanu, yehe lanu ♪
- Asa, come on!
♪ Ulechol Yisrael ♪
♪ Yehe lanu, yehe lanu ♪
♪ Siman tov and mazel tov
and mazel tov and siman tov ♪
♪ Yehe lanu ♪
♪ Yehe lanu, yehe lanu-- ♪
Can I have your attention?
Apparently there's been
an armed robbery.
Some automobiles were taken.
They left all the American cars!
- Oh, my God!
- I think his skull is broken.
- I'm a doctor. Let me in there.
Brooke, our car is gone.
Now who's a genius
for keeping his Regal?
Asa, they got the SL.
That was a fucking
SL55 convertible.
You know how long my brother
was on the waiting list for that thing?
A motherfucking year.
You want to go back to that?!
Yes! I want to go back to that!
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
- How was Mudvayne?
- They rocked.
Look, I-- look, I don't think I'm gonna
be able to make it up there.
What are you talking about?
You know Mom's gonna call here.
I'm a total dick
if I leave here.
Just tell Mom I'm on my way up.
She's just gonna call back.
Come on.
When do I ever
ask you for anything?
All right,
you better stay there.
And be home on time tomorrow.
I don't want any shit from Mom.
Frida, why do you and
Diego have separate houses?
Because we are
two different people,
but our love makes us into one.
- Hello?
- Mead, hi.
Is your brother there?
He's not answering his cell.
- I know. He's asleep.
- What?
I probably shouldn't be telling
you this, but he was pretty zapped.
I knew it. Is he all right?
Mom, he's fine.
Just wait until
you have children.
Not me. I'm never having kids.
So, how are things going?
We're in the middle
of a movie, Mom.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Good night.
G'night.
Come on, light this fucker up.
Gimme the lighter.
It's on the table.
All right, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Hold it! Hold it!
Open up, it's me.
Come on, open the fucking door!
Where's the patient?
I got a new easel, new oils--
- I'm ready to go.
- Salute.
The wedding! What, do you got
everybody outside,
the ushers and everybody?
Bring 'em in!
- Fuckin' disaster.
- What?
Somebody hit us. They stole
all the fuckin' cars.
I had to sedate my own little
girl at her wedding.
Jesus.
I mean, they had one of those,
whaddya call it, those car carrier things?
And it was a very
well-coordinated operation.
The cops are on it, but ya know,
how much faith
have I got in that?
You gotta help me
before they're chopped!
I'm not really
in that business, Ira.
Asa's brother's Benz
was taken, this special thing.
I'm fuckin' gornisht
in Asa's eyes now.
Can't you do anything?
I mean, make some calls?
- Well, that shit's insured.
- He's obsessed with that car,
this fucking Stew guy.
The asshole paid
a $30,000 premium
just to place the fuckin' order.
His glasses, his daybook
were in it.
A.J., it's your mother. Call me.
Ohh. It's my mother.
Ma'am, I told you,
I can't put you through.
- Room 417 has a block on the line.
- I am not waiting.
Who knows what's going on?
God help you if anything
happens in there
like those children
in Westchester.
No! No, don't answer it!
My face is stuck to the rug!
They fuckin' Krazy Glued you.
Housekeeping!
Fuck. What should we do?
We're asleep!
All right, help me.
Ow! Ow!
- Ow! Dude, take it easy.
- I'm trying.
Aaaah. Ow.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, dude.
Ohhh... fuck.
Oh, fuck me.
- Hello.
- Hi, yeah, it's me.
A.J. stayed in the city
with his friends last night,
and he's not home yet, and
I can't get in touch with him.
Take it easy. Slow down.
He's probably
just sleepin' it off.
No, I called Todd's mother,
and Todd came home.
He could be dead by now.
O.D.'ed, God knows what else.
- God, why did I let him go?
- He's all right.
I'll take care of it.
Gimme the number of the hotel.
It's the Hudson Suites
on the West Side.
Tony, just go there, all right?
I am so worried
I'm not even angry anymore.
Alright, alright, I'm on my way.
Anthony?
Goddamn you!
I have been going crazy
trying to reach you!
- Later. I don't feel good.
- What happened to your face?
- Just leave me alone!
- I want to know what happened!
You never even went to Meadow's
after you gave me your word!
- Get off my back!
- You are a liar!
- Fuck you.
- What did you say?
Get back here!
Ohh!
Fuck.
Puritan Salvage.
The big guy's lookin'
for a consignment
from a wedding
in Ringwood last night.
Nothin' came in here.
This Benz
SL55, he wants it pulled.
I'll make some calls.
- Where is he?
- In his room.
What happened to your leg?
He lied to me, Tony,
which means they both lied.
She's coverin' for him.
It's what sisters
are supposed to do.
Oh, of course, right.
He cursed at me. Oh, my God.
What did he say?
He's asleep.
Not anymore.
Oh. Hey, Dad.
I was just takin' out the trash.
It's garbage day tomorrow.
What's different about you?
He has no eyebrows, Tony.
Who did this?
We were just screwin' around.
- What'd you say to your mother?
- Tony--
- What did you say?
- I said the F-word.
You're finished. You're never
gonna drive that fuckin' car
till you're 45 years old.
I'm sellin' it tomorrow!
She wouldn't let me talk! I was
trying to tell her what happened.
Oh, see? It's my fault.
Alright, let's hear it.
Well, I-I was gonna go to
Meadow's, but there weren't any cabs.
And I didn't think you'd want me
sitting in the street
at 11:30 at night,
and we were right by the hotel.
- Enough of your lying.
- I am not lying.
Look at your face!
If you got some kind of sexual
proclivity with that teacher or whatever,
now's the time to tell us. I
mean, what went on up there?
- Poppers and weird sex!
- What?!
No! Look, we don't do drugs,
we're not some stupid dopers.
I had a few beers,
but it just made me sick.
How can anybody believe
what you say?
Because I told you.
You never believe me.
- You had a couple beers.
- Yeah.
- You didn't do any drugs?
- No.
Alright, Carmela, look,
a... coupla beers.
Should be grounded, yeah,
but it's not the end of the world.
What?!
Oh, you know what?
I am sick of your bullshit,
both of you.
- He can go live with you.
- Don't get dramatic now, all right?
- What? Great. Good!
- Shut up!
I have never been
more serious in my life.
Take out the trash. Go outside.
What are we gonna do? Really.
What did I just say?
No, I mean, really. Come on.
Did you think I was joking?
Carmela, this is
normal teenage shit.
You remember us?
The CYO dance. We left Artie out in
the snow. He almost lost his fingers.
And we still
laugh our asses off about it.
No, I don't really blame A.J.
He's doing exactly
what he's supposed to.
He's testing the limits
as much as he can.
- I blame myself.
- What are ya talkin' about?
You don't know what it's like
to have your son hate your guts.
He doesn't hate your guts.
Oh, thank God he's alive.
It's my fault, Tony.
My pathetic need to compete
with you clouded my judgement.
Or I never woulda let him stay over
in New York. I knew he wasn't ready!
I went against all my instincts.
His eyebrows'll grow back!
Nothin' really happened!
No, you know what happened,
I said fuck it.
And you know why?
To get him to love me
as much as he loves you.
He loves you. It's just--
You're his mother. It's different.
I can't be the villain anymore.
I mean it.
And I can't say fuck it.
Take him. Let him live with you.
Homina homma homma homma...
- Ed Norton?
Sorry, Mr. Kramden. No, the
correct answer is Stephen Foster.
But thanks so much, you've been a
wonderful contestant and a swell sport.
Goodbye, Mr. Kramden.
He's here.
Hey! Tarall's,
expiration date 2007.
Over there.
Have a seat.
Uh-oh.
Sounds serious.
You have anything to do with that
wedding takedown in Ringwood?
Why, is that a problem?
I told you that doctor
was a friend of mine.
I deliberately used that word.
Are you aware of how many things
a fuckin' M.D. can do for us?
Sorry, Godfather.
He was in the game.
I thought he was just
another pigeon.
Who authorized you to do it?
And don't call me godfather
with that fuckin' cute smirk.
I know I was away
for a long time,
but when did that happen,
you gotta ask permission
to ply your trade?
Here's your end! Be happy!
When were you gonna tell me
about it if I hadn't called you here?
I'm here now!
I'm tellin' you about it now!
That's the second time
I'm playin' catch-up with you!
- What the fuck are you talkin' about?!
- The lawn cuttin'!
I have to send you a memo
every time I move my bowels,
too?!
You're so concerned
about my end, why didn't you
put one of those cars
through my shops?
What? Johnny Sack told me
about this guy in Newberg.
- Johnny Sack?
- Yeah, Johnny Sack.
Anyway, he gave me a better deal
for shippin' 'em whole.
Are you fuckin' serious?
I don't like the way
I'm being talked to here!
What did I tell you
when you came to me,
said you wanted back in?
I said as long as you don't
step on anybody's toes.
- In my day--
- And that's another thing.
I don't wanna hear no more
about how it was in your day.
You just keep your antidotes
to local color,
like Dynaflows or McGuire
Sisters or shit like that.
Otherwise, shut the fuck up!
Jesus Christ, Feech, I'm tryin'
to ease your transition here,
and this is the thanks I get?
I'm sorry if I offended you.
You gotta remember, Tony,
I still think of you as a kid.
I'll learn.
Yeah?
Yeah.
That's funny!
C'mere.
Ah, shit.
We all right?
Just... get the SL55 back, okay?
Ya know, maybe I was
too hard on that guy.
Did I learn nothin'
from Richie Aprile?
Huh?
Nip it in the bud.
Feech?
He's well liked, T.
That's another thing.
All right, well,
don't be so hard
on yourself, though.
- Hey! Olsen and Johnson.
- How ya doin'?
We stopped by the bakery,
they said you left already.
That's the Canali suit
I promised ya.
He said you should
try on the jacket,
see how the sleeves are.
- How's that?
I look better than Sinatra.
- Very nice.
- All right.
Hey, I'm havin' my wine
and peaches... you want?
No, thanks. We gotta get goin'.
- I'll try some peaches.
- Good!
Peaches are from
fuckin' New Zealand.
They're great.
I'll get you a glass.
No, we should go, we should go.
Take care of that thing.
It can't wait?
Where the fuck ya goin'?
Come on, sit down.
We gotta do this shit. You don't
wanna know, it's all fucked up.
What?
My imbecile cousin,
he was weldin' his boat trailer,
burns down his garage.
Now we got no place
to park the truck that we got.
What's wrong with the street?
Georgia peaches. Those
are considered the best.
See, he don't want me
to know what's in the truck.
Flat screen TVs,
50-inch plasma Philipses.
Guy's comin' down from Montreal,
but he got delayed a coupla days.
- I got a garage right here.
- My cousin's mother's got a place,
- we can lock it up there.
- Park the load here.
This way I'm around,
keep my glims on the stuff.
Yeah? How much you
gonna want for that?
- Two.
- Fuck you, Feech!
- It's fuckin' parkin'.
- You gotta kick in a TV.
Thought I had a plan
for Anthony,
but I'm not so sure now.
I don't know if Rutgers's
summer program
accepts boys without eyebrows.
So you heard about that.
I was a wreck.
I mean, look what happened to
those girls just drivin' to school.
We brought in grief counselors.
How's Anthony coping with that?
I have to say,
he never mentioned it.
They all handle tragedy
differently.
Actually, he just
moved in with his father.
- I don't know if he said.
- Really?
I don't know what you might
have heard about my husband.
Some.
I mean, he's a good father,
don't get me wrong.
Our daughter is at Columbia.
My friends tell me I'm a snob
with this college business,
but with Anthony,
it's something else.
I just know that if he didn't get into a
good enough school to interest him,
and he dropped out, went to
work as a waiter or something,
he wouldn't last a week.
He would be drawn
right in... you know.
My husband doesn't
want that for him either.
You met him. My husband
can be very magnetic.
Bigger than life.
And I was so young.
It was very exciting.
Anyway, he's over there.
I don't know,
maybe it'll be good,
you know, learning the things
that men need to know.
Well...
Anyway, so what about you? How
long have you been at the school?
Since '86.
I suppose that's what
caught me up too, with Astrid.
Some notion of escaping
the quotidian.
So you were married.
For about, well, five minutes.
Chicken marsala?
And the honey balsamic chicken.
Thank you.
Hey, have you read
Madame Bovary?
- No.
- It's almost a perfect novel.
Flaubert writes about bourgeois
loneliness and emptiness.
Emma Bovary destroys herself
for some fantasy in her head.
It's great. It's truly great.
Somehow horrifically funny,
though tragic...
I think you might enjoy it.
Well, I will stop by Borders
on my way home. Heh heh.
Who was it by again?
Gustave Flaubert.
Heh heh.
Heh.
Yeah?
Supervisor Curran, parole board.
Site visit.
Where's Eddie Stimich?
He's out sick.
Just wanna take a look around.
The only thing better about here
than Russia is the food.
Good one.
Eddie examined every fuckin'
dust bunny in the place
- just last week.
- Is that new?
Uh...
Bequest. Friend of mine
passed away.
That your garage?
Nah. It's where I make
the weapons of mass destruction.
Let's go out and open it up.
You wanna see my fuckin' garage?
You never seen
an oil stain before?
Let's go.
Here's the wind-up...
and the pitch.
- Aw!
- Come on!
Fuck Major League Baseball.
Ever since the fuckin' strike.
Let's watch ballet.
Oh, somebody hot-boxed us?
I saw you close the window!
- What's that?
- It's when you close all the windows
and fart on purpose.
That's a "Dutch oven."
In bed it's a Dutch oven.
Well, what's a Dutch oven?
When you fart in bed
with a woman
and you force her head
under the covers.
That's awesome.
Yeah, but first you gotta
be in bed with one.
Yeah, you'd be surprised.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
Yeah, I would.
Oh, my God! What-- Jesus!
All right, that's enough. Go
upstairs, do your Spanish homework.
Gimme fifteen minutes.
No. Now.
Charge!
And he goes down looking.
The end of the inning.
Just got the call.
They put him on a
Corrections bus this morning.
This was the better move
than takin' him out.
Man was a legend.
Christopher agrees, by the way.
That's nice that he agrees.
But I'm not runnin'
a fuckin' popularity contest.
Mommy! Look at me!
Anthony!